[{"front": "\u529b", "id": "1419243697042", "back": "\u529b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e62596d5-59e2-48c4-b30c-432cd75530fc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u529b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u529b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1ef1c"}, {"front": "l\u1ef1c", "id": "1419243697043", "back": "l\u1ef1c  <hr id=answer>  \u529b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e62596d5-59e2-48c4-b30c-432cd75530fc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u529b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u529b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u52f9", "id": "1419243710282", "back": "\u52f9 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52f9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52f9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  bao"}, {"front": "bao", "id": "1419243710283", "back": "bao  <hr id=answer>  \u52f9 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52f9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52f9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u52fa", "id": "1419243725829", "back": "\u52fa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/94a2085a-d540-44f8-b558-46afee51dc9a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52fa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52fa\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u01b0\u1edbc"}, {"front": "ch\u01b0\u1edbc", "id": "1419243725830", "back": "ch\u01b0\u1edbc  <hr id=answer>  \u52fa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/94a2085a-d540-44f8-b558-46afee51dc9a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52fa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52fa\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7684", "id": "1419243734997", "back": "\u7684 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/15b64972-c363-4d07-a8cd-c8aa3557a0b1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7684\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7684\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00edch"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00edch", "id": "1419243734998", "back": "\u0111\u00edch  <hr id=answer>  \u7684 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/15b64972-c363-4d07-a8cd-c8aa3557a0b1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7684\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7684\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f60", "id": "1419243753218", "back": "\u4f60 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/64f9a53d-fc52-4fa5-84b3-656cd223f171/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f60\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f60\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nh\u0129, n\u1ec5"}, {"front": "nh\u0129, n\u1ec5", "id": "1419243753219", "back": "nh\u0129, n\u1ec5  <hr id=answer>  \u4f60 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/64f9a53d-fc52-4fa5-84b3-656cd223f171/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f60\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f60\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5b57", "id": "1419243767776", "back": "\u5b57 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e2458b9d-6460-4cf9-bf12-de488cc8c9e3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b57\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b57\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ef1 (letter)"}, {"front": "t\u1ef1 (letter)", "id": "1419243767777", "back": "t\u1ef1 (letter)  <hr id=answer>  \u5b57 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e2458b9d-6460-4cf9-bf12-de488cc8c9e3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b57\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b57\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5915", "id": "1419243778714", "back": "\u5915 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5915\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5915\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ecbch"}, {"front": "t\u1ecbch", "id": "1419243778715", "back": "t\u1ecbch  <hr id=answer>  \u5915 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5915\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5915\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u540d", "id": "1419243787163", "back": "\u540d <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u540d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u540d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  danh"}, {"front": "danh", "id": "1419243787164", "back": "danh  <hr id=answer>  \u540d <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u540d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u540d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e48<div><br /></div><div>\u4ec0\u4e48</div>", "id": "1419243827225", "back": "\u4e48<div><br /></div><div>\u4ec0\u4e48</div> <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e48<div><br /></div><div>\u4ec0\u4e48</div>\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e48<div><br /></div><div>\u4ec0\u4e48</div>\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  <div>y\u00eau, ma</div><div><div>tiny / small / insignificant</div><div>one / lone / alone</div></div><div><br /></div><div>th\u1eadp ma</div>"}, {"front": "<div>y\u00eau, ma</div><div><div>tiny / small / insignificant</div><div>one / lone / alone</div></div><div><br /></div><div>th\u1eadp ma</div>", "id": "1419243827226", "back": "<div>y\u00eau, ma</div><div><div>tiny / small / insignificant</div><div>one / lone / alone</div></div><div><br /></div><div>th\u1eadp ma</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e48<div><br /></div><div>\u4ec0\u4e48</div> <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e48<div><br /></div><div>\u4ec0\u4e48</div>\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e48<div><br /></div><div>\u4ec0\u4e48</div>\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ec0", "id": "1419243857072", "back": "\u4ec0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/89ae0297-2c3c-4eca-b306-47b911f3e422/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ec0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ec0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1eadp (sundry / miscellaneous / ten)"}, {"front": "th\u1eadp (sundry / miscellaneous / ten)", "id": "1419243857073", "back": "th\u1eadp (sundry / miscellaneous / ten)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ec0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/89ae0297-2c3c-4eca-b306-47b911f3e422/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ec0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ec0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53eb", "id": "1419243879760", "back": "\u53eb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0649d7ba-61fc-47f3-8c30-a69cba92f0fa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53eb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53eb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  khi\u1ebfu<div><br /></div>"}, {"front": "khi\u1ebfu<div><br /></div>", "id": "1419243879761", "back": "khi\u1ebfu<div><br /></div>  <hr id=answer>  \u53eb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0649d7ba-61fc-47f3-8c30-a69cba92f0fa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53eb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53eb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5929", "id": "1419243894449", "back": "\u5929 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5929\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5929\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thi\u00ean (sky)"}, {"front": "thi\u00ean (sky)", "id": "1419243894450", "back": "thi\u00ean (sky)  <hr id=answer>  \u5929 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5929\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5929\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u767d ", "id": "1419243910843", "back": "\u767d  <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a886b58e-5ca4-4b9f-84e7-469f5a42444d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u767d \">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u767d \">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ea1ch<div><br /></div>"}, {"front": "b\u1ea1ch<div><br /></div>", "id": "1419243910844", "back": "b\u1ea1ch<div><br /></div>  <hr id=answer>  \u767d  <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a886b58e-5ca4-4b9f-84e7-469f5a42444d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u767d \">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u767d \">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u767e", "id": "1419243926638", "back": "\u767e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4f742823-1c06-45ec-8f04-bf102ddb6a3b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u767e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u767e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00e1ch"}, {"front": "b\u00e1ch", "id": "1419243926639", "back": "b\u00e1ch  <hr id=answer>  \u767e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4f742823-1c06-45ec-8f04-bf102ddb6a3b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u767e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u767e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5341", "id": "1419244184514", "back": "\u5341 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5341\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5341\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ten<div><br /></div>"}, {"front": "ten<div><br /></div>", "id": "1419244184515", "back": "ten<div><br /></div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5341 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5341\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5341\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e5d", "id": "1419244194833", "back": "\u4e5d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/91286ace-8035-4cef-9f1c-5b7f0286b03d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e5d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e5d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nine"}, {"front": "nine", "id": "1419244194834", "back": "nine  <hr id=answer>  \u4e5d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/91286ace-8035-4cef-9f1c-5b7f0286b03d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e5d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e5d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5200", "id": "1419244204972", "back": "\u5200 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5200\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5200\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  dao"}, {"front": "dao", "id": "1419244204973", "back": "dao  <hr id=answer>  \u5200 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5200\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5200\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u516b", "id": "1419244214940", "back": "\u516b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/989ffec8-b4aa-4586-a118-d8b83d4054d5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u516b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u516b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  eight<div><br /></div>"}, {"front": "eight<div><br /></div>", "id": "1419244214941", "back": "eight<div><br /></div>  <hr id=answer>  \u516b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/989ffec8-b4aa-4586-a118-d8b83d4054d5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u516b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u516b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e03", "id": "1419244235321", "back": "\u4e03 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/12bceb54-5dff-499c-b657-eb64779a5abc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e03\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e03\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  seven"}, {"front": "seven", "id": "1419244235322", "back": "seven  <hr id=answer>  \u4e03 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/12bceb54-5dff-499c-b657-eb64779a5abc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e03\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e03\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u516d", "id": "1419244243088", "back": "\u516d <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u516d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u516d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  six"}, {"front": "six", "id": "1419244243089", "back": "six  <hr id=answer>  \u516d <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u516d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u516d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e94", "id": "1419244251120", "back": "\u4e94 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e2873209-1c85-4574-9d83-e099e35eca27/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e94\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e94\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  five"}, {"front": "five", "id": "1419244251121", "back": "five  <hr id=answer>  \u4e94 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e2873209-1c85-4574-9d83-e099e35eca27/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e94\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e94\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u56db", "id": "1419244258349", "back": "\u56db <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u56db\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u56db\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  four"}, {"front": "four", "id": "1419244258350", "back": "four  <hr id=answer>  \u56db <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u56db\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u56db\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e0b", "id": "1419244273198", "back": "\u4e0b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/44cc2e21-2953-405c-b15e-cadb9f915135/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e0b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e0b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ea1 (down)"}, {"front": "h\u1ea1 (down)", "id": "1419244273199", "back": "h\u1ea1 (down)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e0b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/44cc2e21-2953-405c-b15e-cadb9f915135/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e0b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e0b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e0a", "id": "1419244281587", "back": "\u4e0a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/44cc2e21-2953-405c-b15e-cadb9f915135/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e0a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e0a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u01b0\u1ee3ng"}, {"front": "th\u01b0\u1ee3ng", "id": "1419244281588", "back": "th\u01b0\u1ee3ng  <hr id=answer>  \u4e0a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/44cc2e21-2953-405c-b15e-cadb9f915135/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e0a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e0a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6c34", "id": "1419244289824", "back": "\u6c34 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c34\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c34\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ee7y"}, {"front": "th\u1ee7y", "id": "1419244289825", "back": "th\u1ee7y  <hr id=answer>  \u6c34 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c34\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c34\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u52c7", "id": "1419244301020", "back": "\u52c7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5ac4bbc9-4bee-42a5-bce4-2f838bf6e573/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52c7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52c7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u0169ng"}, {"front": "d\u0169ng", "id": "1419244301021", "back": "d\u0169ng  <hr id=answer>  \u52c7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5ac4bbc9-4bee-42a5-bce4-2f838bf6e573/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52c7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52c7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6c38", "id": "1419244311345", "back": "\u6c38 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dd862507-0f3f-418f-9b82-4f832712b025/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c38\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c38\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u0129nh"}, {"front": "v\u0129nh", "id": "1419244311346", "back": "v\u0129nh  <hr id=answer>  \u6c38 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dd862507-0f3f-418f-9b82-4f832712b025/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c38\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c38\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u597d", "id": "1419559463986", "back": "\u597d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d8d93c48-0285-4ffb-8694-50f42577f0ff/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u597d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u597d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ea3o, hi\u1ebfu"}, {"front": "h\u1ea3o, hi\u1ebfu", "id": "1419559463987", "back": "h\u1ea3o, hi\u1ebfu  <hr id=answer>  \u597d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d8d93c48-0285-4ffb-8694-50f42577f0ff/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u597d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u597d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5973", "id": "1419561008996", "back": "\u5973 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e2a72bd7-4668-4579-8961-9b57a42b67f7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5973\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5973\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  n\u1eef, n\u1ee9, nh\u1eef"}, {"front": "n\u1eef, n\u1ee9, nh\u1eef", "id": "1419561008997", "back": "n\u1eef, n\u1ee9, nh\u1eef  <hr id=answer>  \u5973 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e2a72bd7-4668-4579-8961-9b57a42b67f7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5973\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5973\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8eab", "id": "1419570684149", "back": "\u8eab <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/014389cf-2e01-482b-b5a3-680d640ed44a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8eab\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8eab\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00e2n (body)"}, {"front": "th\u00e2n (body)", "id": "1419570684150", "back": "th\u00e2n (body)  <hr id=answer>  \u8eab <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/014389cf-2e01-482b-b5a3-680d640ed44a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8eab\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8eab\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f53", "id": "1419571368113", "back": "\u4f53 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7db9ebf6-08b3-436a-92ad-f01786797348/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f53\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f53\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ec3<div><br /></div><div>\u9ad4</div>"}, {"front": "th\u1ec3<div><br /></div><div>\u9ad4</div>", "id": "1419571368114", "back": "th\u1ec3<div><br /></div><div>\u9ad4</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4f53 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7db9ebf6-08b3-436a-92ad-f01786797348/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f53\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f53\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5462", "id": "1420596652767", "back": "\u5462 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4d3dd856-241e-4482-9be6-9a9c2fa4cda7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5462\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5462\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ni \uff08\uff1f\uff09"}, {"front": "ni \uff08\uff1f\uff09", "id": "1420596652768", "back": "ni \uff08\uff1f\uff09  <hr id=answer>  \u5462 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4d3dd856-241e-4482-9be6-9a9c2fa4cda7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5462\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5462\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u76ee", "id": "1420596879273", "back": "\u76ee <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fffaf35b-c6fb-4765-8644-0ab4cd5aba56/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76ee\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76ee\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ee5c (eye, category)"}, {"front": "m\u1ee5c (eye, category)", "id": "1420596879274", "back": "m\u1ee5c (eye, category)  <hr id=answer>  \u76ee <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fffaf35b-c6fb-4765-8644-0ab4cd5aba56/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76ee\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76ee\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u89c1", "id": "1420596944684", "back": "\u89c1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/928c87ce-bf3e-4576-a9b4-285e21f5ccfb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u89c1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u89c1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ki\u1ebfn, hi\u1ec7n"}, {"front": "ki\u1ebfn, hi\u1ec7n", "id": "1420596944685", "back": "ki\u1ebfn, hi\u1ec7n  <hr id=answer>  \u89c1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/928c87ce-bf3e-4576-a9b4-285e21f5ccfb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u89c1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u89c1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e0d", "id": "1420596978032", "back": "\u4e0d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b13ed3ed-d138-4881-9b9a-f759808ab2af/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e0d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e0d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ea5t"}, {"front": "b\u1ea5t", "id": "1420596978034", "back": "b\u1ea5t  <hr id=answer>  \u4e0d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b13ed3ed-d138-4881-9b9a-f759808ab2af/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e0d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e0d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e45", "id": "1420597017963", "back": "\u4e45 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ea95f6cf-39b5-47b0-a9be-a6dcc40e18aa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e45\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e45\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1eedu \uff08old\uff09"}, {"front": "c\u1eedu \uff08old\uff09", "id": "1420597017964", "back": "c\u1eedu \uff08old\uff09  <hr id=answer>  \u4e45 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ea95f6cf-39b5-47b0-a9be-a6dcc40e18aa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e45\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e45\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8c22", "id": "1420597055474", "back": "\u8c22 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7925ea76-1196-41dd-a977-4d50b25b280f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c22\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c22\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ea1"}, {"front": "t\u1ea1", "id": "1420597055475", "back": "t\u1ea1  <hr id=answer>  \u8c22 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7925ea76-1196-41dd-a977-4d50b25b280f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c22\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c22\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u662f", "id": "1420597101400", "back": "\u662f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/44732392-a89c-4376-bfbc-ee40feaf5272/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u662f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u662f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ecb (be)"}, {"front": "th\u1ecb (be)", "id": "1420597101401", "back": "th\u1ecb (be)  <hr id=answer>  \u662f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/44732392-a89c-4376-bfbc-ee40feaf5272/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u662f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u662f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5f88", "id": "1420597145505", "back": "\u5f88 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b02d9fc0-4905-4134-a292-789aec5d3c11/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f88\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f88\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u1eadn"}, {"front": "ng\u1eadn", "id": "1420597145506", "back": "ng\u1eadn  <hr id=answer>  \u5f88 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b02d9fc0-4905-4134-a292-789aec5d3c11/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f88\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f88\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6211", "id": "1420597177683", "back": "\u6211 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5d5fd14d-89bc-4c22-831a-e3c39665225d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6211\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6211\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u00e3"}, {"front": "ng\u00e3", "id": "1420597177684", "back": "ng\u00e3  <hr id=answer>  \u6211 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5d5fd14d-89bc-4c22-831a-e3c39665225d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6211\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6211\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5417", "id": "1420597211813", "back": "\u5417 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/757b41ce-b963-4925-983f-9db05e781a6b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5417\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5417\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ma (question)"}, {"front": "ma (question)", "id": "1420597211814", "back": "ma (question)  <hr id=answer>  \u5417 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/757b41ce-b963-4925-983f-9db05e781a6b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5417\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5417\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8a00", "id": "1420600800801", "back": "\u8a00 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5c36c0c1-1d28-4bb6-be38-cb6bf1108c6f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8a00\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8a00\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u00f4n (word)"}, {"front": "ng\u00f4n (word)", "id": "1420600800802", "back": "ng\u00f4n (word)  <hr id=answer>  \u8a00 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5c36c0c1-1d28-4bb6-be38-cb6bf1108c6f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8a00\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8a00\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c3c", "id": "1420600828283", "back": "\u5c3c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c00fcea1-a1c7-4979-a310-c0caa9ab6940/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c3c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c3c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ni (tu)"}, {"front": "ni (tu)", "id": "1420600828284", "back": "ni (tu)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c3c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c00fcea1-a1c7-4979-a310-c0caa9ab6940/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c3c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c3c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c38", "id": "1420600850463", "back": "\u5c38 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2fdc9474-7110-4e98-b5ae-a3fde3bb27ed/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c38\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c38\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thi (corpse)"}, {"front": "thi (corpse)", "id": "1420600850464", "back": "thi (corpse)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c38 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2fdc9474-7110-4e98-b5ae-a3fde3bb27ed/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c38\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c38\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u758b", "id": "1420600877522", "back": "\u758b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7ef939ff-1a14-452b-84c0-491e8c8d6226/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u758b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u758b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u01a1 (foot), th\u1ea5t (roll of cloth)"}, {"front": "s\u01a1 (foot), th\u1ea5t (roll of cloth)", "id": "1420600877523", "back": "s\u01a1 (foot), th\u1ea5t (roll of cloth)  <hr id=answer>  \u758b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7ef939ff-1a14-452b-84c0-491e8c8d6226/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u758b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u758b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u513f", "id": "1420747710113", "back": "\u513f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8f343d27-e7e1-4a5d-a613-ea482719f554/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u513f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u513f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nhi,&nbsp;nh\u00e2n<div>&nbsp;\u5152</div>"}, {"front": "nhi,&nbsp;nh\u00e2n<div>&nbsp;\u5152</div>", "id": "1420747710114", "back": "nhi,&nbsp;nh\u00e2n<div>&nbsp;\u5152</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u513f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8f343d27-e7e1-4a5d-a613-ea482719f554/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u513f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u513f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u518d\u89c1", "id": "1420749102887", "back": "\u518d\u89c1 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u518d\u89c1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u518d\u89c1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  see you gain"}, {"front": "see you gain", "id": "1420749102888", "back": "see you gain  <hr id=answer>  \u518d\u89c1 <br/> <a href=\"\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u518d\u89c1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u518d\u89c1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u91cc", "id": "1420882934033", "back": "\u91cc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ec32abf8-40b0-4b95-8751-3c3b95c6e829/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u91cc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u91cc\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u00ed (house, mile)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u88e1</div>"}, {"front": "l\u00ed (house, mile)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u88e1</div>", "id": "1420882934034", "back": "l\u00ed (house, mile)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u88e1</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u91cc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ec32abf8-40b0-4b95-8751-3c3b95c6e829/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u91cc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u91cc\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7ae5", "id": "1420883082802", "back": "\u7ae5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6174e83f-671d-476c-b6ae-af29247ff672/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ae5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ae5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ed3ng (child)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ed3ng (child)", "id": "1420883082803", "back": "\u0111\u1ed3ng (child)  <hr id=answer>  \u7ae5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6174e83f-671d-476c-b6ae-af29247ff672/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ae5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ae5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7acb", "id": "1420883115299", "back": "\u7acb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e6f1066a-6a44-4420-86cb-9846abc31131/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7acb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7acb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1eadp"}, {"front": "l\u1eadp", "id": "1420883115300", "back": "l\u1eadp  <hr id=answer>  \u7acb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e6f1066a-6a44-4420-86cb-9846abc31131/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7acb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7acb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e5f", "id": "1420883169116", "back": "\u4e5f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6d955a32-5e13-4a64-a589-c805bed6522b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e5f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e5f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u00e3"}, {"front": "d\u00e3", "id": "1420883169117", "back": "d\u00e3  <hr id=answer>  \u4e5f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6d955a32-5e13-4a64-a589-c805bed6522b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e5f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e5f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u518d", "id": "1420883204308", "back": "\u518d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/23885b37-213b-4935-b03b-6783f969ec47/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u518d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u518d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00e1i"}, {"front": "t\u00e1i", "id": "1420883204309", "back": "t\u00e1i  <hr id=answer>  \u518d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/23885b37-213b-4935-b03b-6783f969ec47/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u518d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u518d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u60a8", "id": "1420883243273", "back": "\u60a8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f33bb587-6923-43af-b1f6-736541a22e70/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u60a8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u60a8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  n\u00e2m"}, {"front": "n\u00e2m", "id": "1420883243274", "back": "n\u00e2m  <hr id=answer>  \u60a8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f33bb587-6923-43af-b1f6-736541a22e70/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u60a8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u60a8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5fc3", "id": "1420883270516", "back": "\u5fc3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bf394137-8fc8-4e05-9e45-963ffe17809a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fc3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fc3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00e2m"}, {"front": "t\u00e2m", "id": "1420883270517", "back": "t\u00e2m  <hr id=answer>  \u5fc3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bf394137-8fc8-4e05-9e45-963ffe17809a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fc3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fc3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5b66", "id": "1420883316015", "back": "\u5b66 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/20a881ee-9ec3-410a-92cc-7ce079f8bbe4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b66\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b66\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ecdc<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5b78</div>"}, {"front": "h\u1ecdc<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5b78</div>", "id": "1420883316016", "back": "h\u1ecdc<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5b78</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5b66 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/20a881ee-9ec3-410a-92cc-7ce079f8bbe4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b66\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b66\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u751f", "id": "1420883409993", "back": "\u751f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/90c75975-5f58-4727-b4fb-f4770c30d063/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u751f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u751f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  sinh"}, {"front": "sinh", "id": "1420883409994", "back": "sinh  <hr id=answer>  \u751f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/90c75975-5f58-4727-b4fb-f4770c30d063/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u751f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u751f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8001", "id": "1420883455248", "back": "\u8001 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5612caf0-4d40-4e97-b274-bfc612571ea6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8001\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8001\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u00e3o"}, {"front": "l\u00e3o", "id": "1420883455249", "back": "l\u00e3o  <hr id=answer>  \u8001 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5612caf0-4d40-4e97-b274-bfc612571ea6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8001\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8001\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e08", "id": "1420883510482", "back": "\u5e08 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6848fb57-f13f-4f8e-8151-6acf251c1e1a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e08\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e08\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u01b0"}, {"front": "s\u01b0", "id": "1420883510483", "back": "s\u01b0  <hr id=answer>  \u5e08 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6848fb57-f13f-4f8e-8151-6acf251c1e1a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e08\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e08\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5bf9", "id": "1420883556271", "back": "\u5bf9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/55776403-e761-4508-8e0b-cf3145fb21d6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bf9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bf9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ed1i (correct, opposite, couple)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5c0d</div>"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ed1i (correct, opposite, couple)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5c0d</div>", "id": "1420883556272", "back": "\u0111\u1ed1i (correct, opposite, couple)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5c0d</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5bf9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/55776403-e761-4508-8e0b-cf3145fb21d6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bf9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bf9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5df1", "id": "1420883618246", "back": "\u5df1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a2c97b83-e899-4412-b545-c8d366145181/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5df1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5df1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  k\u1ec9 (self)"}, {"front": "k\u1ec9 (self)", "id": "1420883618247", "back": "k\u1ec9 (self)  <hr id=answer>  \u5df1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a2c97b83-e899-4412-b545-c8d366145181/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5df1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5df1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8d70", "id": "1420883785268", "back": "\u8d70 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/076c88af-e09f-4c2b-8543-de7b4748bc29/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d70\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d70\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ea9u"}, {"front": "t\u1ea9u", "id": "1420883785269", "back": "t\u1ea9u  <hr id=answer>  \u8d70 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/076c88af-e09f-4c2b-8543-de7b4748bc29/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d70\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d70\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8d77", "id": "1420883874468", "back": "\u8d77 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f8031794-ded4-4991-80a2-35df67b00080/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d77\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d77\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u1edfi"}, {"front": "kh\u1edfi", "id": "1420883874469", "back": "kh\u1edfi  <hr id=answer>  \u8d77 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f8031794-ded4-4991-80a2-35df67b00080/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d77\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d77\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bcd", "id": "1420970083100", "back": "\u8bcd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bdbf065f-4640-43ce-9e04-409f9e4babd4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bcd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bcd\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1eeb (word)"}, {"front": "t\u1eeb (word)", "id": "1420970083101", "back": "t\u1eeb (word)  <hr id=answer>  \u8bcd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bdbf065f-4640-43ce-9e04-409f9e4babd4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bcd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bcd\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53f8", "id": "1420970127926", "back": "\u53f8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a2f9cf08-0dd4-4b0f-b142-b189aeee7db8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53f8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53f8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti, t\u01b0"}, {"front": "ti, t\u01b0", "id": "1420970127927", "back": "ti, t\u01b0  <hr id=answer>  \u53f8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a2f9cf08-0dd4-4b0f-b142-b189aeee7db8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53f8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53f8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bf7", "id": "1420970162242", "back": "\u8bf7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/be0119ef-20d7-4024-8d44-5753e13d7f86/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bf7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bf7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ec9nh"}, {"front": "th\u1ec9nh", "id": "1420970162243", "back": "th\u1ec9nh  <hr id=answer>  \u8bf7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/be0119ef-20d7-4024-8d44-5753e13d7f86/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bf7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bf7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9752", "id": "1420970190724", "back": "\u9752 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/70b171fc-e2f5-4bdd-9a9f-74b151f94aea/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9752\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9752\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thanh"}, {"front": "thanh", "id": "1420970190725", "back": "thanh  <hr id=answer>  \u9752 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/70b171fc-e2f5-4bdd-9a9f-74b151f94aea/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9752\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9752\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6708", "id": "1420970234943", "back": "\u6708 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/041cc386-26ac-4de5-b0a5-3bc90c4f9783/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6708\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6708\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nguy\u1ec7t"}, {"front": "nguy\u1ec7t", "id": "1420970234944", "back": "nguy\u1ec7t  <hr id=answer>  \u6708 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/041cc386-26ac-4de5-b0a5-3bc90c4f9783/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6708\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6708\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e95", "id": "1420970258889", "back": "\u4e95 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/801678e0-187e-4eef-acd1-19c84d16f17f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e95\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e95\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ec9nh (well/mine)"}, {"front": "t\u1ec9nh (well/mine)", "id": "1420970258890", "back": "t\u1ec9nh (well/mine)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e95 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/801678e0-187e-4eef-acd1-19c84d16f17f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e95\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e95\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5fd9", "id": "1421547355107", "back": "\u5fd9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d3482cde-6134-4173-8d8c-ddd98d534c85/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fd9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fd9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  mang (busy)"}, {"front": "mang (busy)", "id": "1421547355108", "back": "mang (busy)  <hr id=answer>  \u5fd9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d3482cde-6134-4173-8d8c-ddd98d534c85/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fd9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fd9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ea1", "id": "1421547440513", "back": "\u4ea1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fba3aa50-4211-4608-a7a9-025e5201a6a9/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ea1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ea1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  vong"}, {"front": "vong", "id": "1421547440514", "back": "vong  <hr id=answer>  \u4ea1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fba3aa50-4211-4608-a7a9-025e5201a6a9/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ea1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ea1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bed", "id": "1421547469940", "back": "\u8bed <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1f7d51cb-d7f5-4ac7-884b-527e590bbbd3/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bed\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bed\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u1eef"}, {"front": "ng\u1eef", "id": "1421547469941", "back": "ng\u1eef  <hr id=answer>  \u8bed <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1f7d51cb-d7f5-4ac7-884b-527e590bbbd3/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bed\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bed\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u543e", "id": "1421547493423", "back": "\u543e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f8859bc4-eb18-408d-b131-1edff3477789/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u543e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u543e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u00f4"}, {"front": "ng\u00f4", "id": "1421547493424", "back": "ng\u00f4  <hr id=answer>  \u543e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f8859bc4-eb18-408d-b131-1edff3477789/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u543e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u543e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6c49", "id": "1421547528818", "back": "\u6c49 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/89cf1960-75f5-469f-b327-4bdec9874ac3/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c49\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c49\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u00e1n<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u6f22</div>"}, {"front": "h\u00e1n<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u6f22</div>", "id": "1421547528819", "back": "h\u00e1n<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u6f22</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u6c49 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/89cf1960-75f5-469f-b327-4bdec9874ac3/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c49\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c49\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53c8", "id": "1421547554119", "back": "\u53c8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/51a8df6e-dd4e-4f08-8aca-f13e93b0fcf1/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53c8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53c8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ef1u (hand, both...and...)"}, {"front": "h\u1ef1u (hand, both...and...)", "id": "1421547554120", "back": "h\u1ef1u (hand, both...and...)  <hr id=answer>  \u53c8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/51a8df6e-dd4e-4f08-8aca-f13e93b0fcf1/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53c8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53c8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u96be", "id": "1421547574458", "back": "\u96be <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5840e85c-2c1f-4f3c-b524-0e3c88f2f71f/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u96be\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u96be\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nan<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u96e3</div>"}, {"front": "nan<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u96e3</div>", "id": "1421547574459", "back": "nan<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u96e3</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u96be <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5840e85c-2c1f-4f3c-b524-0e3c88f2f71f/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u96be\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u96be\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u96b9", "id": "1421547598772", "back": "\u96b9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9b4da2a1-1cdd-4d6a-9f7c-c5db9469eb46/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u96b9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u96b9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  chuy (bird)"}, {"front": "chuy (bird)", "id": "1421547598773", "back": "chuy (bird)  <hr id=answer>  \u96b9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9b4da2a1-1cdd-4d6a-9f7c-c5db9469eb46/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u96b9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u96b9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u592a", "id": "1421547621287", "back": "\u592a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/05f50571-b1f8-4d36-ad19-732240fc227b/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u592a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u592a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00e1i"}, {"front": "th\u00e1i", "id": "1421547621288", "back": "th\u00e1i  <hr id=answer>  \u592a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/05f50571-b1f8-4d36-ad19-732240fc227b/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u592a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u592a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7238", "id": "1421547658373", "back": "\u7238 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/70bf3061-dd35-49b9-8372-a4fbfd248e07/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7238\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7238\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ea3 (papa)"}, {"front": "b\u1ea3 (papa)", "id": "1421547658374", "back": "b\u1ea3 (papa)  <hr id=answer>  \u7238 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/70bf3061-dd35-49b9-8372-a4fbfd248e07/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7238\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7238\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5df4", "id": "1421547788156", "back": "\u5df4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4d15409a-01f5-4529-9322-68c194c91ab8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5df4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5df4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ba (desire, hope)"}, {"front": "ba (desire, hope)", "id": "1421547788157", "back": "ba (desire, hope)  <hr id=answer>  \u5df4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4d15409a-01f5-4529-9322-68c194c91ab8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5df4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5df4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7236", "id": "1421547808313", "back": "\u7236 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/db78cfb1-55dc-4a6f-9f08-b726814ab709/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7236\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7236\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u1ee5 (father)"}, {"front": "ph\u1ee5 (father)", "id": "1421547808314", "back": "ph\u1ee5 (father)  <hr id=answer>  \u7236 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/db78cfb1-55dc-4a6f-9f08-b726814ab709/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7236\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7236\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5988", "id": "1421547834794", "back": "\u5988 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9d0b95dc-09aa-45a9-a416-7f2a833fb60d/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5988\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5988\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ma (mom)"}, {"front": "ma (mom)", "id": "1421547834795", "back": "ma (mom)  <hr id=answer>  \u5988 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9d0b95dc-09aa-45a9-a416-7f2a833fb60d/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5988\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5988\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u54e5", "id": "1421547851278", "back": "\u54e5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/67a436b6-1186-49cc-954e-b69b309fc69f/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u54e5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u54e5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ca (brother)"}, {"front": "ca (brother)", "id": "1421547851279", "back": "ca (brother)  <hr id=answer>  \u54e5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/67a436b6-1186-49cc-954e-b69b309fc69f/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u54e5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u54e5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53ef", "id": "1421547872302", "back": "\u53ef <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e18979a4-6754-4277-b6b0-3f59867f2187/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53ef\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53ef\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u1ea3"}, {"front": "kh\u1ea3", "id": "1421547872303", "back": "kh\u1ea3  <hr id=answer>  \u53ef <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e18979a4-6754-4277-b6b0-3f59867f2187/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53ef\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53ef\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5f1f", "id": "1421547888217", "back": "\u5f1f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/feb0c0a0-b2dd-4e2f-92c6-c6f90f1a5afc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f1f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f1f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ec7"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ec7", "id": "1421547888218", "back": "\u0111\u1ec7  <hr id=answer>  \u5f1f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/feb0c0a0-b2dd-4e2f-92c6-c6f90f1a5afc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f1f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f1f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u59b9", "id": "1421547918790", "back": "\u59b9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e249e01c-c59d-4d0e-8337-ce615738c26d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u59b9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u59b9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  mu\u1ed9i"}, {"front": "mu\u1ed9i", "id": "1421547918791", "back": "mu\u1ed9i  <hr id=answer>  \u59b9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e249e01c-c59d-4d0e-8337-ce615738c26d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u59b9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u59b9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u672a", "id": "1421547940247", "back": "\u672a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/775a06d3-ffbb-4468-b715-d60622e64f32/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u672a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u672a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u1ecb, m\u00f9i (not yet, zodiac)"}, {"front": "v\u1ecb, m\u00f9i (not yet, zodiac)", "id": "1421547940248", "back": "v\u1ecb, m\u00f9i (not yet, zodiac)  <hr id=answer>  \u672a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/775a06d3-ffbb-4468-b715-d60622e64f32/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u672a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u672a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ed6", "id": "1421548070783", "back": "\u4ed6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/25c844d8-cf46-47ee-912d-0bdaece41287/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ed6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ed6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tha (male, other)"}, {"front": "tha (male, other)", "id": "1421548070784", "back": "tha (male, other)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ed6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/25c844d8-cf46-47ee-912d-0bdaece41287/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ed6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ed6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5979", "id": "1421548094945", "back": "\u5979 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/57f5f3e1-f93f-4861-afce-927346077f04/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5979\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5979\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tha (female)"}, {"front": "tha (female)", "id": "1421548094946", "back": "tha (female)  <hr id=answer>  \u5979 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/57f5f3e1-f93f-4861-afce-927346077f04/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5979\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5979\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7537", "id": "1421548119656", "back": "\u7537 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1e49e1c0-3150-403a-a04b-57f347023abb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7537\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7537\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nam (male)"}, {"front": "nam (male)", "id": "1421548119657", "back": "nam (male)  <hr id=answer>  \u7537 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1e49e1c0-3150-403a-a04b-57f347023abb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7537\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7537\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7530", "id": "1421548143026", "back": "\u7530 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/36242a1c-6d63-4cc9-b027-dc0173f59e34/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7530\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7530\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111i\u1ec1n"}, {"front": "\u0111i\u1ec1n", "id": "1421548143027", "back": "\u0111i\u1ec1n  <hr id=answer>  \u7530 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/36242a1c-6d63-4cc9-b027-dc0173f59e34/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7530\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7530\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u95e8", "id": "1421548179905", "back": "\u95e8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a24f1361-89d6-4b73-a517-91edd0ae0d62/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u95e8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u95e8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u00f4n"}, {"front": "m\u00f4n", "id": "1421548179906", "back": "m\u00f4n  <hr id=answer>  \u95e8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a24f1361-89d6-4b73-a517-91edd0ae0d62/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u95e8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u95e8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u95ee", "id": "1421548197478", "back": "\u95ee <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f49604c9-20b5-4157-a863-746cdc6d26af/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u95ee\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u95ee\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u1ea5n"}, {"front": "v\u1ea5n", "id": "1421548197479", "back": "v\u1ea5n  <hr id=answer>  \u95ee <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f49604c9-20b5-4157-a863-746cdc6d26af/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u95ee\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u95ee\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u59d3", "id": "1421548232079", "back": "\u59d3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cb344c62-047d-4418-a1dc-5e594318db8e/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u59d3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u59d3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00ednh"}, {"front": "t\u00ednh", "id": "1421548232080", "back": "t\u00ednh  <hr id=answer>  \u59d3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cb344c62-047d-4418-a1dc-5e594318db8e/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u59d3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u59d3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8d35", "id": "1421548261565", "back": "\u8d35 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/15d3b554-18df-46f6-9cbd-1e1e265c36f0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d35\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d35\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  qu\u00fd"}, {"front": "qu\u00fd", "id": "1421548261566", "back": "qu\u00fd  <hr id=answer>  \u8d35 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/15d3b554-18df-46f6-9cbd-1e1e265c36f0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d35\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d35\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5148", "id": "1421548335081", "back": "\u5148 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2aafbf95-d528-4088-bde6-71beedaea8ec/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5148\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5148\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u00ean (first, before)"}, {"front": "ti\u00ean (first, before)", "id": "1421548335082", "back": "ti\u00ean (first, before)  <hr id=answer>  \u5148 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2aafbf95-d528-4088-bde6-71beedaea8ec/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5148\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5148\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5427", "id": "1421548384710", "back": "\u5427 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bb97960b-8b07-4bc6-89ef-56a771677f2a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5427\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5427\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ba (final particle)"}, {"front": "ba (final particle)", "id": "1421548384711", "back": "ba (final particle)  <hr id=answer>  \u5427 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bb97960b-8b07-4bc6-89ef-56a771677f2a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5427\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5427\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8fdb", "id": "1421548404552", "back": "\u8fdb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6cb7e423-230b-4a78-974a-0b1abe0a3856/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fdb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fdb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u1ebfn<div>\u9032</div>"}, {"front": "ti\u1ebfn<div>\u9032</div>", "id": "1421548404553", "back": "ti\u1ebfn<div>\u9032</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8fdb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6cb7e423-230b-4a78-974a-0b1abe0a3856/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fdb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fdb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4eec", "id": "1421548439507", "back": "\u4eec <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d6e7b3bb-ae44-4de4-bff4-66e091e788ad/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4eec\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4eec\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u00f4n (person plural)"}, {"front": "m\u00f4n (person plural)", "id": "1421548439508", "back": "m\u00f4n (person plural)  <hr id=answer>  \u4eec <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d6e7b3bb-ae44-4de4-bff4-66e091e788ad/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4eec\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4eec\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8fd9", "id": "1421548477104", "back": "\u8fd9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a2922f7f-f4f8-4ce9-b57f-489b7631a722/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fd9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fd9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u00e1 (this)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9019</div>"}, {"front": "gi\u00e1 (this)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9019</div>", "id": "1421548477105", "back": "gi\u00e1 (this)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9019</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8fd9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a2922f7f-f4f8-4ce9-b57f-489b7631a722/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fd9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fd9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u90a3", "id": "1421548540082", "back": "\u90a3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ff7fa279-c10f-4cdd-89d0-0a80576905c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u90a3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u90a3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  na (that)"}, {"front": "na (that)", "id": "1421548540083", "back": "na (that)  <hr id=answer>  \u90a3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ff7fa279-c10f-4cdd-89d0-0a80576905c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u90a3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u90a3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u59d0", "id": "1421548572828", "back": "\u59d0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/319efa62-4b10-4ab0-ab78-60a2d8277628/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u59d0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u59d0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ea3, th\u01b0"}, {"front": "t\u1ea3, th\u01b0", "id": "1421548572829", "back": "t\u1ea3, th\u01b0  <hr id=answer>  \u59d0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/319efa62-4b10-4ab0-ab78-60a2d8277628/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u59d0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u59d0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e14", "id": "1421548643965", "back": "\u4e14 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e5e62045-e90d-4e3f-b87f-5b050e0a385d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e14\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e14\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ea3, th\u01b0 (still, both ... and ...)"}, {"front": "th\u1ea3, th\u01b0 (still, both ... and ...)", "id": "1421548643966", "back": "th\u1ea3, th\u01b0 (still, both ... and ...)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e14 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e5e62045-e90d-4e3f-b87f-5b050e0a385d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e14\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e14\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6b22", "id": "1421548660114", "back": "\u6b22 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/81012f04-3b31-4bf4-bad2-fe8e2e1a0e69/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b22\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b22\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  hoan<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u6b61</div>"}, {"front": "hoan<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u6b61</div>", "id": "1421548660115", "back": "hoan<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u6b61</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u6b22 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/81012f04-3b31-4bf4-bad2-fe8e2e1a0e69/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b22\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b22\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6b20", "id": "1421548699280", "back": "\u6b20 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b706f4ec-bf93-403e-93ec-e514c3fa658e/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b20\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b20\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  khi\u1ebfm (deficient)"}, {"front": "khi\u1ebfm (deficient)", "id": "1421548699281", "back": "khi\u1ebfm (deficient)  <hr id=answer>  \u6b20 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b706f4ec-bf93-403e-93ec-e514c3fa658e/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b20\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b20\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8fce", "id": "1421548719040", "back": "\u8fce <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1c1d58ee-f936-468d-91c5-594db7c4ae4d/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fce\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fce\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ngh\u00eanh"}, {"front": "ngh\u00eanh", "id": "1421548719041", "back": "ngh\u00eanh  <hr id=answer>  \u8fce <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1c1d58ee-f936-468d-91c5-594db7c4ae4d/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fce\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fce\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8c01", "id": "1421548883627", "back": "\u8c01 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ce9320fc-97ab-43cf-9ede-c65e6a3a41a0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c01\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c01\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00f9y (who)"}, {"front": "th\u00f9y (who)", "id": "1421548883628", "back": "th\u00f9y (who)  <hr id=answer>  \u8c01 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ce9320fc-97ab-43cf-9ede-c65e6a3a41a0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c01\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c01\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u670b", "id": "1421548903662", "back": "\u670b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ec190381-0e40-46a3-989c-9c47967be052/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u670b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u670b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1eb1ng (friend)"}, {"front": "b\u1eb1ng (friend)", "id": "1421548903663", "back": "b\u1eb1ng (friend)  <hr id=answer>  \u670b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ec190381-0e40-46a3-989c-9c47967be052/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u670b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u670b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53cb", "id": "1421548928507", "back": "\u53cb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6220b8d6-b558-408e-9744-f77be02eecdb/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53cb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53cb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1eefu (friend)"}, {"front": "h\u1eefu (friend)", "id": "1421548928508", "back": "h\u1eefu (friend)  <hr id=answer>  \u53cb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6220b8d6-b558-408e-9744-f77be02eecdb/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53cb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53cb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f4d", "id": "1421548996131", "back": "\u4f4d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fdb9c39d-a937-4bd8-adb9-f799bbb79d41/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f4d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f4d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u1ecb (person unit, position)"}, {"front": "v\u1ecb (person unit, position)", "id": "1421548996132", "back": "v\u1ecb (person unit, position)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f4d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fdb9c39d-a937-4bd8-adb9-f799bbb79d41/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f4d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f4d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u536c", "id": "1421830132803", "back": "\u536c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8a346586-7978-479d-8261-aa01d4dbd1ab/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u536c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u536c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ngang (lofty)"}, {"front": "ngang (lofty)", "id": "1421830132804", "back": "ngang (lofty)  <hr id=answer>  \u536c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8a346586-7978-479d-8261-aa01d4dbd1ab/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u536c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u536c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5189", "id": "1421830278972", "back": "\u5189 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/867219e5-304f-4bd1-a5a6-44f4d1967b94/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5189\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5189\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nhi\u1ec5m (gradually)"}, {"front": "nhi\u1ec5m (gradually)", "id": "1421830278973", "back": "nhi\u1ec5m (gradually)  <hr id=answer>  \u5189 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/867219e5-304f-4bd1-a5a6-44f4d1967b94/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5189\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5189\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5184", "id": "1421830304626", "back": "\u5184 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/05013b5d-4475-49ce-aa43-5e24661b84ad/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5184\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5184\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nhi\u1ec5m (hair)"}, {"front": "nhi\u1ec5m (hair)", "id": "1421830304627", "back": "nhi\u1ec5m (hair)  <hr id=answer>  \u5184 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/05013b5d-4475-49ce-aa43-5e24661b84ad/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5184\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5184\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u672b", "id": "1421830354185", "back": "\u672b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9bf3efb2-9991-4584-b6df-d6580b69f124/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u672b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u672b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ea1t (extremity, end)"}, {"front": "m\u1ea1t (extremity, end)", "id": "1421830354186", "back": "m\u1ea1t (extremity, end)  <hr id=answer>  \u672b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9bf3efb2-9991-4584-b6df-d6580b69f124/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u672b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u672b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u672c", "id": "1421830388876", "back": "\u672c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7c2b8eec-e56b-4926-a466-0e8677f53237/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u672c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u672c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ed5n, b\u1ea3n (root, this)"}, {"front": "b\u1ed5n, b\u1ea3n (root, this)", "id": "1421830388877", "back": "b\u1ed5n, b\u1ea3n (root, this)  <hr id=answer>  \u672c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7c2b8eec-e56b-4926-a466-0e8677f53237/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u672c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u672c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6587", "id": "1421830405433", "back": "\u6587 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1f4bcb68-9292-4be2-a190-669726a381b7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6587\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6587\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u0103n"}, {"front": "v\u0103n", "id": "1421830405434", "back": "v\u0103n  <hr id=answer>  \u6587 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1f4bcb68-9292-4be2-a190-669726a381b7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6587\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6587\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6b62", "id": "1421830443037", "back": "\u6b62 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1ef9a73d-ccde-4746-aeb6-7606d6ec8c23/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b62\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b62\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u1ec9 (stop)"}, {"front": "ch\u1ec9 (stop)", "id": "1421830443038", "back": "ch\u1ec9 (stop)  <hr id=answer>  \u6b62 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1ef9a73d-ccde-4746-aeb6-7606d6ec8c23/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b62\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b62\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8db3", "id": "1421830495783", "back": "\u8db3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0b7c8c7c-8e69-4bc2-8ce2-f1d21459e654/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8db3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8db3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00fac (foot, enough)"}, {"front": "t\u00fac (foot, enough)", "id": "1421830495784", "back": "t\u00fac (foot, enough)  <hr id=answer>  \u8db3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0b7c8c7c-8e69-4bc2-8ce2-f1d21459e654/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8db3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8db3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65a4", "id": "1421830525647", "back": "\u65a4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dfded83b-2c9a-480a-8f03-ff899be1d8fd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65a4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65a4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00e2n (ax, weight unit)"}, {"front": "c\u00e2n (ax, weight unit)", "id": "1421830525648", "back": "c\u00e2n (ax, weight unit)  <hr id=answer>  \u65a4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dfded83b-2c9a-480a-8f03-ff899be1d8fd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65a4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65a4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u51b0", "id": "1421830543729", "back": "\u51b0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bae3f7f8-b55b-4343-a401-09ccc3d536c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51b0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51b0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u0103ng (ice)"}, {"front": "b\u0103ng (ice)", "id": "1421830543730", "back": "b\u0103ng (ice)  <hr id=answer>  \u51b0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bae3f7f8-b55b-4343-a401-09ccc3d536c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51b0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51b0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7f8a", "id": "1421830562180", "back": "\u7f8a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bee22f36-a8fc-48c4-9db4-58cb1a89c7c8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7f8a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7f8a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u01b0\u01a1ng (goat)"}, {"front": "d\u01b0\u01a1ng (goat)", "id": "1421830562181", "back": "d\u01b0\u01a1ng (goat)  <hr id=answer>  \u7f8a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bee22f36-a8fc-48c4-9db4-58cb1a89c7c8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7f8a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7f8a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u821f", "id": "1421830583961", "back": "\u821f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/13241117-4167-4ec7-9de8-9eb264ccc3f5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u821f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u821f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  chu (boat)"}, {"front": "chu (boat)", "id": "1421830583962", "back": "chu (boat)  <hr id=answer>  \u821f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/13241117-4167-4ec7-9de8-9eb264ccc3f5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u821f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u821f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u98df", "id": "1421830636780", "back": "\u98df <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fd6cf134-0470-436e-9b67-d2de0fa8024b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u98df\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u98df\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ef1c (food, eat)<div><br /></div><div>\u9963</div>"}, {"front": "th\u1ef1c (food, eat)<div><br /></div><div>\u9963</div>", "id": "1421830636781", "back": "th\u1ef1c (food, eat)<div><br /></div><div>\u9963</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u98df <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fd6cf134-0470-436e-9b67-d2de0fa8024b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u98df\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u98df\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u79be", "id": "1421830654355", "back": "\u79be <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/19c949c5-c83d-43f6-9524-3a9aa596625b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79be\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79be\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u00f2a (grain)"}, {"front": "h\u00f2a (grain)", "id": "1421830654356", "back": "h\u00f2a (grain)  <hr id=answer>  \u79be <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/19c949c5-c83d-43f6-9524-3a9aa596625b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79be\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79be\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5315", "id": "1421830686315", "back": "\u5315 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/300428f7-658a-4e2a-af3a-40ad670041c3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5315\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5315\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u1ee7y (spoon, person radical)"}, {"front": "ch\u1ee7y (spoon, person radical)", "id": "1421830686316", "back": "ch\u1ee7y (spoon, person radical)  <hr id=answer>  \u5315 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/300428f7-658a-4e2a-af3a-40ad670041c3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5315\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5315\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5f73", "id": "1421830724824", "back": "\u5f73 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dfeaed11-68fd-4038-9bb1-ab14bc3d3c3f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f73\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f73\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u00edch (step, motion radical)"}, {"front": "x\u00edch (step, motion radical)", "id": "1421830724825", "back": "x\u00edch (step, motion radical)  <hr id=answer>  \u5f73 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dfeaed11-68fd-4038-9bb1-ab14bc3d3c3f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f73\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f73\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u884c", "id": "1421830756280", "back": "\u884c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/380bc78d-50d0-493d-ad06-14f940116e91/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u884c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u884c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u00e0nh, h\u1ea1nh, h\u00e0ng, h\u1ea1ng (walk)"}, {"front": "h\u00e0nh, h\u1ea1nh, h\u00e0ng, h\u1ea1ng (walk)", "id": "1421830756281", "back": "h\u00e0nh, h\u1ea1nh, h\u00e0ng, h\u1ea1ng (walk)  <hr id=answer>  \u884c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/380bc78d-50d0-493d-ad06-14f940116e91/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u884c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u884c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5902", "id": "1421830810518", "back": "\u5902 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/743377bf-d272-4c02-868e-f8334e351393/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5902\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5902\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tri, truy (go slowly)"}, {"front": "tri, truy (go slowly)", "id": "1421830810519", "back": "tri, truy (go slowly)  <hr id=answer>  \u5902 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/743377bf-d272-4c02-868e-f8334e351393/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5902\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5902\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u91d1", "id": "1421830828025", "back": "\u91d1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2bc99b55-3814-4ee2-8e5b-50ba99717cd7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u91d1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u91d1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kim (metal radical)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9485</div>"}, {"front": "kim (metal radical)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9485</div>", "id": "1421830828026", "back": "kim (metal radical)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9485</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u91d1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2bc99b55-3814-4ee2-8e5b-50ba99717cd7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u91d1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u91d1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9e1f&nbsp;\u9ce5&nbsp;", "id": "1421830844983", "back": "\u9e1f&nbsp;\u9ce5&nbsp; <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8cb87ac5-46b4-4413-87a9-e39d4925379d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9e1f&nbsp;\u9ce5&nbsp;\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9e1f&nbsp;\u9ce5&nbsp;\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111i\u1ec3u (bird)"}, {"front": "\u0111i\u1ec3u (bird)", "id": "1421830844984", "back": "\u0111i\u1ec3u (bird)  <hr id=answer>  \u9e1f&nbsp;\u9ce5&nbsp; <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8cb87ac5-46b4-4413-87a9-e39d4925379d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9e1f&nbsp;\u9ce5&nbsp;\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9e1f&nbsp;\u9ce5&nbsp;\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65b9", "id": "1421830876471", "back": "\u65b9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/350f4e07-0f0f-40e1-bb36-deb52a661c97/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65b9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65b9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u01b0\u01a1ng (square, direction, location)"}, {"front": "ph\u01b0\u01a1ng (square, direction, location)", "id": "1421830876472", "back": "ph\u01b0\u01a1ng (square, direction, location)  <hr id=answer>  \u65b9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/350f4e07-0f0f-40e1-bb36-deb52a661c97/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65b9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65b9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u793a", "id": "1421830905115", "back": "\u793a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/07769cc5-4ccb-4083-8283-416dbc0200a8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u793a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u793a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ecb (show, demonstrate)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u793b</div>"}, {"front": "th\u1ecb (show, demonstrate)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u793b</div>", "id": "1421830905116", "back": "th\u1ecb (show, demonstrate)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u793b</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u793a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/07769cc5-4ccb-4083-8283-416dbc0200a8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u793a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u793a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8f9b", "id": "1421830975901", "back": "\u8f9b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/07311c32-5166-4b0e-8a5d-f3434980ec4f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8f9b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8f9b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00e2n (bitter, hard)"}, {"front": "t\u00e2n (bitter, hard)", "id": "1421830975902", "back": "t\u00e2n (bitter, hard)  <hr id=answer>  \u8f9b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/07311c32-5166-4b0e-8a5d-f3434980ec4f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8f9b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8f9b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7cf8", "id": "1421831019276", "back": "\u7cf8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0bbc7b28-9b89-414d-91a6-e336f2db45fe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7cf8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7cf8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ecbch (silk)"}, {"front": "m\u1ecbch (silk)", "id": "1421831019277", "back": "m\u1ecbch (silk)  <hr id=answer>  \u7cf8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0bbc7b28-9b89-414d-91a6-e336f2db45fe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7cf8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7cf8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u72ac", "id": "1421831052390", "back": "\u72ac <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/36d6738b-b338-438f-95c6-80ab55515810/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u72ac\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u72ac\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  khuy\u1ec3n (dog, radical)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u72ad</div>"}, {"front": "khuy\u1ec3n (dog, radical)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u72ad</div>", "id": "1421831052391", "back": "khuy\u1ec3n (dog, radical)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u72ad</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u72ac <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/36d6738b-b338-438f-95c6-80ab55515810/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u72ac\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u72ac\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u96e8", "id": "1421831069436", "back": "\u96e8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/301ca772-f063-42ad-a3e4-5a4bbfdc9d40/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u96e8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u96e8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u0169 (rain)"}, {"front": "v\u0169 (rain)", "id": "1421831069437", "back": "v\u0169 (rain)  <hr id=answer>  \u96e8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/301ca772-f063-42ad-a3e4-5a4bbfdc9d40/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u96e8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u96e8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6535", "id": "1421831113667", "back": "\u6535 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/047eae26-0645-424a-87d9-ff81e92d69cc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6535\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6535\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  truy (knock, tap)"}, {"front": "truy (knock, tap)", "id": "1421831113668", "back": "truy (knock, tap)  <hr id=answer>  \u6535 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/047eae26-0645-424a-87d9-ff81e92d69cc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6535\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6535\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6237", "id": "1421831137012", "back": "\u6237 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ed23b096-e417-4dab-82e8-f2a8c438f606/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6237\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6237\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ed9 (door, house)<div>&nbsp;\u6236</div>"}, {"front": "h\u1ed9 (door, house)<div>&nbsp;\u6236</div>", "id": "1421831137013", "back": "h\u1ed9 (door, house)<div>&nbsp;\u6236</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u6237 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ed23b096-e417-4dab-82e8-f2a8c438f606/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6237\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6237\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9149", "id": "1421831194351", "back": "\u9149 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/94ffae75-8b2a-446e-a574-19a676099dc9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9149\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9149\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u1eadu (wine jug, one of 12 zodiac)"}, {"front": "d\u1eadu (wine jug, one of 12 zodiac)", "id": "1421831194352", "back": "d\u1eadu (wine jug, one of 12 zodiac)  <hr id=answer>  \u9149 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/94ffae75-8b2a-446e-a574-19a676099dc9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9149\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9149\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u76bf", "id": "1421831216084", "back": "\u76bf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/83bd19af-39c1-4c4d-8690-7e5d866c198f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76bf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76bf\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u00e3nh (bowl)"}, {"front": "m\u00e3nh (bowl)", "id": "1421831216085", "back": "m\u00e3nh (bowl)  <hr id=answer>  \u76bf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/83bd19af-39c1-4c4d-8690-7e5d866c198f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76bf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76bf\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7fbd", "id": "1421831239964", "back": "\u7fbd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/45fe8b60-be47-4ac5-a70f-8c8da266190b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7fbd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7fbd\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u0169 (bird feather)"}, {"front": "v\u0169 (bird feather)", "id": "1421831239965", "back": "v\u0169 (bird feather)  <hr id=answer>  \u7fbd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/45fe8b60-be47-4ac5-a70f-8c8da266190b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7fbd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7fbd\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8f66", "id": "1421831294023", "back": "\u8f66 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/535c822c-3788-41cd-837a-6123f56efe13/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8f66\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8f66\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  xa (cart)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8eca</div>"}, {"front": "xa (cart)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8eca</div>", "id": "1421831294024", "back": "xa (cart)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8eca</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8f66 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/535c822c-3788-41cd-837a-6123f56efe13/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8f66\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8f66\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4fe1", "id": "1422171095262", "back": "\u4fe1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a64d239f-d093-400b-bb36-0d1578a2ce92/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4fe1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4fe1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00edn (believe, mail)"}, {"front": "t\u00edn (believe, mail)", "id": "1422171095263", "back": "t\u00edn (believe, mail)  <hr id=answer>  \u4fe1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a64d239f-d093-400b-bb36-0d1578a2ce92/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4fe1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4fe1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53bb", "id": "1422171231228", "back": "\u53bb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ba8b3620-362e-4d5c-bfe9-cb8157eadcb6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53bb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53bb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u1ee9 (go, gone, in order to)"}, {"front": "kh\u1ee9 (go, gone, in order to)", "id": "1422171231229", "back": "kh\u1ee9 (go, gone, in order to)  <hr id=answer>  \u53bb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ba8b3620-362e-4d5c-bfe9-cb8157eadcb6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53bb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53bb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u94f6", "id": "1422171265105", "back": "\u94f6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dc0a6848-04a8-4e55-8f37-39db9e8f4263/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u94f6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u94f6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u00e2n (silver)"}, {"front": "ng\u00e2n (silver)", "id": "1422171265106", "back": "ng\u00e2n (silver)  <hr id=answer>  \u94f6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dc0a6848-04a8-4e55-8f37-39db9e8f4263/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u94f6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u94f6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u90ae", "id": "1422171343089", "back": "\u90ae <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e9be7890-b04b-47bc-b3fe-56ef3e21b851/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u90ae\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u90ae\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u01b0u (postal)&nbsp;<div>&nbsp;\u90f5</div>"}, {"front": "b\u01b0u (postal)&nbsp;<div>&nbsp;\u90f5</div>", "id": "1422171343090", "back": "b\u01b0u (postal)&nbsp;<div>&nbsp;\u90f5</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u90ae <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e9be7890-b04b-47bc-b3fe-56ef3e21b851/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u90ae\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u90ae\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c40", "id": "1422171456267", "back": "\u5c40 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/84a206ba-8074-409c-946b-333b44dd5993/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c40\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c40\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ee5c (bureau, circumstance)"}, {"front": "c\u1ee5c (bureau, circumstance)", "id": "1422171456268", "back": "c\u1ee5c (bureau, circumstance)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c40 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/84a206ba-8074-409c-946b-333b44dd5993/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c40\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c40\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8c55", "id": "1422171483182", "back": "\u8c55 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fe81a3be-e2b0-4ce2-80cb-f12605d71f2b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c55\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c55\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ec9 (pig)"}, {"front": "th\u1ec9 (pig)", "id": "1422171483183", "back": "th\u1ec9 (pig)  <hr id=answer>  \u8c55 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fe81a3be-e2b0-4ce2-80cb-f12605d71f2b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c55\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c55\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5bb6", "id": "1422171670272", "back": "\u5bb6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d07162ce-7e0d-429a-a08b-4ba54746ed95/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bb6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bb6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gia (house, family)"}, {"front": "gia (house, family)", "id": "1422171670273", "back": "gia (house, family)  <hr id=answer>  \u5bb6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d07162ce-7e0d-429a-a08b-4ba54746ed95/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bb6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bb6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8c6c", "id": "1422171699299", "back": "\u8c6c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3f76aaa0-e35b-4093-ac61-4256591742ab/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c6c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c6c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u01b0 (pig)"}, {"front": "tr\u01b0 (pig)", "id": "1422171699300", "back": "tr\u01b0 (pig)  <hr id=answer>  \u8c6c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3f76aaa0-e35b-4093-ac61-4256591742ab/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c6c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c6c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8005", "id": "1422171841747", "back": "\u8005 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/568fc286-4085-49d1-8fe5-8bb5046a9c6e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8005\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8005\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u1ea3 (someone who ..., -er -ist)"}, {"front": "gi\u1ea3 (someone who ..., -er -ist)", "id": "1422171841748", "back": "gi\u1ea3 (someone who ..., -er -ist)  <hr id=answer>  \u8005 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/568fc286-4085-49d1-8fe5-8bb5046a9c6e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8005\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8005\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ea5", "id": "1422171858010", "back": "\u4ea5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/33e3b2b2-8325-4bd3-be2c-3cf0a804e4b3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ea5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ea5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ee3i"}, {"front": "h\u1ee3i", "id": "1422171858011", "back": "h\u1ee3i  <hr id=answer>  \u4ea5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/33e3b2b2-8325-4bd3-be2c-3cf0a804e4b3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ea5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ea5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6709", "id": "1422171875457", "back": "\u6709 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/af4a13ca-bc09-4f09-b711-d11ae9691aca/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6709\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6709\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1eefu (have)"}, {"front": "h\u1eefu (have)", "id": "1422171875458", "back": "h\u1eefu (have)  <hr id=answer>  \u6709 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/af4a13ca-bc09-4f09-b711-d11ae9691aca/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6709\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6709\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u548c", "id": "1422171971018", "back": "\u548c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7313304e-0dea-4d65-be9d-2cecfc91d8bf/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u548c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u548c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u00f2a (harmony, and)"}, {"front": "h\u00f2a (harmony, and)", "id": "1422171971019", "back": "h\u00f2a (harmony, and)  <hr id=answer>  \u548c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7313304e-0dea-4d65-be9d-2cecfc91d8bf/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u548c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u548c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6bb3", "id": "1422172027611", "back": "\u6bb3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2a3fdb3d-8555-4265-ad4a-a1da4c865403/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bb3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bb3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00f9 (radical to make verb)"}, {"front": "th\u00f9 (radical to make verb)", "id": "1422172027612", "back": "th\u00f9 (radical to make verb)  <hr id=answer>  \u6bb3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2a3fdb3d-8555-4265-ad4a-a1da4c865403/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bb3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bb3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6ca1", "id": "1422172180460", "back": "\u6ca1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/817bfbac-bb92-461f-8412-f3d84c4f4582/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6ca1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6ca1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ed9t (not, drown, over, not yet)"}, {"front": "m\u1ed9t (not, drown, over, not yet)", "id": "1422172180461", "back": "m\u1ed9t (not, drown, over, not yet)  <hr id=answer>  \u6ca1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/817bfbac-bb92-461f-8412-f3d84c4f4582/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6ca1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6ca1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7237", "id": "1422172311849", "back": "\u7237 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9fa61756-1d2c-4178-8344-c9ffe8b61878/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7237\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7237\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gia (father, title for superior)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u723a</div>"}, {"front": "gia (father, title for superior)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u723a</div>", "id": "1422172311850", "back": "gia (father, title for superior)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u723a</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u7237 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9fa61756-1d2c-4178-8344-c9ffe8b61878/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7237\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7237\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5976", "id": "1422172365708", "back": "\u5976 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2890d593-cbab-473e-88a5-2b16b8883b1e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5976\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5976\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  n\u00e3i (milk, grandmother)"}, {"front": "n\u00e3i (milk, grandmother)", "id": "1422172365709", "back": "n\u00e3i (milk, grandmother)  <hr id=answer>  \u5976 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2890d593-cbab-473e-88a5-2b16b8883b1e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5976\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5976\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e43", "id": "1422172504171", "back": "\u4e43 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/82dd1d57-9a55-475a-8f09-98138b528556/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e43\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e43\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  n\u00e3i (be, then, indeed, you/your)"}, {"front": "n\u00e3i (be, then, indeed, you/your)", "id": "1422172504172", "back": "n\u00e3i (be, then, indeed, you/your)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e43 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/82dd1d57-9a55-475a-8f09-98138b528556/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e43\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e43\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5171", "id": "1422172570420", "back": "\u5171 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/91704afd-947c-4972-b5dc-229e587091c1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5171\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5171\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ed9ng (together)"}, {"front": "c\u1ed9ng (together)", "id": "1422172570421", "back": "c\u1ed9ng (together)  <hr id=answer>  \u5171 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/91704afd-947c-4972-b5dc-229e587091c1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5171\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5171\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e2a", "id": "1422172804633", "back": "\u4e2a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/19c1170a-77b5-4ee3-978e-b0e871d9c95f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e2a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e2a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00e1 (item, about, individual)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u500b</div>"}, {"front": "c\u00e1 (item, about, individual)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u500b</div>", "id": "1422172804634", "back": "c\u00e1 (item, about, individual)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u500b</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e2a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/19c1170a-77b5-4ee3-978e-b0e871d9c95f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e2a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e2a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u90fd", "id": "1422172931945", "back": "\u90fd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b9905945-fb2a-480b-aa5d-511ede517bdd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u90fd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u90fd\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00f4 (capital, all)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00f4 (capital, all)", "id": "1422172931946", "back": "\u0111\u00f4 (capital, all)  <hr id=answer>  \u90fd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b9905945-fb2a-480b-aa5d-511ede517bdd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u90fd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u90fd\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4eca", "id": "1422172963430", "back": "\u4eca <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/41a7200f-b5c0-45da-87aa-c8c72495ccea/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4eca\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4eca\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kim (present, now)"}, {"front": "kim (present, now)", "id": "1422172963431", "back": "kim (present, now)  <hr id=answer>  \u4eca <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/41a7200f-b5c0-45da-87aa-c8c72495ccea/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4eca\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4eca\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e74", "id": "1422173004855", "back": "\u5e74 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d43efc00-e730-4d68-884b-cced4fe5a225/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e74\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e74\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  <div>ni\u00ean (year, period)</div>"}, {"front": "<div>ni\u00ean (year, period)</div>", "id": "1422173004856", "back": "<div>ni\u00ean (year, period)</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5e74 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d43efc00-e730-4d68-884b-cced4fe5a225/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e74\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e74\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c81", "id": "1422173043558", "back": "\u5c81 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3bc7ada2-4f3f-48e8-b15a-b22a9d7d5661/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c81\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c81\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tu\u1ebf (year, age)<div>(\u6b72)</div>"}, {"front": "tu\u1ebf (year, age)<div>(\u6b72)</div>", "id": "1422173043559", "back": "tu\u1ebf (year, age)<div>(\u6b72)</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5c81 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3bc7ada2-4f3f-48e8-b15a-b22a9d7d5661/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c81\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c81\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bb8", "id": "1422173130994", "back": "\u8bb8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d3e5de80-380b-44d6-9996-e467a10186c3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bb8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bb8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ee9a (permit, promise, very)"}, {"front": "h\u1ee9a (permit, promise, very)", "id": "1422173130995", "back": "h\u1ee9a (permit, promise, very)  <hr id=answer>  \u8bb8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d3e5de80-380b-44d6-9996-e467a10186c3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bb8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bb8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5348", "id": "1422173161543", "back": "\u5348 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3ec50f27-b505-436f-aae8-f896898249c2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5348\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5348\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u1ecd (noon, zodiac)"}, {"front": "ng\u1ecd (noon, zodiac)", "id": "1422173161544", "back": "ng\u1ecd (noon, zodiac)  <hr id=answer>  \u5348 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3ec50f27-b505-436f-aae8-f896898249c2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5348\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5348\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u591a", "id": "1422173242480", "back": "\u591a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9a610ed5-2009-4855-86d7-40bb8500bb15/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u591a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u591a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111a (many/much, over/more than)"}, {"front": "\u0111a (many/much, over/more than)", "id": "1422173242481", "back": "\u0111a (many/much, over/more than)  <hr id=answer>  \u591a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9a610ed5-2009-4855-86d7-40bb8500bb15/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u591a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u591a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5b50", "id": "1422175073750", "back": "\u5b50 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a0d5fde0-ceb3-4588-9449-f382fe5ce8c4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b50\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b50\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1eed, t\u00ed"}, {"front": "t\u1eed, t\u00ed", "id": "1422175073751", "back": "t\u1eed, t\u00ed  <hr id=answer>  \u5b50 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a0d5fde0-ceb3-4588-9449-f382fe5ce8c4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b50\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b50\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5bf8", "id": "1422175094901", "back": "\u5bf8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9282e92f-f255-4cb4-8ab8-d72ae9d22356/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bf8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bf8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ed1n (inch)"}, {"front": "th\u1ed1n (inch)", "id": "1422175094902", "back": "th\u1ed1n (inch)  <hr id=answer>  \u5bf8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9282e92f-f255-4cb4-8ab8-d72ae9d22356/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bf8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bf8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8349", "id": "1422175555117", "back": "\u8349 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1967b62d-3eea-4e3a-8c08-f3da87fa33a8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8349\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8349\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ea3o (grass)<div><br /></div><div>\u8278&nbsp;</div>"}, {"front": "th\u1ea3o (grass)<div><br /></div><div>\u8278&nbsp;</div>", "id": "1422175555118", "back": "th\u1ea3o (grass)<div><br /></div><div>\u8278&nbsp;</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8349 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1967b62d-3eea-4e3a-8c08-f3da87fa33a8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8349\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8349\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65e9", "id": "1422175568448", "back": "\u65e9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/081c4408-b01e-439e-8e1b-1a7767a601fc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65e9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65e9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ea3o (early)"}, {"front": "t\u1ea3o (early)", "id": "1422175568449", "back": "t\u1ea3o (early)  <hr id=answer>  \u65e9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/081c4408-b01e-439e-8e1b-1a7767a601fc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65e9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65e9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5f13", "id": "1422175610922", "back": "\u5f13 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fc79789c-4955-4ce8-8adb-3257ce93f741/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f13\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f13\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  cung"}, {"front": "cung", "id": "1422175610923", "back": "cung  <hr id=answer>  \u5f13 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fc79789c-4955-4ce8-8adb-3257ce93f741/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f13\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f13\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8fb5", "id": "1422175641675", "back": "\u8fb5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f19a0380-8797-4d5d-9c52-476b7d929a04/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fb5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fb5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u01b0\u1edbc"}, {"front": "s\u01b0\u1edbc", "id": "1422175641676", "back": "s\u01b0\u1edbc  <hr id=answer>  \u8fb5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f19a0380-8797-4d5d-9c52-476b7d929a04/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fb5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fb5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6208", "id": "1422175695658", "back": "\u6208 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/71f2022a-d0b4-4002-9839-0cae0ca6cffd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6208\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6208\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  qua (halberd)"}, {"front": "qua (halberd)", "id": "1422175695659", "back": "qua (halberd)  <hr id=answer>  \u6208 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/71f2022a-d0b4-4002-9839-0cae0ca6cffd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6208\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6208\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8033", "id": "1422175708704", "back": "\u8033 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6a2a75ab-797a-46f0-adfa-c18b3dc0932b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8033\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8033\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nh\u0129 (ear)"}, {"front": "nh\u0129 (ear)", "id": "1422175708705", "back": "nh\u0129 (ear)  <hr id=answer>  \u8033 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6a2a75ab-797a-46f0-adfa-c18b3dc0932b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8033\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8033\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e72", "id": "1422260187308", "back": "\u5e72 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1200264e-3929-434b-9f5d-d12b9aef4cbc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e72\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e72\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  can (shield, Celestial Stem, bank (river), interfere)<div>&nbsp;\u4e7e</div>"}, {"front": "can (shield, Celestial Stem, bank (river), interfere)<div>&nbsp;\u4e7e</div>", "id": "1422260187309", "back": "can (shield, Celestial Stem, bank (river), interfere)<div>&nbsp;\u4e7e</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5e72 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1200264e-3929-434b-9f5d-d12b9aef4cbc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e72\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e72\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e7f", "id": "1422260272035", "back": "\u5e7f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/764d76e0-705c-439e-9d58-7b60dcc1c4f4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e7f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e7f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  qu\u1ea3ng (expand, expansive, width)<div>&nbsp;\u5ee3</div>"}, {"front": "qu\u1ea3ng (expand, expansive, width)<div>&nbsp;\u5ee3</div>", "id": "1422260272036", "back": "qu\u1ea3ng (expand, expansive, width)<div>&nbsp;\u5ee3</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5e7f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/764d76e0-705c-439e-9d58-7b60dcc1c4f4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e7f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e7f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u77f3", "id": "1422260287069", "back": "\u77f3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/be0e6d5d-883f-42e0-bf2e-4a14e09414af/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u77f3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u77f3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ea1ch (stone, barren)"}, {"front": "th\u1ea1ch (stone, barren)", "id": "1422260287070", "back": "th\u1ea1ch (stone, barren)  <hr id=answer>  \u77f3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/be0e6d5d-883f-42e0-bf2e-4a14e09414af/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u77f3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u77f3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8d1d", "id": "1422260395352", "back": "\u8d1d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fc310202-92f9-45e7-8a0a-c03b52cf580c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d1d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d1d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ed1i (shell)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8c9d</div>"}, {"front": "b\u1ed1i (shell)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8c9d</div>", "id": "1422260395353", "back": "b\u1ed1i (shell)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8c9d</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8d1d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fc310202-92f9-45e7-8a0a-c03b52cf580c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d1d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d1d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5de5", "id": "1422260556352", "back": "\u5de5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9062b61a-325f-40f1-8345-0b5b5cbf5e35/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5de5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5de5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00f4ng (work)"}, {"front": "c\u00f4ng (work)", "id": "1422260556353", "back": "c\u00f4ng (work)  <hr id=answer>  \u5de5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9062b61a-325f-40f1-8345-0b5b5cbf5e35/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5de5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5de5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u51e0", "id": "1422260678874", "back": "\u51e0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/efdd7903-de4a-4a7c-aea3-b334202c341a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51e0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51e0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  k\u1ec9 (table, what)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5e7e</div>"}, {"front": "k\u1ec9 (table, what)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5e7e</div>", "id": "1422260678875", "back": "k\u1ec9 (table, what)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5e7e</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u51e0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/efdd7903-de4a-4a7c-aea3-b334202c341a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51e0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51e0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5dfe", "id": "1422260919976", "back": "\u5dfe <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7c005d81-77ee-42ac-8ce1-62370b56fcbd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5dfe\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5dfe\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00e2n (kh\u0103n, turban)"}, {"front": "c\u00e2n (kh\u0103n, turban)", "id": "1422260919977", "back": "c\u00e2n (kh\u0103n, turban)  <hr id=answer>  \u5dfe <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7c005d81-77ee-42ac-8ce1-62370b56fcbd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5dfe\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5dfe\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u961c", "id": "1422261055903", "back": "\u961c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0ad7f96c-6eae-4c50-b9ae-7c9bde4fd558/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u961c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u961c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u1ee5 (mound, abundant)"}, {"front": "ph\u1ee5 (mound, abundant)", "id": "1422261055904", "back": "ph\u1ee5 (mound, abundant)  <hr id=answer>  \u961c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0ad7f96c-6eae-4c50-b9ae-7c9bde4fd558/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u961c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u961c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7a74", "id": "1422261272563", "back": "\u7a74 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/400756ff-a793-4425-9ab3-8a89182d9c30/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7a74\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7a74\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  huy\u1ec7t (cave, hole, acupuncture point)"}, {"front": "huy\u1ec7t (cave, hole, acupuncture point)", "id": "1422261272564", "back": "huy\u1ec7t (cave, hole, acupuncture point)  <hr id=answer>  \u7a74 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/400756ff-a793-4425-9ab3-8a89182d9c30/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7a74\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7a74\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u76ae", "id": "1422261476300", "back": "\u76ae <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c15dd68e-b0c1-4638-bb15-a3f56b6ca46e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76ae\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76ae\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00ec (skin)"}, {"front": "b\u00ec (skin)", "id": "1422261476301", "back": "b\u00ec (skin)  <hr id=answer>  \u76ae <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c15dd68e-b0c1-4638-bb15-a3f56b6ca46e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76ae\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76ae\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5317", "id": "1422261679384", "back": "\u5317 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/10cf21d7-3398-44a8-9571-8604463c616b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5317\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5317\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1eafc (north, defeated)"}, {"front": "b\u1eafc (north, defeated)", "id": "1422261679385", "back": "b\u1eafc (north, defeated)  <hr id=answer>  \u5317 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/10cf21d7-3398-44a8-9571-8604463c616b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5317\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5317\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4eac", "id": "1422261868751", "back": "\u4eac <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c73be64a-6e93-46a2-afdd-a990410848cd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4eac\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4eac\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kinh (capital, great)"}, {"front": "kinh (capital, great)", "id": "1422261868752", "back": "kinh (capital, great)  <hr id=answer>  \u4eac <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c73be64a-6e93-46a2-afdd-a990410848cd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4eac\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4eac\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7ebd", "id": "1422261992095", "back": "\u7ebd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8f51d5cf-71df-4b6a-9c1b-1518ecb26806/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ebd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ebd\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  n\u1eefu (button, tie)"}, {"front": "n\u1eefu (button, tie)", "id": "1422261992096", "back": "n\u1eefu (button, tie)  <hr id=answer>  \u7ebd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8f51d5cf-71df-4b6a-9c1b-1518ecb26806/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ebd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ebd\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e11", "id": "1422262217212", "back": "\u4e11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7468fa82-9418-4253-be9e-205d7ca8c1b9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e11\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u1eedu (second in Zodiac), x\u00fa (ugly)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u919c</div>"}, {"front": "s\u1eedu (second in Zodiac), x\u00fa (ugly)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u919c</div>", "id": "1422262217213", "back": "s\u1eedu (second in Zodiac), x\u00fa (ugly)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u919c</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7468fa82-9418-4253-be9e-205d7ca8c1b9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e11\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7ea6&nbsp;\u7d04", "id": "1422262328259", "back": "\u7ea6&nbsp;\u7d04 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/185c76b5-b27c-48bc-aaed-7b9b7d5925ac/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ea6&nbsp;\u7d04\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ea6&nbsp;\u7d04\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u01b0\u1edbc (agreement, approximate)"}, {"front": "\u01b0\u1edbc (agreement, approximate)", "id": "1422262328260", "back": "\u01b0\u1edbc (agreement, approximate)  <hr id=answer>  \u7ea6&nbsp;\u7d04 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/185c76b5-b27c-48bc-aaed-7b9b7d5925ac/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ea6&nbsp;\u7d04\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ea6&nbsp;\u7d04\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e2d", "id": "1422262659198", "back": "\u4e2d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bc3173d0-0d91-4e06-8a2a-4bc3939a81c8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e2d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e2d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  trung, tr\u00fang (middle, hit)"}, {"front": "trung, tr\u00fang (middle, hit)", "id": "1422262659199", "back": "trung, tr\u00fang (middle, hit)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e2d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bc3173d0-0d91-4e06-8a2a-4bc3939a81c8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e2d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e2d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u56fd", "id": "1422263196017", "back": "\u56fd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/12c9d1c3-a1b5-4f57-89d9-5c85b89972f5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u56fd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u56fd\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  qu\u1ed1c<div><br /><div>&nbsp;\u570b</div></div>"}, {"front": "qu\u1ed1c<div><br /><div>&nbsp;\u570b</div></div>", "id": "1422263196018", "back": "qu\u1ed1c<div><br /><div>&nbsp;\u570b</div></div>  <hr id=answer>  \u56fd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/12c9d1c3-a1b5-4f57-89d9-5c85b89972f5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u56fd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u56fd\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7f8e", "id": "1422263420594", "back": "\u7f8e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3c3cf899-4c7a-4f65-8d1c-33abadb76728/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7f8e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7f8e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u0129 (beautiful, America)"}, {"front": "m\u0129 (beautiful, America)", "id": "1422263420595", "back": "m\u0129 (beautiful, America)  <hr id=answer>  \u7f8e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3c3cf899-4c7a-4f65-8d1c-33abadb76728/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7f8e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7f8e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7c73", "id": "1422409758312", "back": "\u7c73 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/21cb5360-8d54-4add-afe5-cbf00ae09da3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7c73\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7c73\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ec5 (rice, meter, US)"}, {"front": "m\u1ec5 (rice, meter, US)", "id": "1422409758313", "back": "m\u1ec5 (rice, meter, US)  <hr id=answer>  \u7c73 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/21cb5360-8d54-4add-afe5-cbf00ae09da3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7c73\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7c73\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8863", "id": "1422410046337", "back": "\u8863 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7261c684-2354-4ba0-b8da-cda5abd3459a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8863\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8863\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  y (clothes, covering)<div><br /></div><div>\u8864</div>"}, {"front": "y (clothes, covering)<div><br /></div><div>\u8864</div>", "id": "1422410046338", "back": "y (clothes, covering)<div><br /></div><div>\u8864</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8863 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7261c684-2354-4ba0-b8da-cda5abd3459a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8863\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8863\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c0f", "id": "1422410327269", "back": "\u5c0f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/93e04840-d109-4a6d-af63-6a7ea6ca7c6f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c0f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c0f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u1ec3u (little, slight)"}, {"front": "ti\u1ec3u (little, slight)", "id": "1422410327270", "back": "ti\u1ec3u (little, slight)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c0f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/93e04840-d109-4a6d-af63-6a7ea6ca7c6f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c0f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c0f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u624b", "id": "1422410578278", "back": "\u624b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6488b2bc-14c6-4f7a-ac35-2e41ae3a4da2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u624b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u624b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ee7 (hand)"}, {"front": "th\u1ee7 (hand)", "id": "1422410578279", "back": "th\u1ee7 (hand)  <hr id=answer>  \u624b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6488b2bc-14c6-4f7a-ac35-2e41ae3a4da2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u624b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u624b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u866b", "id": "1422433289985", "back": "\u866b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/73fe8093-960d-4471-bd5b-916140c4de1b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u866b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u866b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u00f9ng (insect, worm)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u87f2</div>"}, {"front": "tr\u00f9ng (insect, worm)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u87f2</div>", "id": "1422433289986", "back": "tr\u00f9ng (insect, worm)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u87f2</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u866b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/73fe8093-960d-4471-bd5b-916140c4de1b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u866b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u866b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7592", "id": "1422433547548", "back": "\u7592 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d30293a3-7d83-4a1f-9767-1906b64ceff4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7592\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7592\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  n\u1ea1ch (sickness)"}, {"front": "n\u1ea1ch (sickness)", "id": "1422433547549", "back": "n\u1ea1ch (sickness)  <hr id=answer>  \u7592 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d30293a3-7d83-4a1f-9767-1906b64ceff4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7592\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7592\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7af9 \u2eae", "id": "1422433696015", "back": "\u7af9 \u2eae <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/723e2c99-aa8f-4b5a-80a8-ec557effa6f8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7af9 \u2eae\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7af9 \u2eae\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u00fac (bamboo)"}, {"front": "tr\u00fac (bamboo)", "id": "1422433696016", "back": "tr\u00fac (bamboo)  <hr id=answer>  \u7af9 \u2eae <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/723e2c99-aa8f-4b5a-80a8-ec557effa6f8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7af9 \u2eae\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7af9 \u2eae\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9875", "id": "1422433999784", "back": "\u9875 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/978b520c-d0dd-4879-b0b4-49a84fbd7f90/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9875\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9875\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  hi\u1ec7t (page)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9801</div>"}, {"front": "hi\u1ec7t (page)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9801</div>", "id": "1422433999785", "back": "hi\u1ec7t (page)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9801</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u9875 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/978b520c-d0dd-4879-b0b4-49a84fbd7f90/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9875\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9875\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7f51", "id": "1422437763844", "back": "\u7f51 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b47079d4-7562-462e-8f55-be5409b03f7b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7f51\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7f51\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u00f5ng (net)<div>\u7f52&nbsp;\u7db2</div>"}, {"front": "v\u00f5ng (net)<div>\u7f52&nbsp;\u7db2</div>", "id": "1422437763845", "back": "v\u00f5ng (net)<div>\u7f52&nbsp;\u7db2</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u7f51 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b47079d4-7562-462e-8f55-be5409b03f7b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7f51\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7f51\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u725b", "id": "1422437969276", "back": "\u725b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e181bf1b-fb4e-4c5c-a5be-6aef35eadd86/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u725b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u725b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u01b0u (cow)<div>radical:&nbsp;\u725c</div>"}, {"front": "ng\u01b0u (cow)<div>radical:&nbsp;\u725c</div>", "id": "1422437969277", "back": "ng\u01b0u (cow)<div>radical:&nbsp;\u725c</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u725b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e181bf1b-fb4e-4c5c-a5be-6aef35eadd86/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u725b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u725b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c71", "id": "1422438177796", "back": "\u5c71 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2dbb98e4-7885-45d1-900b-efcf0159511f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c71\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c71\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  san, s\u01a1n"}, {"front": "san, s\u01a1n", "id": "1422438177797", "back": "san, s\u01a1n  <hr id=answer>  \u5c71 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2dbb98e4-7885-45d1-900b-efcf0159511f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c71\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c71\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u706b", "id": "1422438318141", "back": "\u706b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/06de0e71-2c95-4ebd-b25e-b5a942cec7a2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u706b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u706b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ecfa (fire, urgent)"}, {"front": "h\u1ecfa (fire, urgent)", "id": "1422438318142", "back": "h\u1ecfa (fire, urgent)  <hr id=answer>  \u706b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/06de0e71-2c95-4ebd-b25e-b5a942cec7a2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u706b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u706b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5382", "id": "1422438499715", "back": "\u5382 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/62d9a2a4-e091-4134-9673-fad20de5ea7f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5382\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5382\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u01b0\u1edfng (factory),&nbsp;h\u00e1n (cliff)<div>&nbsp;\u5ee0</div>"}, {"front": "x\u01b0\u1edfng (factory),&nbsp;h\u00e1n (cliff)<div>&nbsp;\u5ee0</div>", "id": "1422438499716", "back": "x\u01b0\u1edfng (factory),&nbsp;h\u00e1n (cliff)<div>&nbsp;\u5ee0</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5382 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/62d9a2a4-e091-4134-9673-fad20de5ea7f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5382\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5382\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u820c", "id": "1422438658255", "back": "\u820c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b5a2432f-6bad-4ff6-9dea-080c92798a28/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u820c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u820c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thi\u1ec7t (tongue)"}, {"front": "thi\u1ec7t (tongue)", "id": "1422438658256", "back": "thi\u1ec7t (tongue)  <hr id=answer>  \u820c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b5a2432f-6bad-4ff6-9dea-080c92798a28/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u820c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u820c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6bcd", "id": "1422439038943", "back": "\u6bcd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8ebdfa30-4990-4208-afae-e56bdf559bb1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bcd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bcd\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1eabu (mother, female)"}, {"front": "m\u1eabu (mother, female)", "id": "1422439038944", "back": "m\u1eabu (mother, female)  <hr id=answer>  \u6bcd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8ebdfa30-4990-4208-afae-e56bdf559bb1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bcd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bcd\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e4b", "id": "1422439398838", "back": "\u4e4b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f197faab-4470-4ec3-9964-8682014e0ded/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e4b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e4b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  chi ('s, go to, it/them)"}, {"front": "chi ('s, go to, it/them)", "id": "1422439398839", "back": "chi ('s, go to, it/them)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e4b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f197faab-4470-4ec3-9964-8682014e0ded/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e4b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e4b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u529f", "id": "1422439798306", "back": "\u529f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4a996d08-6f52-4010-8296-00c4d3057910/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u529f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u529f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00f4ng (achievement, result)"}, {"front": "c\u00f4ng (achievement, result)", "id": "1422439798307", "back": "c\u00f4ng (achievement, result)  <hr id=answer>  \u529f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4a996d08-6f52-4010-8296-00c4d3057910/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u529f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u529f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6210", "id": "1422439906376", "back": "\u6210 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/22056c2d-48be-4afb-98ad-4872faa1396c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6210\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6210\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00e0nh (complete, 1/10, become)"}, {"front": "th\u00e0nh (complete, 1/10, become)", "id": "1422439906377", "back": "th\u00e0nh (complete, 1/10, become)  <hr id=answer>  \u6210 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/22056c2d-48be-4afb-98ad-4872faa1396c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6210\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6210\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8d25", "id": "1422440133276", "back": "\u8d25 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d3564e03-86b9-4f2f-9b8b-784bcab0f49b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d25\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d25\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ea1i (defeated, fail, decay)"}, {"front": "b\u1ea1i (defeated, fail, decay)", "id": "1422440133277", "back": "b\u1ea1i (defeated, fail, decay)  <hr id=answer>  \u8d25 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d3564e03-86b9-4f2f-9b8b-784bcab0f49b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d25\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d25\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5931", "id": "1422440280848", "back": "\u5931 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3a66f736-52a7-4471-a4cf-71379b6a975a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5931\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5931\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ea5t (lose, miss, mistake)"}, {"front": "th\u1ea5t (lose, miss, mistake)", "id": "1422440280849", "back": "th\u1ea5t (lose, miss, mistake)  <hr id=answer>  \u5931 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3a66f736-52a7-4471-a4cf-71379b6a975a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5931\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5931\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6c11", "id": "1422440390317", "back": "\u6c11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/95ddfbc3-4c0e-4365-be16-14c168b0f6a5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c11\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u00e2n (people, public)"}, {"front": "d\u00e2n (people, public)", "id": "1422440390318", "back": "d\u00e2n (people, public)  <hr id=answer>  \u6c11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/95ddfbc3-4c0e-4365-be16-14c168b0f6a5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c11\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6628", "id": "1422584886587", "back": "\u6628 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a97fef89-b3f1-40fa-abc6-47d6139b6f07/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6628\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6628\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ea1c (last, past)"}, {"front": "t\u1ea1c (last, past)", "id": "1422584886588", "back": "t\u1ea1c (last, past)  <hr id=answer>  \u6628 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a97fef89-b3f1-40fa-abc6-47d6139b6f07/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6628\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6628\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u661f", "id": "1422607652666", "back": "\u661f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/437b3e8e-475b-4e6f-b395-ad97fb7edb1c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u661f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u661f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tinh (star, tiny particle)"}, {"front": "tinh (star, tiny particle)", "id": "1422607652667", "back": "tinh (star, tiny particle)  <hr id=answer>  \u661f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/437b3e8e-475b-4e6f-b395-ad97fb7edb1c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u661f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u661f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u671f", "id": "1422607986750", "back": "\u671f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bc8557cb-4fad-4452-aa17-9282ebcaf0a4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u671f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u671f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  k\u00ec (period, expect)"}, {"front": "k\u00ec (period, expect)", "id": "1422607986751", "back": "k\u00ec (period, expect)  <hr id=answer>  \u671f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bc8557cb-4fad-4452-aa17-9282ebcaf0a4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u671f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u671f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5176", "id": "1422608433177", "back": "\u5176 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2d6eecb4-7470-4d9c-a425-c38717d567d3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5176\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5176\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  k\u00ec (they/their,&nbsp;interrogative used to introduce a question)"}, {"front": "k\u00ec (they/their,&nbsp;interrogative used to introduce a question)", "id": "1422608433178", "back": "k\u00ec (they/their,&nbsp;interrogative used to introduce a question)  <hr id=answer>  \u5176 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2d6eecb4-7470-4d9c-a425-c38717d567d3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5176\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5176\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u56de", "id": "1422609282816", "back": "\u56de <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5551c95e-2535-421c-89e6-10e894a493c2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u56de\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u56de\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ed3i (return, Islam/Hui people; a time/occurrence/chapter)"}, {"front": "h\u1ed3i (return, Islam/Hui people; a time/occurrence/chapter)", "id": "1422609282817", "back": "h\u1ed3i (return, Islam/Hui people; a time/occurrence/chapter)  <hr id=answer>  \u56de <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5551c95e-2535-421c-89e6-10e894a493c2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u56de\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u56de\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6821", "id": "1422609714842", "back": "\u6821 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/794bdddb-2105-4e02-ac5b-1a2c77c8ac35/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6821\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6821\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u00e1o (proofread, revise), hi\u1ec7u (school, officer grade)"}, {"front": "gi\u00e1o (proofread, revise), hi\u1ec7u (school, officer grade)", "id": "1422609714843", "back": "gi\u00e1o (proofread, revise), hi\u1ec7u (school, officer grade)  <hr id=answer>  \u6821 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/794bdddb-2105-4e02-ac5b-1a2c77c8ac35/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6821\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6821\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u516c", "id": "1422609990133", "back": "\u516c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/de1b5aba-e443-4fa1-9913-430871ad9fed/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u516c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u516c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00f4ng (fair, public, duke rank in China's five-grades of the nobility, male animals)"}, {"front": "c\u00f4ng (fair, public, duke rank in China's five-grades of the nobility, male animals)", "id": "1422609990134", "back": "c\u00f4ng (fair, public, duke rank in China's five-grades of the nobility, male animals)  <hr id=answer>  \u516c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/de1b5aba-e443-4fa1-9913-430871ad9fed/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u516c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u516c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u56ed", "id": "1422610468518", "back": "\u56ed <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cccf0399-3c04-450a-ad28-d6dde51a2a65/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u56ed\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u56ed\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  vi\u00ean (park/garden)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5712</div>"}, {"front": "vi\u00ean (park/garden)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5712</div>", "id": "1422610468519", "back": "vi\u00ean (park/garden)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5712</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u56ed <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cccf0399-3c04-450a-ad28-d6dde51a2a65/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u56ed\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u56ed\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5143", "id": "1422952616845", "back": "\u5143 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3771694a-d497-4462-9bf0-cc2cf08d6c5b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5143\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5143\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nguy\u00ean (head, prime, first)"}, {"front": "nguy\u00ean (head, prime, first)", "id": "1422952616847", "back": "nguy\u00ean (head, prime, first)  <hr id=answer>  \u5143 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3771694a-d497-4462-9bf0-cc2cf08d6c5b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5143\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5143\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5b89", "id": "1422952836451", "back": "\u5b89 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/59d5be4e-3b8d-4659-888d-ecb66d0bd0e7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b89\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b89\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  an, y\u00ean (peace, safe)"}, {"front": "an, y\u00ean (peace, safe)", "id": "1422952836453", "back": "an, y\u00ean (peace, safe)  <hr id=answer>  \u5b89 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/59d5be4e-3b8d-4659-888d-ecb66d0bd0e7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b89\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b89\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u620a", "id": "1422952979897", "back": "\u620a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e6faafb0-82dc-46ae-ba5e-afcccde98ccc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u620a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u620a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1eadu (fifth Celestial Stem)"}, {"front": "m\u1eadu (fifth Celestial Stem)", "id": "1422952979898", "back": "m\u1eadu (fifth Celestial Stem)  <hr id=answer>  \u620a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e6faafb0-82dc-46ae-ba5e-afcccde98ccc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u620a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u620a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e4d", "id": "1422953129519", "back": "\u4e4d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5fad8ded-46fa-4900-a18d-8efd790f6513/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e4d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e4d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u1ea1, t\u00e1c (suddenly, for the first time)"}, {"front": "s\u1ea1, t\u00e1c (suddenly, for the first time)", "id": "1422953129520", "back": "s\u1ea1, t\u00e1c (suddenly, for the first time)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e4d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5fad8ded-46fa-4900-a18d-8efd790f6513/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e4d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e4d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ea4", "id": "1422953378893", "back": "\u4ea4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/57cf9d12-0fe1-4475-a5db-f9c25e64bcd9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ea4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ea4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  giao (exchange, inter-, deliver)"}, {"front": "giao (exchange, inter-, deliver)", "id": "1422953378894", "back": "giao (exchange, inter-, deliver)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ea4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/57cf9d12-0fe1-4475-a5db-f9c25e64bcd9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ea4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ea4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65f6", "id": "1422953617882", "back": "\u65f6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f67041cd-00d7-4462-9977-b458cbce61ce/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65f6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65f6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00ec, th\u1eddi (time, period)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;(\u6642)</div>"}, {"front": "th\u00ec, th\u1eddi (time, period)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;(\u6642)</div>", "id": "1422953617883", "back": "th\u00ec, th\u1eddi (time, period)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;(\u6642)</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u65f6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f67041cd-00d7-4462-9977-b458cbce61ce/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65f6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65f6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u95f4", "id": "1422953868766", "back": "\u95f4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cb4be8ab-1543-4bd1-b492-5cea464831cb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u95f4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u95f4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gian, gi\u00e1n (interval/space between, divide/division)<div>&nbsp;\u9593</div>"}, {"front": "gian, gi\u00e1n (interval/space between, divide/division)<div>&nbsp;\u9593</div>", "id": "1422953868767", "back": "gian, gi\u00e1n (interval/space between, divide/division)<div>&nbsp;\u9593</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u95f4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cb4be8ab-1543-4bd1-b492-5cea464831cb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u95f4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u95f4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e8b", "id": "1422954109979", "back": "\u4e8b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a8f1dcb4-1c0b-4111-987a-2729b1eea957/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e8b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e8b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u1ef1 (business/affair, job/duty)"}, {"front": "s\u1ef1 (business/affair, job/duty)", "id": "1422954109980", "back": "s\u1ef1 (business/affair, job/duty)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e8b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a8f1dcb4-1c0b-4111-987a-2729b1eea957/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e8b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e8b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u80fd", "id": "1422954404636", "back": "\u80fd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1760c320-4868-4029-84d5-2a1b3ba19859/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u80fd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u80fd\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  n\u0103ng (able, potential, energy)"}, {"front": "n\u0103ng (able, potential, energy)", "id": "1422954404637", "back": "n\u0103ng (able, potential, energy)  <hr id=answer>  \u80fd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1760c320-4868-4029-84d5-2a1b3ba19859/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u80fd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u80fd\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ee5", "id": "1422954748018", "back": "\u4ee5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/24156687-de45-4f4d-8e98-74b9924294db/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ee5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ee5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u0129 (use, by means of, because)"}, {"front": "d\u0129 (use, by means of, because)", "id": "1422954748019", "back": "d\u0129 (use, by means of, because)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ee5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/24156687-de45-4f4d-8e98-74b9924294db/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ee5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ee5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u73b0", "id": "1422954913837", "back": "\u73b0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/44c8e487-04f2-415b-a42a-75aa0389f405/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u73b0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u73b0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  hi\u1ec7n (appear, present/now, ready/available)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u73fe</div>"}, {"front": "hi\u1ec7n (appear, present/now, ready/available)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u73fe</div>", "id": "1422954913838", "back": "hi\u1ec7n (appear, present/now, ready/available)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u73fe</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u73b0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/44c8e487-04f2-415b-a42a-75aa0389f405/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u73b0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u73b0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5728", "id": "1422955268376", "back": "\u5728 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/350dd139-6f43-4a30-8cec-1e5c0c2a495e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5728\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5728\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ea1i (at, during, doing/in progress)"}, {"front": "t\u1ea1i (at, during, doing/in progress)", "id": "1422955268377", "back": "t\u1ea1i (at, during, doing/in progress)  <hr id=answer>  \u5728 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/350dd139-6f43-4a30-8cec-1e5c0c2a495e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5728\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5728\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e2e", "id": "1422955443795", "back": "\u5e2e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/af441598-5c02-4588-b01b-7fef9e88fdc6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e2e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e2e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  bang (help/assist, gang/group, sides of shoe/boat)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5e6b</div>"}, {"front": "bang (help/assist, gang/group, sides of shoe/boat)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5e6b</div>", "id": "1422955443796", "back": "bang (help/assist, gang/group, sides of shoe/boat)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5e6b</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5e2e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/af441598-5c02-4588-b01b-7fef9e88fdc6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e2e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e2e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5ba2", "id": "1423002211236", "back": "\u5ba2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/70951ac8-92d8-4828-836f-a77fffa10139/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5ba2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5ba2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u00e1ch (guest, customer)"}, {"front": "kh\u00e1ch (guest, customer)", "id": "1423002211238", "back": "kh\u00e1ch (guest, customer)  <hr id=answer>  \u5ba2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/70951ac8-92d8-4828-836f-a77fffa10139/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5ba2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5ba2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6c14", "id": "1423002615380", "back": "\u6c14 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4eafe3b0-ffbd-4832-8901-3891e9cd0398/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c14\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c14\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u00ed (air/gas, breath, spirit/life force, angry)&nbsp;<div>&nbsp;\u6c23</div>"}, {"front": "kh\u00ed (air/gas, breath, spirit/life force, angry)&nbsp;<div>&nbsp;\u6c23</div>", "id": "1423002615381", "back": "kh\u00ed (air/gas, breath, spirit/life force, angry)&nbsp;<div>&nbsp;\u6c23</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u6c14 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4eafe3b0-ffbd-4832-8901-3891e9cd0398/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c14\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c14\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u52b3", "id": "1423002895467", "back": "\u52b3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/11bc0c61-56aa-47bb-8b8f-03d346a16893/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52b3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52b3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  lao, l\u1ea1o (labor, bother/worry)"}, {"front": "lao, l\u1ea1o (labor, bother/worry)", "id": "1423002895468", "back": "lao, l\u1ea1o (labor, bother/worry)  <hr id=answer>  \u52b3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/11bc0c61-56aa-47bb-8b8f-03d346a16893/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52b3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52b3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9a7e", "id": "1423003174265", "back": "\u9a7e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/51c79e4e-3b9b-4cb2-9f12-6558396d3436/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9a7e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9a7e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u00e1 (drive/pilot, carriage, emperor/respectful term for someone)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u99d5</div>"}, {"front": "gi\u00e1 (drive/pilot, carriage, emperor/respectful term for someone)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u99d5</div>", "id": "1423003174266", "back": "gi\u00e1 (drive/pilot, carriage, emperor/respectful term for someone)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u99d5</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u9a7e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/51c79e4e-3b9b-4cb2-9f12-6558396d3436/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9a7e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9a7e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5173", "id": "1423003587088", "back": "\u5173 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d77fcb0a-80c5-4df4-8ae6-7f3ccdf18160/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5173\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5173\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  quan (frontier pass/customs/key point, shut/close, involve/concern)<div>&nbsp;\u95dc</div>"}, {"front": "quan (frontier pass/customs/key point, shut/close, involve/concern)<div>&nbsp;\u95dc</div>", "id": "1423003587089", "back": "quan (frontier pass/customs/key point, shut/close, involve/concern)<div>&nbsp;\u95dc</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5173 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d77fcb0a-80c5-4df4-8ae6-7f3ccdf18160/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5173\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5173\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7cfb", "id": "1423003884470", "back": "\u7cfb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f58b63de-5ea2-40f5-80d5-37d9cfdc0d19/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7cfb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7cfb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ec7 (system, relate)"}, {"front": "h\u1ec7 (system, relate)", "id": "1423003884471", "back": "h\u1ec7 (system, relate)  <hr id=answer>  \u7cfb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f58b63de-5ea2-40f5-80d5-37d9cfdc0d19/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7cfb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7cfb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bf4", "id": "1423004047604", "back": "\u8bf4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9791f59e-9c32-489e-9a82-8aa0785276e5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bf4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bf4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thuy\u1ebft (speak, tell, theory)"}, {"front": "thuy\u1ebft (speak, tell, theory)", "id": "1423004047605", "back": "thuy\u1ebft (speak, tell, theory)  <hr id=answer>  \u8bf4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9791f59e-9c32-489e-9a82-8aa0785276e5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bf4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bf4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5bc4", "id": "1423004353997", "back": "\u5bc4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7c0d6f22-ab26-4a56-8763-f8dc66c9323a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bc4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bc4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  k\u00ed (send/transmit, entrust/rely, foster parent/child)"}, {"front": "k\u00ed (send/transmit, entrust/rely, foster parent/child)", "id": "1423004353998", "back": "k\u00ed (send/transmit, entrust/rely, foster parent/child)  <hr id=answer>  \u5bc4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7c0d6f22-ab26-4a56-8763-f8dc66c9323a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bc4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bc4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c01", "id": "1423005811679", "back": "\u5c01 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/62618d55-08a7-4d8e-bbe1-5a80fbb1d414/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c01\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c01\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  phong (grant title, seal/cover, envelope/numerary adjunct)"}, {"front": "phong (grant title, seal/cover, envelope/numerary adjunct)", "id": "1423005811680", "back": "phong (grant title, seal/cover, envelope/numerary adjunct)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c01 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/62618d55-08a7-4d8e-bbe1-5a80fbb1d414/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c01\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c01\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8981", "id": "1423006102370", "back": "\u8981 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/52336f1d-6832-4195-9877-4a9dc25ad905/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8981\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8981\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  y\u1ebfu (important/necessary, want/request, must)"}, {"front": "y\u1ebfu (important/necessary, want/request, must)", "id": "1423006102371", "back": "y\u1ebfu (important/necessary, want/request, must)  <hr id=answer>  \u8981 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/52336f1d-6832-4195-9877-4a9dc25ad905/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8981\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8981\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4fee", "id": "1423006198109", "back": "\u4fee <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/14d27856-e67e-4528-86bd-9ae5d8742a60/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4fee\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4fee\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tu (study, repair, cultivate)"}, {"front": "tu (study, repair, cultivate)", "id": "1423006198110", "back": "tu (study, repair, cultivate)  <hr id=answer>  \u4fee <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/14d27856-e67e-4528-86bd-9ae5d8742a60/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4fee\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4fee\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u81ea", "id": "1423006366683", "back": "\u81ea <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dfc1f02b-f6ff-4a50-85c0-19a0e5a83760/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u81ea\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u81ea\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ef1 (self/personally, certainly, from)"}, {"front": "t\u1ef1 (self/personally, certainly, from)", "id": "1423006366684", "back": "t\u1ef1 (self/personally, certainly, from)  <hr id=answer>  \u81ea <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dfc1f02b-f6ff-4a50-85c0-19a0e5a83760/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u81ea\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u81ea\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f1a", "id": "1423007411271", "back": "\u4f1a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/83fa1306-468e-40df-9ec5-ef7fb7a77688/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f1a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f1a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ed9i (meeting, society, understand/able to)<div>&nbsp;\u6703</div>"}, {"front": "h\u1ed9i (meeting, society, understand/able to)<div>&nbsp;\u6703</div>", "id": "1423007411272", "back": "h\u1ed9i (meeting, society, understand/able to)<div>&nbsp;\u6703</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4f1a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/83fa1306-468e-40df-9ec5-ef7fb7a77688/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f1a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f1a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53ea", "id": "1423007596128", "back": "\u53ea <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c65c847c-f3c7-44e7-9fbb-a0ab677c9c45/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53ea\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53ea\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u1ec9 (only, just, simply)&nbsp;ch\u00edch (odd, lone, numerary adjunct)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u96bb</div>"}, {"front": "ch\u1ec9 (only, just, simply)&nbsp;ch\u00edch (odd, lone, numerary adjunct)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u96bb</div>", "id": "1423007596129", "back": "ch\u1ec9 (only, just, simply)&nbsp;ch\u00edch (odd, lone, numerary adjunct)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u96bb</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u53ea <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c65c847c-f3c7-44e7-9fbb-a0ab677c9c45/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53ea\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53ea\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u90a6", "id": "1423007691434", "back": "\u90a6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/daaa3b8d-e4c4-4967-8543-7fcfce2a5049/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u90a6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u90a6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  bang (state, nation)"}, {"front": "bang (state, nation)", "id": "1423007691435", "back": "bang (state, nation)  <hr id=answer>  \u90a6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/daaa3b8d-e4c4-4967-8543-7fcfce2a5049/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u90a6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u90a6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u624d", "id": "1423007940221", "back": "\u624d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/09825c2d-7993-450c-a7be-8375bb6fe640/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u624d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u624d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00e0i (talent/ability, just/only/merely)"}, {"front": "t\u00e0i (talent/ability, just/only/merely)", "id": "1423007940222", "back": "t\u00e0i (talent/ability, just/only/merely)  <hr id=answer>  \u624d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/09825c2d-7993-450c-a7be-8375bb6fe640/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u624d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u624d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7389", "id": "1423008194764", "back": "\u7389 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5f979410-9839-4342-a127-ba23d3f33b5f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7389\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7389\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u1ecdc, t\u00fac (jade, pure/fair/feminine)"}, {"front": "ng\u1ecdc, t\u00fac (jade, pure/fair/feminine)", "id": "1423008194765", "back": "ng\u1ecdc, t\u00fac (jade, pure/fair/feminine)  <hr id=answer>  \u7389 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5f979410-9839-4342-a127-ba23d3f33b5f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7389\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7389\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5bb4", "id": "1423008320038", "back": "\u5bb4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6632b5ed-9450-4c49-9863-49e6f8c4479e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bb4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bb4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  y\u1ebfn (banquet, entertain, leisure)"}, {"front": "y\u1ebfn (banquet, entertain, leisure)", "id": "1423008320039", "back": "y\u1ebfn (banquet, entertain, leisure)  <hr id=answer>  \u5bb4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6632b5ed-9450-4c49-9863-49e6f8c4479e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bb4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bb4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5404", "id": "1423008433384", "back": "\u5404 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ae7cb812-9585-47cc-b7ca-8353c8d0d408/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5404\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5404\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00e1c (every, each, all)"}, {"front": "c\u00e1c (every, each, all)", "id": "1423008433385", "back": "c\u00e1c (every, each, all)  <hr id=answer>  \u5404 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ae7cb812-9585-47cc-b7ca-8353c8d0d408/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5404\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5404\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u52a0", "id": "1423008608042", "back": "\u52a0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ea9e667c-c890-402c-a0fa-690be89e2b36/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52a0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52a0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gia (add, increase)"}, {"front": "gia (add, increase)", "id": "1423008608043", "back": "gia (add, increase)  <hr id=answer>  \u52a0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ea9e667c-c890-402c-a0fa-690be89e2b36/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52a0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52a0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5947", "id": "1423008852353", "back": "\u5947 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/eccd8fc5-9f01-4a92-a09f-859bd049df05/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5947\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5947\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  k\u00ec (strange, unusual)"}, {"front": "k\u00ec (strange, unusual)", "id": "1423008852354", "back": "k\u00ec (strange, unusual)  <hr id=answer>  \u5947 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/eccd8fc5-9f01-4a92-a09f-859bd049df05/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5947\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5947\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u738b", "id": "1423009021663", "back": "\u738b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8e7c32b2-4377-4ac9-b2bd-6c610b72a075/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u738b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u738b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u01b0\u01a1ng (king)"}, {"front": "v\u01b0\u01a1ng (king)", "id": "1423009021664", "back": "v\u01b0\u01a1ng (king)  <hr id=answer>  \u738b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8e7c32b2-4377-4ac9-b2bd-6c610b72a075/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u738b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u738b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6538", "id": "1423297753884", "back": "\u6538 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/df470bd6-6b61-4630-8c84-05f71efe4495/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6538\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6538\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  du (far, Nguyen Du)"}, {"front": "du (far, Nguyen Du)", "id": "1423297753885", "back": "du (far, Nguyen Du)  <hr id=answer>  \u6538 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/df470bd6-6b61-4630-8c84-05f71efe4495/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6538\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6538\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e30", "id": "1423297985232", "back": "\u4e30 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5337d02d-c115-40f7-8779-c2443842b3ec/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e30\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e30\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  phong (beautiful/beauty, abundant/plenty)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8c50</div>"}, {"front": "phong (beautiful/beauty, abundant/plenty)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8c50</div>", "id": "1423297985233", "back": "phong (beautiful/beauty, abundant/plenty)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8c50</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e30 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5337d02d-c115-40f7-8779-c2443842b3ec/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e30\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e30\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5151", "id": "1423298472948", "back": "\u5151 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cb1e3e06-e1b7-4a68-86c2-aca49a10f38d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5151\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5151\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111o\u00e1i, \u0111o\u00e0i (cash, exchange,&nbsp;second of the eight trigrams/west)&nbsp;"}, {"front": "\u0111o\u00e1i, \u0111o\u00e0i (cash, exchange,&nbsp;second of the eight trigrams/west)&nbsp;", "id": "1423298472949", "back": "\u0111o\u00e1i, \u0111o\u00e0i (cash, exchange,&nbsp;second of the eight trigrams/west)&nbsp;  <hr id=answer>  \u5151 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cb1e3e06-e1b7-4a68-86c2-aca49a10f38d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5151\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5151\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7535", "id": "1423298897443", "back": "\u7535 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a0cf1d5f-09f4-4764-8764-d3b86a5c122a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7535\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7535\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111i\u1ec7n (electricity, lightning)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u96fb</div>"}, {"front": "\u0111i\u1ec7n (electricity, lightning)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u96fb</div>", "id": "1423298897444", "back": "\u0111i\u1ec7n (electricity, lightning)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u96fb</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u7535 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a0cf1d5f-09f4-4764-8764-d3b86a5c122a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7535\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7535\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bdd", "id": "1423299117623", "back": "\u8bdd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b4061be2-4a97-4b58-91fe-055edc7fcee5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bdd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bdd\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tho\u1ea1i (speech/talk, conversation/sayings, language/dialect)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8a71</div>"}, {"front": "tho\u1ea1i (speech/talk, conversation/sayings, language/dialect)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8a71</div>", "id": "1423299117624", "back": "tho\u1ea1i (speech/talk, conversation/sayings, language/dialect)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8a71</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8bdd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b4061be2-4a97-4b58-91fe-055edc7fcee5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bdd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bdd\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u522b&nbsp;&nbsp;\u5225", "id": "1423299490493", "back": "\u522b&nbsp;&nbsp;\u5225 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4fbf7135-98b9-4a5d-87e5-a0ce36eb374a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u522b&nbsp;&nbsp;\u5225\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u522b&nbsp;&nbsp;\u5225\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  bi\u1ec7t (separate/part, don't, another, difference/distinguish)"}, {"front": "bi\u1ec7t (separate/part, don't, another, difference/distinguish)", "id": "1423299490494", "back": "bi\u1ec7t (separate/part, don't, another, difference/distinguish)  <hr id=answer>  \u522b&nbsp;&nbsp;\u5225 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4fbf7135-98b9-4a5d-87e5-a0ce36eb374a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u522b&nbsp;&nbsp;\u5225\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u522b&nbsp;&nbsp;\u5225\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u63a5", "id": "1423299710489", "back": "\u63a5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9c288057-63e9-41e2-b83d-5242c61cd800/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u63a5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u63a5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u1ebfp (receive, continue/succeed, contact/connect)"}, {"front": "ti\u1ebfp (receive, continue/succeed, contact/connect)", "id": "1423299710490", "back": "ti\u1ebfp (receive, continue/succeed, contact/connect)  <hr id=answer>  \u63a5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9c288057-63e9-41e2-b83d-5242c61cd800/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u63a5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u63a5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6b65", "id": "1423300141278", "back": "\u6b65 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cad24cbf-5c47-4917-9983-bc4297a92f21/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b65\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b65\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ed9 (walk/on foot, situation/state/fortune)"}, {"front": "b\u1ed9 (walk/on foot, situation/state/fortune)", "id": "1423300141279", "back": "b\u1ed9 (walk/on foot, situation/state/fortune)  <hr id=answer>  \u6b65 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cad24cbf-5c47-4917-9983-bc4297a92f21/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b65\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b65\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6563", "id": "1423300370748", "back": "\u6563 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ae63cf90-50cc-457b-a1e8-a66125c888cf/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6563\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6563\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00e1n, t\u1ea3n (scatter/disperse, free/leisure)"}, {"front": "t\u00e1n, t\u1ea3n (scatter/disperse, free/leisure)", "id": "1423300370749", "back": "t\u00e1n, t\u1ea3n (scatter/disperse, free/leisure)  <hr id=answer>  \u6563 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ae63cf90-50cc-457b-a1e8-a66125c888cf/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6563\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6563\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6e38", "id": "1423300761295", "back": "\u6e38 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ccbeb168-8cf3-46e3-b721-b925d78aca94/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6e38\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6e38\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  du (swim, float/drift/wander, river part)&nbsp;"}, {"front": "du (swim, float/drift/wander, river part)&nbsp;", "id": "1423300761296", "back": "du (swim, float/drift/wander, river part)&nbsp;  <hr id=answer>  \u6e38 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ccbeb168-8cf3-46e3-b721-b925d78aca94/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6e38\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6e38\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6cf3", "id": "1423300861440", "back": "\u6cf3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/46a9e30a-ab4f-4ca7-a674-44a96b49c04c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6cf3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6cf3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u1ecbnh (swim/dive)"}, {"front": "v\u1ecbnh (swim/dive)", "id": "1423300861441", "back": "v\u1ecbnh (swim/dive)  <hr id=answer>  \u6cf3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/46a9e30a-ab4f-4ca7-a674-44a96b49c04c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6cf3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6cf3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7761", "id": "1423301251742", "back": "\u7761 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3107ece4-a2e3-4b1f-88ac-f8810e7fe20e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7761\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7761\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ee5y (sleep, doze)"}, {"front": "th\u1ee5y (sleep, doze)", "id": "1423301251743", "back": "th\u1ee5y (sleep, doze)  <hr id=answer>  \u7761 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3107ece4-a2e3-4b1f-88ac-f8810e7fe20e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7761\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7761\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5782", "id": "1423301454921", "back": "\u5782 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d510256c-2954-4143-a110-fd4349c90d49/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5782\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5782\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00f9y (suspend/hang down, pass to next generation, almost/nearly, condescend)"}, {"front": "th\u00f9y (suspend/hang down, pass to next generation, almost/nearly, condescend)", "id": "1423301454922", "back": "th\u00f9y (suspend/hang down, pass to next generation, almost/nearly, condescend)  <hr id=answer>  \u5782 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d510256c-2954-4143-a110-fd4349c90d49/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5782\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5782\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u89c9", "id": "1423301711514", "back": "\u89c9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/793b6073-851c-4d47-a51e-c860d8014489/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u89c9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u89c9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u00e1c (wake up, realize, sense), gi\u00e1o (sleep/nap)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u89ba</div>"}, {"front": "gi\u00e1c (wake up, realize, sense), gi\u00e1o (sleep/nap)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u89ba</div>", "id": "1423301711515", "back": "gi\u00e1c (wake up, realize, sense), gi\u00e1o (sleep/nap)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u89ba</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u89c9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/793b6073-851c-4d47-a51e-c860d8014489/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u89c9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u89c9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5916", "id": "1423302074509", "back": "\u5916 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5f512f2c-773c-42f1-b10b-13c3e972aff6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5916\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5916\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ngo\u1ea1i (outside, foreign/alien/unofficial, alienate)"}, {"front": "ngo\u1ea1i (outside, foreign/alien/unofficial, alienate)", "id": "1423302074510", "back": "ngo\u1ea1i (outside, foreign/alien/unofficial, alienate)  <hr id=answer>  \u5916 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5f512f2c-773c-42f1-b10b-13c3e972aff6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5916\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5916\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8fb9", "id": "1423302419634", "back": "\u8fb9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/936b524c-a7cc-4360-ba2b-1aa45e05e6a4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fb9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fb9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  bi\u00ean (edge/border, limit)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u908a</div>"}, {"front": "bi\u00ean (edge/border, limit)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u908a</div>", "id": "1423302419635", "back": "bi\u00ean (edge/border, limit)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u908a</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8fb9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/936b524c-a7cc-4360-ba2b-1aa45e05e6a4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fb9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fb9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u59be", "id": "1423745240952", "back": "\u59be <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/566b9d9b-6908-4427-a31a-123837a54e55/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u59be\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u59be\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thi\u1ebfp (concubine)"}, {"front": "thi\u1ebfp (concubine)", "id": "1423745240953", "back": "thi\u1ebfp (concubine)  <hr id=answer>  \u59be <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/566b9d9b-6908-4427-a31a-123837a54e55/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u59be\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u59be\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e16", "id": "1423745679441", "back": "\u4e16 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a158fffb-c057-42f7-ac38-d51526e4da8d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e16\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e16\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ebf (world, generation, era)"}, {"front": "th\u1ebf (world, generation, era)", "id": "1423745679442", "back": "th\u1ebf (world, generation, era)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e16 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a158fffb-c057-42f7-ac38-d51526e4da8d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e16\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e16\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u754c", "id": "1423745880259", "back": "\u754c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b4cc1902-3287-4898-8c64-e8e74536da94/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u754c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u754c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u1edbi (boundary, area/world)"}, {"front": "gi\u1edbi (boundary, area/world)", "id": "1423745880260", "back": "gi\u1edbi (boundary, area/world)  <hr id=answer>  \u754c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b4cc1902-3287-4898-8c64-e8e74536da94/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u754c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u754c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8fdc", "id": "1423746262793", "back": "\u8fdc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dc9a73b8-611e-4dd9-9179-fbd75fa9e68c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fdc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fdc\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  vi\u1ec5n (distant/remote, profound)<div>&nbsp;\u9060</div>"}, {"front": "vi\u1ec5n (distant/remote, profound)<div>&nbsp;\u9060</div>", "id": "1423746262794", "back": "vi\u1ec5n (distant/remote, profound)<div>&nbsp;\u9060</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8fdc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dc9a73b8-611e-4dd9-9179-fbd75fa9e68c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fdc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fdc\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u60c5", "id": "1423746568800", "back": "\u60c5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/eec7cb44-2d5a-462d-94d8-95a79f265508/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u60c5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u60c5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00ecnh (feeling/love, fact/situation)"}, {"front": "t\u00ecnh (feeling/love, fact/situation)", "id": "1423746568801", "back": "t\u00ecnh (feeling/love, fact/situation)  <hr id=answer>  \u60c5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/eec7cb44-2d5a-462d-94d8-95a79f265508/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u60c5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u60c5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e73", "id": "1423746762389", "back": "\u5e73 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/db377174-5d61-4a15-8f82-29fbb07b1cb7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e73\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e73\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00ecnh (flat/level, even/fair, calm/peace, normal/regular)"}, {"front": "b\u00ecnh (flat/level, even/fair, calm/peace, normal/regular)", "id": "1423746762390", "back": "b\u00ecnh (flat/level, even/fair, calm/peace, normal/regular)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e73 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/db377174-5d61-4a15-8f82-29fbb07b1cb7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e73\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e73\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u904a", "id": "1423747228288", "back": "\u904a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/63e85a55-dda1-478f-8257-e8ccc7ec51c1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u904a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u904a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  du (travel, move eye)"}, {"front": "du (travel, move eye)", "id": "1423747228289", "back": "du (travel, move eye)  <hr id=answer>  \u904a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/63e85a55-dda1-478f-8257-e8ccc7ec51c1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u904a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u904a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5206", "id": "1423747420601", "back": "\u5206 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e74d1fd4-cc9d-47ba-847c-1ea8b39b00c3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5206\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5206\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u00e2n, ph\u1ea7n, ph\u1eadn (divide, cm/minute/cent)"}, {"front": "ph\u00e2n, ph\u1ea7n, ph\u1eadn (divide, cm/minute/cent)", "id": "1423747420602", "back": "ph\u00e2n, ph\u1ea7n, ph\u1eadn (divide, cm/minute/cent)  <hr id=answer>  \u5206 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e74d1fd4-cc9d-47ba-847c-1ea8b39b00c3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5206\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5206\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e07", "id": "1423748293280", "back": "\u4e07 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/03ebc949-9bb9-42b9-b5b3-5b7fe9ab6bfc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e07\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e07\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u1ea1n (10000, lots of, all)<div>&nbsp;\u842c</div>"}, {"front": "v\u1ea1n (10000, lots of, all)<div>&nbsp;\u842c</div>", "id": "1423748293281", "back": "v\u1ea1n (10000, lots of, all)<div>&nbsp;\u842c</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e07 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/03ebc949-9bb9-42b9-b5b3-5b7fe9ab6bfc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e07\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e07\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5343", "id": "1423748590700", "back": "\u5343 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/79cee91b-b13f-4b05-8c70-c928473bb616/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5343\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5343\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thi\u00ean (1000, a lot of/very)"}, {"front": "thi\u00ean (1000, a lot of/very)", "id": "1423748590701", "back": "thi\u00ean (1000, a lot of/very)  <hr id=answer>  \u5343 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/79cee91b-b13f-4b05-8c70-c928473bb616/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5343\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5343\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8c0b", "id": "1423748734787", "back": "\u8c0b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/04f51209-d923-4bd7-8d4c-c66d9627af45/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c0b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c0b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u01b0u (plan/scheme)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8b00</div>"}, {"front": "m\u01b0u (plan/scheme)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8b00</div>", "id": "1423748734788", "back": "m\u01b0u (plan/scheme)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8b00</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8c0b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/04f51209-d923-4bd7-8d4c-c66d9627af45/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c0b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c0b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u67d0", "id": "1423748972857", "back": "\u67d0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8c5a4032-999b-4e9f-b184-a8be47eeeb71/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u67d0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u67d0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ed7 (someone/something, I)"}, {"front": "m\u1ed7 (someone/something, I)", "id": "1423748972858", "back": "m\u1ed7 (someone/something, I)  <hr id=answer>  \u67d0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8c5a4032-999b-4e9f-b184-a8be47eeeb71/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u67d0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u67d0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6de1", "id": "1423749233871", "back": "\u6de1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/83103630-dcb2-4846-8082-fe98e0a05fb4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6de1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6de1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ea1m (bland, modest, slight/weak/thin, not salty)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ea1m (bland, modest, slight/weak/thin, not salty)", "id": "1423749233872", "back": "\u0111\u1ea1m (bland, modest, slight/weak/thin, not salty)  <hr id=answer>  \u6de1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/83103630-dcb2-4846-8082-fe98e0a05fb4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6de1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6de1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u708e", "id": "1423749432295", "back": "\u708e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/602d047f-ca32-4267-be0e-702fe63b3b7e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u708e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u708e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  vi\u00eam (hot/burning, to flame/flare up, inflamation)"}, {"front": "vi\u00eam (hot/burning, to flame/flare up, inflamation)", "id": "1423749432296", "back": "vi\u00eam (hot/burning, to flame/flare up, inflamation)  <hr id=answer>  \u708e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/602d047f-ca32-4267-be0e-702fe63b3b7e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u708e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u708e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7518", "id": "1423749570144", "back": "\u7518 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c1eaaf67-75f3-49a9-8940-a52741921c4d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7518\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7518\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  cam (sweet, accepting)"}, {"front": "cam (sweet, accepting)", "id": "1423749570145", "back": "cam (sweet, accepting)  <hr id=answer>  \u7518 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c1eaaf67-75f3-49a9-8940-a52741921c4d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7518\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7518\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6c60", "id": "1424934126667", "back": "\u6c60 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bdfc75d8-ed98-4450-95e5-51749f213273/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c60\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c60\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u00ec (pond/moat, floor)"}, {"front": "tr\u00ec (pond/moat, floor)", "id": "1424934126668", "back": "tr\u00ec (pond/moat, floor)  <hr id=answer>  \u6c60 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bdfc75d8-ed98-4450-95e5-51749f213273/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c60\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c60\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5f00", "id": "1424934288648", "back": "\u5f00 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cdce3526-5701-4b9d-9471-a6dc7defd64e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f00\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f00\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  khai (open, split/remove)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u958b&nbsp;</div>"}, {"front": "khai (open, split/remove)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u958b&nbsp;</div>", "id": "1424934288649", "back": "khai (open, split/remove)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u958b&nbsp;</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5f00 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cdce3526-5701-4b9d-9471-a6dc7defd64e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f00\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f00\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u77e5", "id": "1424934958026", "back": "\u77e5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/065476b2-c63a-40bc-b92d-8dc7d2c43eb7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u77e5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u77e5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tri (know)"}, {"front": "tri (know)", "id": "1424934958027", "back": "tri (know)  <hr id=answer>  \u77e5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/065476b2-c63a-40bc-b92d-8dc7d2c43eb7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u77e5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u77e5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bc6", "id": "1424935199967", "back": "\u8bc6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9c372af6-c32c-4675-8406-3a69eb96f60d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bc6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bc6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ee9c (recognize/know, knowledge)<div>ch\u00ed (memorize)</div><div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8b58</div>"}, {"front": "th\u1ee9c (recognize/know, knowledge)<div>ch\u00ed (memorize)</div><div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8b58</div>", "id": "1424935199968", "back": "th\u1ee9c (recognize/know, knowledge)<div>ch\u00ed (memorize)</div><div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8b58</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8bc6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9c372af6-c32c-4675-8406-3a69eb96f60d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bc6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bc6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5ac1", "id": "1424935409529", "back": "\u5ac1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2893740a-b943-4223-af97-ef8e2d7f072e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5ac1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5ac1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u00e1 (marry a husband/blame)"}, {"front": "gi\u00e1 (marry a husband/blame)", "id": "1424935409530", "back": "gi\u00e1 (marry a husband/blame)  <hr id=answer>  \u5ac1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2893740a-b943-4223-af97-ef8e2d7f072e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5ac1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5ac1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u59bb", "id": "1424935503206", "back": "\u59bb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/520905a3-988e-4e0c-a498-e5c86d0e9142/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u59bb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u59bb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00ea (wife)"}, {"front": "th\u00ea (wife)", "id": "1424935503207", "back": "th\u00ea (wife)  <hr id=answer>  \u59bb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/520905a3-988e-4e0c-a498-e5c86d0e9142/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u59bb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u59bb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6728", "id": "1424935627125", "back": "\u6728 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4ad202d1-76ab-4f3d-b0fc-907a5064808a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6728\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6728\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ed9c (wood/tree, simple/numb/dull)"}, {"front": "m\u1ed9c (wood/tree, simple/numb/dull)", "id": "1424935627126", "back": "m\u1ed9c (wood/tree, simple/numb/dull)  <hr id=answer>  \u6728 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4ad202d1-76ab-4f3d-b0fc-907a5064808a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6728\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6728\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u674e", "id": "1424935903566", "back": "\u674e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0862c0cf-528f-4eae-8bb2-59de5ebbbde1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u674e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u674e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u00ed (last name, plum)"}, {"front": "l\u00ed (last name, plum)", "id": "1424935903567", "back": "l\u00ed (last name, plum)  <hr id=answer>  \u674e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0862c0cf-528f-4eae-8bb2-59de5ebbbde1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u674e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u674e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6816", "id": "1424936065250", "back": "\u6816 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/249d4bfe-291a-4cbd-b1b3-47ea62c68268/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6816\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6816\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00ea, th\u00ea (stay/rest, bed)<div><br /><div>&nbsp;\u68f2</div></div>"}, {"front": "t\u00ea, th\u00ea (stay/rest, bed)<div><br /><div>&nbsp;\u68f2</div></div>", "id": "1424936065251", "back": "t\u00ea, th\u00ea (stay/rest, bed)<div><br /><div>&nbsp;\u68f2</div></div>  <hr id=answer>  \u6816 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/249d4bfe-291a-4cbd-b1b3-47ea62c68268/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6816\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6816\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u592b", "id": "1424936247505", "back": "\u592b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b98f606b-d1eb-4d2a-9685-998c06f9f8e1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u592b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u592b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  phu (husband/man)"}, {"front": "phu (husband/man)", "id": "1424936247506", "back": "phu (husband/man)  <hr id=answer>  \u592b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b98f606b-d1eb-4d2a-9685-998c06f9f8e1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u592b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u592b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c11", "id": "1424936542763", "back": "\u5c11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bebc1310-17bf-4b35-b3ef-8414b87a7f6b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c11\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thi\u1ec3u, thi\u1ebfu (little, missing/absent/wanting)"}, {"front": "thi\u1ec3u, thi\u1ebfu (little, missing/absent/wanting)", "id": "1424936542764", "back": "thi\u1ec3u, thi\u1ebfu (little, missing/absent/wanting)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bebc1310-17bf-4b35-b3ef-8414b87a7f6b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c11\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c16", "id": "1424936654636", "back": "\u5c16 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a50eb7de-4cbb-4d38-870f-6d51824032d0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c16\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c16\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u00eam (sharp/pointed, pointed part)"}, {"front": "ti\u00eam (sharp/pointed, pointed part)", "id": "1424936654637", "back": "ti\u00eam (sharp/pointed, pointed part)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c16 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a50eb7de-4cbb-4d38-870f-6d51824032d0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c16\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c16\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u660e", "id": "1424936786535", "back": "\u660e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bf12242d-4640-4b2a-9e08-7265d290c3ab/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u660e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u660e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  minh (bright/brilliant, day/dawn)"}, {"front": "minh (bright/brilliant, day/dawn)", "id": "1424936786536", "back": "minh (bright/brilliant, day/dawn)  <hr id=answer>  \u660e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bf12242d-4640-4b2a-9e08-7265d290c3ab/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u660e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u660e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65e6", "id": "1424937092585", "back": "\u65e6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f031c64f-1528-48ae-871a-055878276990/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65e6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65e6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00e1n (dawn, day, female role in Chinese opera)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00e1n (dawn, day, female role in Chinese opera)", "id": "1424937092586", "back": "\u0111\u00e1n (dawn, day, female role in Chinese opera)  <hr id=answer>  \u65e6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f031c64f-1528-48ae-871a-055878276990/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65e6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65e6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6676", "id": "1424937480448", "back": "\u6676 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/95d19c50-4771-4cc1-80d8-a3f4fd9b9c8e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6676\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6676\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tinh (clear/crystal, light)"}, {"front": "tinh (clear/crystal, light)", "id": "1424937480449", "back": "tinh (clear/crystal, light)  <hr id=answer>  \u6676 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/95d19c50-4771-4cc1-80d8-a3f4fd9b9c8e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6676\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6676\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7532", "id": "1424938298552", "back": "\u7532 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ff8cf8a8-7a84-48d1-8953-c506e2d0d768/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7532\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7532\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u00e1p (first of&nbsp;thi\u00ean can, armor/nail/shell, most outstanding/first)"}, {"front": "gi\u00e1p (first of&nbsp;thi\u00ean can, armor/nail/shell, most outstanding/first)", "id": "1424938298553", "back": "gi\u00e1p (first of&nbsp;thi\u00ean can, armor/nail/shell, most outstanding/first)  <hr id=answer>  \u7532 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ff8cf8a8-7a84-48d1-8953-c506e2d0d768/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7532\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7532\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f11", "id": "1424938385044", "back": "\u4f11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9f3b7bf9-e407-4295-a32f-bf59e87cb352/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f11\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u01b0u (rest/stop/cease, joy/happiness)"}, {"front": "h\u01b0u (rest/stop/cease, joy/happiness)", "id": "1424938385045", "back": "h\u01b0u (rest/stop/cease, joy/happiness)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9f3b7bf9-e407-4295-a32f-bf59e87cb352/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f11\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e1c", "id": "1424938641655", "back": "\u4e1c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/48d596d5-7be2-4fcc-8779-b0b33236c3a4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e1c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e1c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00f4ng (east, Japan, host/owner)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u6771</div>"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00f4ng (east, Japan, host/owner)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u6771</div>", "id": "1424938641656", "back": "\u0111\u00f4ng (east, Japan, host/owner)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u6771</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e1c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/48d596d5-7be2-4fcc-8779-b0b33236c3a4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e1c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e1c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u897f", "id": "1424938845955", "back": "\u897f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/61d28145-056a-4d87-ad76-5546c9684d88/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u897f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u897f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00e2y (west)"}, {"front": "t\u00e2y (west)", "id": "1424938845956", "back": "t\u00e2y (west)  <hr id=answer>  \u897f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/61d28145-056a-4d87-ad76-5546c9684d88/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u897f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u897f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5357", "id": "1424939510089", "back": "\u5357 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a591f18e-f0d6-4cfd-ab60-23ba0171d34a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5357\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5357\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nam (south)"}, {"front": "nam (south)", "id": "1424939510090", "back": "nam (south)  <hr id=answer>  \u5357 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a591f18e-f0d6-4cfd-ab60-23ba0171d34a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5357\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5357\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5974", "id": "1424939642421", "back": "\u5974 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2afd0296-dfad-4895-8cf0-2400e19a1263/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5974\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5974\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  n\u00f4 (slave/servant)"}, {"front": "n\u00f4 (slave/servant)", "id": "1424939642422", "back": "n\u00f4 (slave/servant)  <hr id=answer>  \u5974 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2afd0296-dfad-4895-8cf0-2400e19a1263/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5974\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5974\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u770b", "id": "1424939799836", "back": "\u770b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8497a70f-b6a3-4f82-ba31-7af8c4dddc64/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u770b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u770b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u00e1n (observe, watch/look after)"}, {"front": "kh\u00e1n (observe, watch/look after)", "id": "1424939799837", "back": "kh\u00e1n (observe, watch/look after)  <hr id=answer>  \u770b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8497a70f-b6a3-4f82-ba31-7af8c4dddc64/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u770b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u770b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5de6", "id": "1424939950480", "back": "\u5de6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ac5a8531-be83-436f-9c93-012fdf9f5cd7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5de6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5de6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ea3, t\u00e1 (left/east, wrong/bad)"}, {"front": "t\u1ea3, t\u00e1 (left/east, wrong/bad)", "id": "1424939950481", "back": "t\u1ea3, t\u00e1 (left/east, wrong/bad)  <hr id=answer>  \u5de6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ac5a8531-be83-436f-9c93-012fdf9f5cd7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5de6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5de6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53f3", "id": "1424940115157", "back": "\u53f3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f09546b3-b931-4433-865d-940207db3f03/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53f3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53f3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1eefu (right/west, good/important, help/aid/emphasize)"}, {"front": "h\u1eefu (right/west, good/important, help/aid/emphasize)", "id": "1424940115158", "back": "h\u1eefu (right/west, good/important, help/aid/emphasize)  <hr id=answer>  \u53f3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f09546b3-b931-4433-865d-940207db3f03/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53f3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53f3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53d6", "id": "1424940261807", "back": "\u53d6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/42d94ca1-c89d-4c93-a01e-01d173c26c70/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53d6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53d6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ee7 (summon, obtain/take)"}, {"front": "th\u1ee7 (summon, obtain/take)", "id": "1424940261808", "back": "th\u1ee7 (summon, obtain/take)  <hr id=answer>  \u53d6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/42d94ca1-c89d-4c93-a01e-01d173c26c70/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53d6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53d6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5a36", "id": "1424940449956", "back": "\u5a36 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0fbdcb67-3c38-48ec-a698-cc854cbbdbbc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5a36\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5a36\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00fa (marrying a wife)"}, {"front": "th\u00fa (marrying a wife)", "id": "1424940449957", "back": "th\u00fa (marrying a wife)  <hr id=answer>  \u5a36 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0fbdcb67-3c38-48ec-a698-cc854cbbdbbc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5a36\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5a36\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5144", "id": "1424940513537", "back": "\u5144 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2b23a702-ff88-44a0-92a2-4ff511b5b700/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5144\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5144\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  huynh (older brother)"}, {"front": "huynh (older brother)", "id": "1424940513538", "back": "huynh (older brother)  <hr id=answer>  \u5144 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2b23a702-ff88-44a0-92a2-4ff511b5b700/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5144\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5144\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53e4", "id": "1424941779587", "back": "\u53e4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5b627f36-d7fa-4610-a7b5-b77e68daf3e6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53e4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53e4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ed5 (old)"}, {"front": "c\u1ed5 (old)", "id": "1424941779588", "back": "c\u1ed5 (old)  <hr id=answer>  \u53e4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5b627f36-d7fa-4610-a7b5-b77e68daf3e6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53e4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53e4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8ba1", "id": "1424942004438", "back": "\u8ba1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/08134d9c-1611-4bd7-b496-688969bf829d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8ba1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8ba1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  k\u1ebf (plan/scheme), count/measure"}, {"front": "k\u1ebf (plan/scheme), count/measure", "id": "1424942004439", "back": "k\u1ebf (plan/scheme), count/measure  <hr id=answer>  \u8ba1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/08134d9c-1611-4bd7-b496-688969bf829d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8ba1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8ba1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6012", "id": "1424942119292", "back": "\u6012 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2de78952-f422-4b45-9477-09b30d67b207/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6012\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6012\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  n\u1ed9 (anger, vigorous, sprout forth)&nbsp;"}, {"front": "n\u1ed9 (anger, vigorous, sprout forth)&nbsp;", "id": "1424942119293", "back": "n\u1ed9 (anger, vigorous, sprout forth)&nbsp;  <hr id=answer>  \u6012 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2de78952-f422-4b45-9477-09b30d67b207/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6012\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6012\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6015", "id": "1424993438811", "back": "\u6015 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5d681a30-0a13-456a-8563-f0cbc92adced/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6015\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6015\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u1ea1 (fear/afraid, maybe)"}, {"front": "ph\u1ea1 (fear/afraid, maybe)", "id": "1424993438813", "back": "ph\u1ea1 (fear/afraid, maybe)  <hr id=answer>  \u6015 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5d681a30-0a13-456a-8563-f0cbc92adced/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6015\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6015\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9f7f", "id": "1424993561134", "back": "\u9f7f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/61a78790-6a30-498d-8490-c48983d01904/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9f7f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9f7f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u1ec9 (teeth, age, mention)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9f52</div>"}, {"front": "x\u1ec9 (teeth, age, mention)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9f52</div>", "id": "1424993561135", "back": "x\u1ec9 (teeth, age, mention)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9f52</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u9f7f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/61a78790-6a30-498d-8490-c48983d01904/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9f7f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9f7f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6b63", "id": "1424993789769", "back": "\u6b63 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7f0031e2-2f31-4fcb-bfb5-3ee736b7dd28/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b63\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b63\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u00e1nh, ch\u00ednh (right/correct/just, person in command,&nbsp;"}, {"front": "ch\u00e1nh, ch\u00ednh (right/correct/just, person in command,&nbsp;", "id": "1424993789771", "back": "ch\u00e1nh, ch\u00ednh (right/correct/just, person in command,&nbsp;  <hr id=answer>  \u6b63 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7f0031e2-2f31-4fcb-bfb5-3ee736b7dd28/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b63\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b63\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u571f", "id": "1424993888318", "back": "\u571f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9aedc168-b383-41bc-9998-50c0276b9f62/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u571f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u571f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ed5 (earth/soil/land, local/native)"}, {"front": "th\u1ed5 (earth/soil/land, local/native)", "id": "1424993888319", "back": "th\u1ed5 (earth/soil/land, local/native)  <hr id=answer>  \u571f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9aedc168-b383-41bc-9998-50c0276b9f62/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u571f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u571f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u58eb", "id": "1424994114410", "back": "\u58eb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/90722c2e-b5df-4d76-b17a-6beeefbb9be3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u58eb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u58eb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u0129 (scholar/man/officer/soldier)"}, {"front": "s\u0129 (scholar/man/officer/soldier)", "id": "1424994114411", "back": "s\u0129 (scholar/man/officer/soldier)  <hr id=answer>  \u58eb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/90722c2e-b5df-4d76-b17a-6beeefbb9be3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u58eb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u58eb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5750", "id": "1424994295376", "back": "\u5750 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7ecbb8e8-4718-498f-9be0-d6e4ddd048fc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5750\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5750\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ecda (sit/ride, be accused/punished)"}, {"front": "t\u1ecda (sit/ride, be accused/punished)", "id": "1424994295377", "back": "t\u1ecda (sit/ride, be accused/punished)  <hr id=answer>  \u5750 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7ecbb8e8-4718-498f-9be0-d6e4ddd048fc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5750\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5750\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u51fa", "id": "1424994359192", "back": "\u51fa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ab34675a-5190-46c8-a7d2-8175f951265d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51fa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51fa\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  xu\u1ea5t (go out)"}, {"front": "xu\u1ea5t (go out)", "id": "1424994359193", "back": "xu\u1ea5t (go out)  <hr id=answer>  \u51fa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ab34675a-5190-46c8-a7d2-8175f951265d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51fa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51fa\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8d31", "id": "1424994387820", "back": "\u8d31 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/db675089-5040-468d-aaaf-c7dd0494efa7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d31\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d31\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u1ec7n (cheap)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8ce4</div>"}, {"front": "ti\u1ec7n (cheap)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8ce4</div>", "id": "1424994387821", "back": "ti\u1ec7n (cheap)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8ce4</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8d31 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/db675089-5040-468d-aaaf-c7dd0494efa7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d31\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d31\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e70&nbsp;\u8cb7", "id": "1424994504132", "back": "\u4e70&nbsp;\u8cb7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/16006eb6-752c-4f1e-b40f-23f839c57cbe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e70&nbsp;\u8cb7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e70&nbsp;\u8cb7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u00e3i (buy)"}, {"front": "m\u00e3i (buy)", "id": "1424994504133", "back": "m\u00e3i (buy)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e70&nbsp;\u8cb7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/16006eb6-752c-4f1e-b40f-23f839c57cbe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e70&nbsp;\u8cb7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e70&nbsp;\u8cb7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5356", "id": "1424994562842", "back": "\u5356 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/72929128-2461-4bcf-87ad-e5c29e351a84/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5356\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5356\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ea1i (sell)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8ce3</div>"}, {"front": "m\u1ea1i (sell)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8ce3</div>", "id": "1424994562843", "back": "m\u1ea1i (sell)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8ce3</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5356 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/72929128-2461-4bcf-87ad-e5c29e351a84/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5356\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5356\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6cc9", "id": "1424994646044", "back": "\u6cc9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d0824486-47c3-4166-88ba-7e74a6b0e51f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6cc9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6cc9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tuy\u1ec1n&nbsp;<div>spring, money (archaic)</div>"}, {"front": "tuy\u1ec1n&nbsp;<div>spring, money (archaic)</div>", "id": "1424994646046", "back": "tuy\u1ec1n&nbsp;<div>spring, money (archaic)</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u6cc9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d0824486-47c3-4166-88ba-7e74a6b0e51f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6cc9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6cc9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6f0f", "id": "1424994737194", "back": "\u6f0f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5582a1d6-0359-4f99-9bbc-3c905baee2f8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6f0f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6f0f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1eadu (leak, water clock/hourglass)"}, {"front": "l\u1eadu (leak, water clock/hourglass)", "id": "1424994737195", "back": "l\u1eadu (leak, water clock/hourglass)  <hr id=answer>  \u6f0f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5582a1d6-0359-4f99-9bbc-3c905baee2f8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6f0f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6f0f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e91", "id": "1424994916374", "back": "\u4e91 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c6df7e99-0135-46b2-a21e-e80caa7aafe8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e91\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e91\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u00e2n (cloud, say/speak, \"et cetera\")<div>&nbsp;\u96f2</div><div><br /></div>"}, {"front": "v\u00e2n (cloud, say/speak, \"et cetera\")<div>&nbsp;\u96f2</div><div><br /></div>", "id": "1424994916375", "back": "v\u00e2n (cloud, say/speak, \"et cetera\")<div>&nbsp;\u96f2</div><div><br /></div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e91 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c6df7e99-0135-46b2-a21e-e80caa7aafe8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e91\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e91\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u96ea", "id": "1424994995719", "back": "\u96ea <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c8eddb20-5d81-4bd2-979c-67d04622f659/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u96ea\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u96ea\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tuy\u1ebft (snow, clean, wipe/wash)"}, {"front": "tuy\u1ebft (snow, clean, wipe/wash)", "id": "1424994995720", "back": "tuy\u1ebft (snow, clean, wipe/wash)  <hr id=answer>  \u96ea <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c8eddb20-5d81-4bd2-979c-67d04622f659/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u96ea\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u96ea\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u96f7", "id": "1424995070041", "back": "\u96f7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/12d5f78b-70bd-4971-b512-d07af1210239/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u96f7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u96f7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u00f4i (thunder, mine)"}, {"front": "l\u00f4i (thunder, mine)", "id": "1424995070042", "back": "l\u00f4i (thunder, mine)  <hr id=answer>  \u96f7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/12d5f78b-70bd-4971-b512-d07af1210239/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u96f7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u96f7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f1e", "id": "1424995168339", "back": "\u4f1e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/27f15627-ad65-40af-9a40-1fec72c381a5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f1e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f1e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00e1n (umbrella/parachute)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5098</div>"}, {"front": "t\u00e1n (umbrella/parachute)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5098</div>", "id": "1424995168340", "back": "t\u00e1n (umbrella/parachute)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5098</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4f1e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/27f15627-ad65-40af-9a40-1fec72c381a5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f1e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f1e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5ddd", "id": "1424995237225", "back": "\u5ddd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f71ee1bb-d634-4abe-b0c0-e933b03b47fa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5ddd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5ddd\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  xuy\u00ean (river, boil with water)"}, {"front": "xuy\u00ean (river, boil with water)", "id": "1424995237226", "back": "xuy\u00ean (river, boil with water)  <hr id=answer>  \u5ddd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f71ee1bb-d634-4abe-b0c0-e933b03b47fa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5ddd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5ddd\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c9b", "id": "1424995257800", "back": "\u5c9b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3e8e96c7-8ac1-46f5-8f19-61782c50c437/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c9b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c9b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ea3o (island)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ea3o (island)", "id": "1424995257801", "back": "\u0111\u1ea3o (island)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c9b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3e8e96c7-8ac1-46f5-8f19-61782c50c437/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c9b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c9b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e4c", "id": "1424995375557", "back": "\u4e4c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dee7fbca-f71c-4c14-afe0-5ce59b6e0e62/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e4c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e4c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u00f4&nbsp;<div>crow/raven, dark, sun (similar to rabbit for moon)</div>"}, {"front": "\u00f4&nbsp;<div>crow/raven, dark, sun (similar to rabbit for moon)</div>", "id": "1424995375558", "back": "\u00f4&nbsp;<div>crow/raven, dark, sun (similar to rabbit for moon)</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e4c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dee7fbca-f71c-4c14-afe0-5ce59b6e0e62/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e4c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e4c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u98de", "id": "1424995529131", "back": "\u98de <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1b48792f-518a-4f2e-baf1-7f0df1242012/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u98de\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u98de\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  phi (fly, fleeting/unsubstantial/surprise)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u98db</div>"}, {"front": "phi (fly, fleeting/unsubstantial/surprise)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u98db</div>", "id": "1424995529133", "back": "phi (fly, fleeting/unsubstantial/surprise)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u98db</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u98de <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1b48792f-518a-4f2e-baf1-7f0df1242012/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u98de\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u98de\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e60&nbsp;\u7fd2", "id": "1424995625686", "back": "\u4e60&nbsp;\u7fd2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a5458e5f-3ad2-4e53-bfe3-a2dceb8a3200/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e60&nbsp;\u7fd2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e60&nbsp;\u7fd2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1eadp (practice/learn, habit/custom)"}, {"front": "t\u1eadp (practice/learn, habit/custom)", "id": "1424995625687", "back": "t\u1eadp (practice/learn, habit/custom)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e60&nbsp;\u7fd2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a5458e5f-3ad2-4e53-bfe3-a2dceb8a3200/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e60&nbsp;\u7fd2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e60&nbsp;\u7fd2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6247", "id": "1424995702321", "back": "\u6247 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c5bb80fa-5cce-41cc-a5e0-1751824caa4b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6247\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6247\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  phi\u1ebfn (fan, numerary for door/gate leaves)"}, {"front": "phi\u1ebfn (fan, numerary for door/gate leaves)", "id": "1424995702322", "back": "phi\u1ebfn (fan, numerary for door/gate leaves)  <hr id=answer>  \u6247 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c5bb80fa-5cce-41cc-a5e0-1751824caa4b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6247\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6247\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9c7c", "id": "1424995730406", "back": "\u9c7c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/768469ec-704a-40ab-a237-5029bc1ec6ea/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9c7c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9c7c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u01b0<div>fish</div><div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9b5a</div>"}, {"front": "ng\u01b0<div>fish</div><div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9b5a</div>", "id": "1424995730407", "back": "ng\u01b0<div>fish</div><div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9b5a</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u9c7c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/768469ec-704a-40ab-a237-5029bc1ec6ea/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9c7c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9c7c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6e14", "id": "1424995828644", "back": "\u6e14 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f249b41a-aeca-414b-ba2d-da6dc956e2b7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6e14\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6e14\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u01b0<div>fishing, to fish, seek dishonorably</div>"}, {"front": "ng\u01b0<div>fishing, to fish, seek dishonorably</div>", "id": "1424995828645", "back": "ng\u01b0<div>fishing, to fish, seek dishonorably</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u6e14 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f249b41a-aeca-414b-ba2d-da6dc956e2b7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6e14\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6e14\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9c81", "id": "1424995869096", "back": "\u9c81 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d3150913-0566-4a9d-a830-7e838af0d436/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9c81\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9c81\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1ed7 (foolish)"}, {"front": "l\u1ed7 (foolish)", "id": "1424995869097", "back": "l\u1ed7 (foolish)  <hr id=answer>  \u9c81 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d3150913-0566-4a9d-a830-7e838af0d436/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9c81\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9c81\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7f94", "id": "1425020428165", "back": "\u7f94 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/34d903f0-1e81-43f4-9ac0-c0156d7c0627/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7f94\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7f94\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  cao (lamb, young/little)"}, {"front": "cao (lamb, young/little)", "id": "1425020428166", "back": "cao (lamb, young/little)  <hr id=answer>  \u7f94 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/34d903f0-1e81-43f4-9ac0-c0156d7c0627/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7f94\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7f94\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e49", "id": "1425020628930", "back": "\u4e49 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/17ab1acf-231c-410f-8ed2-0e25c8ca5fbf/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e49\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e49\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ngh\u0129a (justice/chivalry, meaning, faux/artificial)<div>&nbsp;\u7fa9</div>"}, {"front": "ngh\u0129a (justice/chivalry, meaning, faux/artificial)<div>&nbsp;\u7fa9</div>", "id": "1425020628932", "back": "ngh\u0129a (justice/chivalry, meaning, faux/artificial)<div>&nbsp;\u7fa9</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e49 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/17ab1acf-231c-410f-8ed2-0e25c8ca5fbf/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e49\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e49\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6d0b", "id": "1425021233752", "back": "\u6d0b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6a10dd49-9b12-4656-8816-f01b75fd659e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d0b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d0b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u01b0\u01a1ng (ocean, big/great, foreign)"}, {"front": "d\u01b0\u01a1ng (ocean, big/great, foreign)", "id": "1425021233753", "back": "d\u01b0\u01a1ng (ocean, big/great, foreign)  <hr id=answer>  \u6d0b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6a10dd49-9b12-4656-8816-f01b75fd659e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d0b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d0b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7fa1", "id": "1425021556712", "back": "\u7fa1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c6408ac8-3e90-417a-8a1e-78b84ff249af/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7fa1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7fa1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u1ec7n (to covet/envy)<div><br /></div><div>\u7fa8</div>"}, {"front": "ti\u1ec7n (to covet/envy)<div><br /></div><div>\u7fa8</div>", "id": "1425021556713", "back": "ti\u1ec7n (to covet/envy)<div><br /></div><div>\u7fa8</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u7fa1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c6408ac8-3e90-417a-8a1e-78b84ff249af/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7fa1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7fa1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8c08", "id": "1425021643802", "back": "\u8c08 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4f19c9ee-a542-4679-bef7-13ad05ce3a7a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c08\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c08\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00e0m (talk/chat)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8ac7</div>"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00e0m (talk/chat)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8ac7</div>", "id": "1425021643803", "back": "\u0111\u00e0m (talk/chat)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8ac7</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8c08 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4f19c9ee-a542-4679-bef7-13ad05ce3a7a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c08\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c08\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7070", "id": "1425022090805", "back": "\u7070 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d8b9a470-c785-4c12-be0e-60404d3ad322/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7070\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7070\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u00f4i, kh\u00f4i (ash, lime, disappointed/discouraged)"}, {"front": "h\u00f4i, kh\u00f4i (ash, lime, disappointed/discouraged)", "id": "1425022090806", "back": "h\u00f4i, kh\u00f4i (ash, lime, disappointed/discouraged)  <hr id=answer>  \u7070 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d8b9a470-c785-4c12-be0e-60404d3ad322/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7070\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7070\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u707e", "id": "1425022171563", "back": "\u707e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/87c4ac5c-0176-4287-846b-de8079a31f50/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u707e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u707e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tai (disaster)"}, {"front": "tai (disaster)", "id": "1425022171564", "back": "tai (disaster)  <hr id=answer>  \u707e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/87c4ac5c-0176-4287-846b-de8079a31f50/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u707e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u707e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u717d", "id": "1425022232513", "back": "\u717d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9e36a912-c6bc-4c1a-a699-81a3fb9170eb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u717d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u717d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  phi\u1ebfn (to fan/stir up a fire, to incite)"}, {"front": "phi\u1ebfn (to fan/stir up a fire, to incite)", "id": "1425022232514", "back": "phi\u1ebfn (to fan/stir up a fire, to incite)  <hr id=answer>  \u717d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9e36a912-c6bc-4c1a-a699-81a3fb9170eb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u717d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u717d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u70e7", "id": "1425022482212", "back": "\u70e7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b1693ad6-1c06-470a-bf6e-d10e9c130bfe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u70e7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u70e7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thi\u00eau (burn/cook, fever)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u71d2</div>"}, {"front": "thi\u00eau (burn/cook, fever)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u71d2</div>", "id": "1425022482213", "back": "thi\u00eau (burn/cook, fever)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u71d2</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u70e7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b1693ad6-1c06-470a-bf6e-d10e9c130bfe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u70e7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u70e7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c27", "id": "1425022529413", "back": "\u5c27 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/59d43413-5219-4305-93b6-e59844ed90a7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c27\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c27\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nghi\u00eau (vua&nbsp;Nghi\u00eau)"}, {"front": "nghi\u00eau (vua&nbsp;Nghi\u00eau)", "id": "1425022529414", "back": "nghi\u00eau (vua&nbsp;Nghi\u00eau)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c27 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/59d43413-5219-4305-93b6-e59844ed90a7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c27\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c27\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9ed1", "id": "1425022614108", "back": "\u9ed1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/eab65b59-a528-427e-a5e7-4d780f59dc3e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9ed1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9ed1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1eafc (black/dark/evil)"}, {"front": "h\u1eafc (black/dark/evil)", "id": "1425022614109", "back": "h\u1eafc (black/dark/evil)  <hr id=answer>  \u9ed1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/eab65b59-a528-427e-a5e7-4d780f59dc3e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9ed1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9ed1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u58a8", "id": "1425022758095", "back": "\u58a8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5e5b3f9e-7369-4b72-9ef7-6079cf48c139/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u58a8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u58a8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1eb7c (ink/black)"}, {"front": "m\u1eb7c (ink/black)", "id": "1425022758096", "back": "m\u1eb7c (ink/black)  <hr id=answer>  \u58a8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5e5b3f9e-7369-4b72-9ef7-6079cf48c139/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u58a8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u58a8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u70b9", "id": "1425023007669", "back": "\u70b9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/12eaabf4-dc9e-4a56-8cfd-c0f09596c840/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u70b9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u70b9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111i\u1ec3m (dot, light/ignite, select/nod, show/instruct)<div>&nbsp;\u9ede</div>"}, {"front": "\u0111i\u1ec3m (dot, light/ignite, select/nod, show/instruct)<div>&nbsp;\u9ede</div>", "id": "1425023007670", "back": "\u0111i\u1ec3m (dot, light/ignite, select/nod, show/instruct)<div>&nbsp;\u9ede</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u70b9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/12eaabf4-dc9e-4a56-8cfd-c0f09596c840/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u70b9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u70b9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u82d7", "id": "1425023151737", "back": "\u82d7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2fd63c8d-a4f0-4370-bf98-4d43b0da9fb5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82d7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82d7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  mi\u00eau (sprout/beginning, descendant, vaccine)"}, {"front": "mi\u00eau (sprout/beginning, descendant, vaccine)", "id": "1425023151738", "back": "mi\u00eau (sprout/beginning, descendant, vaccine)  <hr id=answer>  \u82d7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2fd63c8d-a4f0-4370-bf98-4d43b0da9fb5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82d7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82d7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53f6", "id": "1425023282442", "back": "\u53f6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/93ec9423-b077-4c6f-9751-fa91308d7c10/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53f6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53f6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  di\u1ec7p (leaf/page, period/era)<div><br /></div><div>\u8449</div>"}, {"front": "di\u1ec7p (leaf/page, period/era)<div><br /></div><div>\u8449</div>", "id": "1425023282443", "back": "di\u1ec7p (leaf/page, period/era)<div><br /></div><div>\u8449</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u53f6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/93ec9423-b077-4c6f-9751-fa91308d7c10/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53f6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53f6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u82b1", "id": "1425023482879", "back": "\u82b1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6489c0cc-7f4e-4d18-b44d-d11eb36602c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82b1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82b1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  hoa (flower, spend/waste)"}, {"front": "hoa (flower, spend/waste)", "id": "1425023482880", "back": "hoa (flower, spend/waste)  <hr id=answer>  \u82b1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6489c0cc-7f4e-4d18-b44d-d11eb36602c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82b1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82b1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8336", "id": "1425023710539", "back": "\u8336 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3cfde061-a536-4e28-8f5e-7600ad2b58cd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8336\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8336\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u00e0 (tea)"}, {"front": "tr\u00e0 (tea)", "id": "1425023710540", "back": "tr\u00e0 (tea)  <hr id=answer>  \u8336 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3cfde061-a536-4e28-8f5e-7600ad2b58cd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8336\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8336\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u82f1", "id": "1425023832594", "back": "\u82f1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c908aebb-5120-4138-87f4-26f11c491ae2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82f1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82f1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  anh (hero, brilliant, England/English)"}, {"front": "anh (hero, brilliant, England/English)", "id": "1425023832595", "back": "anh (hero, brilliant, England/English)  <hr id=answer>  \u82f1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c908aebb-5120-4138-87f4-26f11c491ae2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82f1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82f1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7b14", "id": "1425023921047", "back": "\u7b14 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/62f09c6f-1fd2-46a8-b59e-1136882a5c0d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b14\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b14\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00fat (brush/pen, write)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u7b46</div>"}, {"front": "b\u00fat (brush/pen, write)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u7b46</div>", "id": "1425023921048", "back": "b\u00fat (brush/pen, write)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u7b46</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u7b14 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/62f09c6f-1fd2-46a8-b59e-1136882a5c0d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b14\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b14\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7b97", "id": "1425285055956", "back": "\u7b97 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cd9b5bfa-5258-4376-8b5c-432264cfd29b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b97\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b97\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  to\u00e1n (count/calculate, plan/scheme)"}, {"front": "to\u00e1n (count/calculate, plan/scheme)", "id": "1425285055959", "back": "to\u00e1n (count/calculate, plan/scheme)  <hr id=answer>  \u7b97 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cd9b5bfa-5258-4376-8b5c-432264cfd29b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b97\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b97\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7b11", "id": "1425285228517", "back": "\u7b11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c9a576b1-385f-44a1-8551-8be09ddaa864/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b11\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u1ebfu (laugh/deride)"}, {"front": "ti\u1ebfu (laugh/deride)", "id": "1425285228518", "back": "ti\u1ebfu (laugh/deride)  <hr id=answer>  \u7b11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c9a576b1-385f-44a1-8551-8be09ddaa864/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b11\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u79cb", "id": "1425285335083", "back": "\u79cb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0d526f96-4898-4cce-bcc8-ec2d828f4d2a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79cb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79cb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thu (autumn, year/old age)"}, {"front": "thu (autumn, year/old age)", "id": "1425285335084", "back": "thu (autumn, year/old age)  <hr id=answer>  \u79cb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0d526f96-4898-4cce-bcc8-ec2d828f4d2a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79cb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79cb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6101", "id": "1425285916114", "back": "\u6101 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/580623e2-032f-4bae-9c21-c72fca95db72/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6101\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6101\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u1ea7u (sad)"}, {"front": "s\u1ea7u (sad)", "id": "1425285916115", "back": "s\u1ea7u (sad)  <hr id=answer>  \u6101 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/580623e2-032f-4bae-9c21-c72fca95db72/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6101\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6101\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7a0e", "id": "1425286111318", "back": "\u7a0e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4593b1b9-5cdd-4560-b5f4-86a28452cf24/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7a0e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7a0e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thu\u1ebf (taxes), rent/trade, release"}, {"front": "thu\u1ebf (taxes), rent/trade, release", "id": "1425286111319", "back": "thu\u1ebf (taxes), rent/trade, release  <hr id=answer>  \u7a0e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4593b1b9-5cdd-4560-b5f4-86a28452cf24/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7a0e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7a0e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u79c3", "id": "1425286219378", "back": "\u79c3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c25de532-775b-4f52-ad63-f62d4b573a42/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79c3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79c3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u1ed1c (bald/bare)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u79bf</div>"}, {"front": "ng\u1ed1c (bald/bare)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u79bf</div>", "id": "1425286219379", "back": "ng\u1ed1c (bald/bare)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u79bf</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u79c3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c25de532-775b-4f52-ad63-f62d4b573a42/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79c3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79c3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u82cf", "id": "1425286452011", "back": "\u82cf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d0b37c81-0189-45b4-8e32-c1dee92ad787/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82cf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82cf\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00f4 (last name/province name, revive, mint, Soviet)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8607</div>"}, {"front": "t\u00f4 (last name/province name, revive, mint, Soviet)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8607</div>", "id": "1425286452012", "back": "t\u00f4 (last name/province name, revive, mint, Soviet)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u8607</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u82cf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d0b37c81-0189-45b4-8e32-c1dee92ad787/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82cf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82cf\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9999", "id": "1425286599725", "back": "\u9999 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ca68680c-44e7-4672-b3d3-3fd03d183d31/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9999\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9999\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u01b0\u01a1ng (fragrance, incense, female/beautiful)"}, {"front": "h\u01b0\u01a1ng (fragrance, incense, female/beautiful)", "id": "1425286599726", "back": "h\u01b0\u01a1ng (fragrance, incense, female/beautiful)  <hr id=answer>  \u9999 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ca68680c-44e7-4672-b3d3-3fd03d183d31/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9999\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9999\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ef6", "id": "1425286701717", "back": "\u4ef6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d1022868-6351-4938-b35e-c0636c00aa15/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ef6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ef6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ki\u1ec7n (a unit of thing)"}, {"front": "ki\u1ec7n (a unit of thing)", "id": "1425286701718", "back": "ki\u1ec7n (a unit of thing)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ef6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d1022868-6351-4938-b35e-c0636c00aa15/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ef6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ef6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7262", "id": "1425286929654", "back": "\u7262 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f4420ae0-f6a4-43dd-ba06-b2077355b1e5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7262\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7262\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  lao (pen/stable/prison, secure, worried)"}, {"front": "lao (pen/stable/prison, secure, worried)", "id": "1425286929655", "back": "lao (pen/stable/prison, secure, worried)  <hr id=answer>  \u7262 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f4420ae0-f6a4-43dd-ba06-b2077355b1e5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7262\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7262\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u534a", "id": "1425287035682", "back": "\u534a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b758a14e-8b70-43d5-bdeb-1392f31036b9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u534a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u534a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00e1n (half/semi, little)"}, {"front": "b\u00e1n (half/semi, little)", "id": "1425287035683", "back": "b\u00e1n (half/semi, little)  <hr id=answer>  \u534a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b758a14e-8b70-43d5-bdeb-1392f31036b9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u534a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u534a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f34", "id": "1425287106295", "back": "\u4f34 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a130ce07-09cb-4816-b634-021faf0f691e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f34\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f34\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ea1n (friend/companion, to accompany)"}, {"front": "b\u1ea1n (friend/companion, to accompany)", "id": "1425287106296", "back": "b\u1ea1n (friend/companion, to accompany)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f34 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a130ce07-09cb-4816-b634-021faf0f691e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f34\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f34\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u544a", "id": "1425406332736", "back": "\u544a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9991a2ea-c4c1-4ed2-a82c-3ac36f429bec/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u544a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u544a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00e1o (tell/announce, accuse)"}, {"front": "c\u00e1o (tell/announce, accuse)", "id": "1425406332738", "back": "c\u00e1o (tell/announce, accuse)  <hr id=answer>  \u544a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9991a2ea-c4c1-4ed2-a82c-3ac36f429bec/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u544a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u544a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7267", "id": "1425406430535", "back": "\u7267 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/81b27704-f637-4418-8f49-f8d05903aeb2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7267\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7267\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ee5c (to shepherd, govern)"}, {"front": "m\u1ee5c (to shepherd, govern)", "id": "1425406430536", "back": "m\u1ee5c (to shepherd, govern)  <hr id=answer>  \u7267 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/81b27704-f637-4418-8f49-f8d05903aeb2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7267\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7267\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9c9c", "id": "1425406551511", "back": "\u9c9c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ddd93baf-73a8-42bf-af38-b40fc5333d80/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9c9c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9c9c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u00ean (rare/uncooked, fresh/delicious/bright)"}, {"front": "ti\u00ean (rare/uncooked, fresh/delicious/bright)", "id": "1425406551512", "back": "ti\u00ean (rare/uncooked, fresh/delicious/bright)  <hr id=answer>  \u9c9c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ddd93baf-73a8-42bf-af38-b40fc5333d80/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9c9c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9c9c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8089", "id": "1425406694741", "back": "\u8089 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7278f309-f659-4e2c-b8f6-915ea3cf1ef7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8089\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8089\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nh\u1ee5c (meat/carnal, soft, slow)"}, {"front": "nh\u1ee5c (meat/carnal, soft, slow)", "id": "1425406694742", "back": "nh\u1ee5c (meat/carnal, soft, slow)  <hr id=answer>  \u8089 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7278f309-f659-4e2c-b8f6-915ea3cf1ef7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8089\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8089\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u80d6", "id": "1425406813520", "back": "\u80d6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/50417580-711d-4e86-83b6-011e0a399f1a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u80d6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u80d6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00e0n (fat, comfortable)"}, {"front": "b\u00e0n (fat, comfortable)", "id": "1425406813521", "back": "b\u00e0n (fat, comfortable)  <hr id=answer>  \u80d6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/50417580-711d-4e86-83b6-011e0a399f1a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u80d6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u80d6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6765", "id": "1425407314573", "back": "\u6765 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5e390707-9f9d-44d5-abbb-41f2c5bd113b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6765\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6765\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  lai (coming/next, do: in place of another verb, about)<div>&nbsp;\u4f86</div>"}, {"front": "lai (coming/next, do: in place of another verb, about)<div>&nbsp;\u4f86</div>", "id": "1425407314574", "back": "lai (coming/next, do: in place of another verb, about)<div>&nbsp;\u4f86</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u6765 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5e390707-9f9d-44d5-abbb-41f2c5bd113b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6765\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6765\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u679c", "id": "1425407498784", "back": "\u679c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/955c3de2-b878-422e-bde1-f1022bfa214f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u679c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u679c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  qu\u1ea3 (fruit, result, complete)"}, {"front": "qu\u1ea3 (fruit, result, complete)", "id": "1425407498785", "back": "qu\u1ea3 (fruit, result, complete)  <hr id=answer>  \u679c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/955c3de2-b878-422e-bde1-f1022bfa214f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u679c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u679c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bfe", "id": "1425407712983", "back": "\u8bfe <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3f6f5db3-ba79-4c05-a703-0b3b6841e1b2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bfe\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bfe\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u00f3a (lesson, tax, supervise, unit of lesson/work)<div>&nbsp;\u8ab2</div>"}, {"front": "kh\u00f3a (lesson, tax, supervise, unit of lesson/work)<div>&nbsp;\u8ab2</div>", "id": "1425407712984", "back": "kh\u00f3a (lesson, tax, supervise, unit of lesson/work)<div>&nbsp;\u8ab2</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8bfe <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3f6f5db3-ba79-4c05-a703-0b3b6841e1b2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bfe\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bfe\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5de2", "id": "1425407797162", "back": "\u5de2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0571edf0-68bd-4b93-b16b-d517c81d9fb9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5de2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5de2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u00e0o (nest, den/hideout)"}, {"front": "s\u00e0o (nest, den/hideout)", "id": "1425407797163", "back": "s\u00e0o (nest, den/hideout)  <hr id=answer>  \u5de2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0571edf0-68bd-4b93-b16b-d517c81d9fb9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5de2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5de2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7231", "id": "1425408006725", "back": "\u7231 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9f237782-b424-4a9f-87be-54c2f2d78a52/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7231\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7231\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u00e1i (love, favor)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u611b</div>"}, {"front": "\u00e1i (love, favor)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u611b</div>", "id": "1425408006726", "back": "\u00e1i (love, favor)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u611b</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u7231 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9f237782-b424-4a9f-87be-54c2f2d78a52/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7231\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7231\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u60f3", "id": "1425408259377", "back": "\u60f3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f32d9ae0-a562-47c4-815b-1849c34ef1dd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u60f3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u60f3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u01b0\u1edfng (think, hope/longing)"}, {"front": "t\u01b0\u1edfng (think, hope/longing)", "id": "1425408259378", "back": "t\u01b0\u1edfng (think, hope/longing)  <hr id=answer>  \u60f3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f32d9ae0-a562-47c4-815b-1849c34ef1dd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u60f3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u60f3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5fc6", "id": "1425408416003", "back": "\u5fc6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/61d22811-aefb-4c6e-8d0f-7ceb2ffd05c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fc6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fc6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u1ee9c (remember/recall)<div>&nbsp;\u61b6</div>"}, {"front": "\u1ee9c (remember/recall)<div>&nbsp;\u61b6</div>", "id": "1425408416004", "back": "\u1ee9c (remember/recall)<div>&nbsp;\u61b6</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5fc6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/61d22811-aefb-4c6e-8d0f-7ceb2ffd05c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fc6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fc6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5fd8", "id": "1425408491053", "back": "\u5fd8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1f020a72-c05a-421e-9487-5e147c1be44c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fd8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fd8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  vong (forget, miss)"}, {"front": "vong (forget, miss)", "id": "1425408491054", "back": "vong (forget, miss)  <hr id=answer>  \u5fd8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1f020a72-c05a-421e-9487-5e147c1be44c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fd8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fd8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5feb", "id": "1425408637490", "back": "\u5feb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6b4bb135-fbe6-45a0-a9d3-bd78294d3f57/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5feb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5feb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kho\u00e1i (quick/hurry, sharp, pleasant/happy, police/sheriff)"}, {"front": "kho\u00e1i (quick/hurry, sharp, pleasant/happy, police/sheriff)", "id": "1425408637491", "back": "kho\u00e1i (quick/hurry, sharp, pleasant/happy, police/sheriff)  <hr id=answer>  \u5feb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6b4bb135-fbe6-45a0-a9d3-bd78294d3f57/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5feb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5feb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5306", "id": "1425408961183", "back": "\u5306 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6b83eeb6-f8c6-415e-88dd-9481b2b538f8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5306\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5306\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00f4ng (hastily)"}, {"front": "th\u00f4ng (hastily)", "id": "1425408961184", "back": "th\u00f4ng (hastily)  <hr id=answer>  \u5306 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6b83eeb6-f8c6-415e-88dd-9481b2b538f8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5306\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5306\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u826f", "id": "1425428614668", "back": "\u826f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cbe1a2b1-f445-48da-8423-a2a3117349e7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u826f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u826f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u01b0\u01a1ng (good, innate, very/truly)"}, {"front": "l\u01b0\u01a1ng (good, innate, very/truly)", "id": "1425428614670", "back": "l\u01b0\u01a1ng (good, innate, very/truly)  <hr id=answer>  \u826f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cbe1a2b1-f445-48da-8423-a2a3117349e7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u826f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u826f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5360", "id": "1425428660935", "back": "\u5360 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1aa3f527-5794-4d83-8a47-b8dfa0c37702/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5360\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5360\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  chi\u00eam, chi\u1ebfm (seize, occupy)"}, {"front": "chi\u00eam, chi\u1ebfm (seize, occupy)", "id": "1425428660936", "back": "chi\u00eam, chi\u1ebfm (seize, occupy)  <hr id=answer>  \u5360 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1aa3f527-5794-4d83-8a47-b8dfa0c37702/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5360\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5360\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u77e2", "id": "1425428740534", "back": "\u77e2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f6a02792-c79a-48fb-84c5-91b44f8fbe12/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u77e2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u77e2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ec9 (arrow, vow, display, straightforward)"}, {"front": "th\u1ec9 (arrow, vow, display, straightforward)", "id": "1425428740535", "back": "th\u1ec9 (arrow, vow, display, straightforward)  <hr id=answer>  \u77e2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f6a02792-c79a-48fb-84c5-91b44f8fbe12/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u77e2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u77e2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u667a", "id": "1425428782910", "back": "\u667a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/289ec661-b2a3-4762-9e18-b63cb1756e35/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u667a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u667a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u00ed (wisdom, wise)"}, {"front": "tr\u00ed (wisdom, wise)", "id": "1425428782911", "back": "tr\u00ed (wisdom, wise)  <hr id=answer>  \u667a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/289ec661-b2a3-4762-9e18-b63cb1756e35/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u667a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u667a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5316", "id": "1425428901915", "back": "\u5316 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5b512777-5f06-454b-adcd-446e689e35f6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5316\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5316\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u00f3a (change/transform, chemistry)"}, {"front": "h\u00f3a (change/transform, chemistry)", "id": "1425428901916", "back": "h\u00f3a (change/transform, chemistry)  <hr id=answer>  \u5316 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5b512777-5f06-454b-adcd-446e689e35f6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5316\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5316\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f59", "id": "1425429009355", "back": "\u4f59 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6b658351-bbc4-4727-84fb-be1909824903/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f59\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f59\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u01b0 (I, last name, the rest/remainder)"}, {"front": "d\u01b0 (I, last name, the rest/remainder)", "id": "1425429009356", "back": "d\u01b0 (I, last name, the rest/remainder)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f59 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6b658351-bbc4-4727-84fb-be1909824903/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f59\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f59\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u592e", "id": "1425429122601", "back": "\u592e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/55761543-3743-466a-97f5-88af6819af44/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u592e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u592e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u01b0\u01a1ng (central, to entreat)"}, {"front": "\u01b0\u01a1ng (central, to entreat)", "id": "1425429122603", "back": "\u01b0\u01a1ng (central, to entreat)  <hr id=answer>  \u592e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/55761543-3743-466a-97f5-88af6819af44/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u592e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u592e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5140", "id": "1425429290460", "back": "\u5140 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/94c6bb5a-8e21-40a1-b73f-0ea7077004a9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5140\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5140\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u1ed9t (high/flat, ignorant-looking, punish by cutting off the feet)"}, {"front": "ng\u1ed9t (high/flat, ignorant-looking, punish by cutting off the feet)", "id": "1425429290461", "back": "ng\u1ed9t (high/flat, ignorant-looking, punish by cutting off the feet)  <hr id=answer>  \u5140 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/94c6bb5a-8e21-40a1-b73f-0ea7077004a9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5140\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5140\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u80a1", "id": "1425429401320", "back": "\u80a1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/57024a83-6ffd-42ae-aa88-e45693883927/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u80a1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u80a1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ed5 (thigh/hip, part of something, a unit)"}, {"front": "c\u1ed5 (thigh/hip, part of something, a unit)", "id": "1425429401321", "back": "c\u1ed5 (thigh/hip, part of something, a unit)  <hr id=answer>  \u80a1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/57024a83-6ffd-42ae-aa88-e45693883927/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u80a1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u80a1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e02", "id": "1425429478105", "back": "\u5e02 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2b0585c4-8f62-46b2-8d0e-9e9d848da5d8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e02\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e02\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ecb (market/marketplace, city, buy/sell)"}, {"front": "th\u1ecb (market/marketplace, city, buy/sell)", "id": "1425429478106", "back": "th\u1ecb (market/marketplace, city, buy/sell)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e02 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2b0585c4-8f62-46b2-8d0e-9e9d848da5d8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e02\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e02\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e3b", "id": "1425429563235", "back": "\u4e3b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ed10cbdc-91c9-4f06-9ee6-ef3ba2071b96/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e3b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e3b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u1ee7 (master, person)"}, {"front": "ch\u1ee7 (master, person)", "id": "1425429563236", "back": "ch\u1ee7 (master, person)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e3b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ed10cbdc-91c9-4f06-9ee6-ef3ba2071b96/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e3b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e3b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u76f8", "id": "1425429952915", "back": "\u76f8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b308e934-6c6e-42c5-ba8d-8ddf71c5e931/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76f8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76f8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u01b0\u01a1ng, t\u01b0\u1edbng (mutual, substance, posture, prime minister - not general)"}, {"front": "t\u01b0\u01a1ng, t\u01b0\u1edbng (mutual, substance, posture, prime minister - not general)", "id": "1425429952916", "back": "t\u01b0\u01a1ng, t\u01b0\u1edbng (mutual, substance, posture, prime minister - not general)  <hr id=answer>  \u76f8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b308e934-6c6e-42c5-ba8d-8ddf71c5e931/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76f8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76f8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e59", "id": "1425430040855", "back": "\u4e59 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2771faa3-649f-4d40-bd25-ded219a1ed66/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e59\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e59\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u1ea5t (second in&nbsp;thi\u00ean can, someone)&nbsp;"}, {"front": "\u1ea5t (second in&nbsp;thi\u00ean can, someone)&nbsp;", "id": "1425430040856", "back": "\u1ea5t (second in&nbsp;thi\u00ean can, someone)&nbsp;  <hr id=answer>  \u4e59 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2771faa3-649f-4d40-bd25-ded219a1ed66/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e59\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e59\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u610f", "id": "1425430123404", "back": "\u610f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f11bbe54-2433-4a78-bee0-6137e5a0e824/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u610f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u610f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u00fd (thought/idea)"}, {"front": "\u00fd (thought/idea)", "id": "1425430123405", "back": "\u00fd (thought/idea)  <hr id=answer>  \u610f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f11bbe54-2433-4a78-bee0-6137e5a0e824/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u610f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u610f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u97f3", "id": "1425430859150", "back": "\u97f3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c3d54871-0804-45b2-9d20-725f3b427d19/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u97f3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u97f3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u00e2m (sound/voice, news)"}, {"front": "\u00e2m (sound/voice, news)", "id": "1425430859151", "back": "\u00e2m (sound/voice, news)  <hr id=answer>  \u97f3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c3d54871-0804-45b2-9d20-725f3b427d19/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u97f3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u97f3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e66", "id": "1425719965332", "back": "\u4e66 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f3994fe2-14d6-4edf-971c-3ce09cbf7182/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e66\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e66\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u01b0 (book, mail/letter/document, write)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u66f8</div>"}, {"front": "th\u01b0 (book, mail/letter/document, write)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u66f8</div>", "id": "1425719965333", "back": "th\u01b0 (book, mail/letter/document, write)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u66f8</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e66 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f3994fe2-14d6-4edf-971c-3ce09cbf7182/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e66\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e66\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6cd5", "id": "1425720138079", "back": "\u6cd5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5159af98-4ef7-44fb-979e-88a5053c0a81/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6cd5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6cd5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u00e1p (French, law, way - Buddhist)"}, {"front": "ph\u00e1p (French, law, way - Buddhist)", "id": "1425720138080", "back": "ph\u00e1p (French, law, way - Buddhist)  <hr id=answer>  \u6cd5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5159af98-4ef7-44fb-979e-88a5053c0a81/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6cd5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6cd5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4fc4", "id": "1425720242773", "back": "\u4fc4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/53df6d7b-814f-42ea-8041-3d71b100025f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4fc4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4fc4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nga (Russian, sudden)"}, {"front": "nga (Russian, sudden)", "id": "1425720242774", "back": "nga (Russian, sudden)  <hr id=answer>  \u4fc4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/53df6d7b-814f-42ea-8041-3d71b100025f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4fc4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4fc4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u73ed", "id": "1425720416273", "back": "\u73ed <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7e0f78d9-3eed-4a45-9563-be2414599d57/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u73ed\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u73ed\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ban (distribute, grade/position/company, shift/scheduled run)"}, {"front": "ban (distribute, grade/position/company, shift/scheduled run)", "id": "1425720416274", "back": "ban (distribute, grade/position/company, shift/scheduled run)  <hr id=answer>  \u73ed <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7e0f78d9-3eed-4a45-9563-be2414599d57/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u73ed\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u73ed\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7259", "id": "1425720523189", "back": "\u7259 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6dabed04-cdd3-4988-8d23-1113a9070212/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7259\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7259\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nha (teeth, ivory, bite)"}, {"front": "nha (teeth, ivory, bite)", "id": "1425720523190", "back": "nha (teeth, ivory, bite)  <hr id=answer>  \u7259 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6dabed04-cdd3-4988-8d23-1113a9070212/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7259\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7259\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5fb7", "id": "1425720656138", "back": "\u5fb7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b8b77624-dc11-4c41-bc13-87cd4989fde8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fb7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fb7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ee9c (ethics/virtues, favor, grateful)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ee9c (ethics/virtues, favor, grateful)", "id": "1425720656139", "back": "\u0111\u1ee9c (ethics/virtues, favor, grateful)  <hr id=answer>  \u5fb7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b8b77624-dc11-4c41-bc13-87cd4989fde8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fb7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fb7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u963f", "id": "1425720876890", "back": "\u963f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f300ca55-9457-4061-be0c-0c1eb3005f49/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u963f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u963f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  a, \u00e1 (word for transliteration or surprise, name prefix, rely on)"}, {"front": "a, \u00e1 (word for transliteration or surprise, name prefix, rely on)", "id": "1425720876891", "back": "a, \u00e1 (word for transliteration or surprise, name prefix, rely on)  <hr id=answer>  \u963f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f300ca55-9457-4061-be0c-0c1eb3005f49/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u963f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u963f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u62c9", "id": "1425720994079", "back": "\u62c9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b00ca699-7474-41ba-94e7-97fb605e7cc2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u62c9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u62c9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1ea1p (pull, lengthen, discharge stool/urine, transcription of \"ra\")"}, {"front": "l\u1ea1p (pull, lengthen, discharge stool/urine, transcription of \"ra\")", "id": "1425720994080", "back": "l\u1ea1p (pull, lengthen, discharge stool/urine, transcription of \"ra\")  <hr id=answer>  \u62c9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b00ca699-7474-41ba-94e7-97fb605e7cc2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u62c9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u62c9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f2f", "id": "1425721081963", "back": "\u4f2f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d63b0a41-ab08-41ac-80e4-0fbda9ab259d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f2f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f2f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00e1 (one's father's elder brother / a rank of the nobility - a count)"}, {"front": "b\u00e1 (one's father's elder brother / a rank of the nobility - a count)", "id": "1425721081964", "back": "b\u00e1 (one's father's elder brother / a rank of the nobility - a count)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f2f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d63b0a41-ab08-41ac-80e4-0fbda9ab259d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f2f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f2f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6742", "id": "1425721237437", "back": "\u6742 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ae5547d7-87b7-4157-858f-8003cd0d7cd7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6742\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6742\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ea1p (mixed, miscellaneous)<div>&nbsp;\u96dc</div>"}, {"front": "t\u1ea1p (mixed, miscellaneous)<div>&nbsp;\u96dc</div>", "id": "1425721237438", "back": "t\u1ea1p (mixed, miscellaneous)<div>&nbsp;\u96dc</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u6742 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ae5547d7-87b7-4157-858f-8003cd0d7cd7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6742\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6742\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5fd7", "id": "1425721311778", "back": "\u5fd7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/21c2eeea-7124-4888-bb0a-836ee2c4c986/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fd7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fd7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u00ed (ambition, record, write/remember)"}, {"front": "ch\u00ed (ambition, record, write/remember)", "id": "1425721311779", "back": "ch\u00ed (ambition, record, write/remember)  <hr id=answer>  \u5fd7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/21c2eeea-7124-4888-bb0a-836ee2c4c986/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fd7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fd7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5229", "id": "1425885813003", "back": "\u5229 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/01508a2c-2c57-44de-9175-cd26f65dae5b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5229\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5229\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1ee3i (profit/benefit, sharp/quick)"}, {"front": "l\u1ee3i (profit/benefit, sharp/quick)", "id": "1425885813004", "back": "l\u1ee3i (profit/benefit, sharp/quick)  <hr id=answer>  \u5229 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/01508a2c-2c57-44de-9175-cd26f65dae5b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5229\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5229\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6559", "id": "1426325273233", "back": "\u6559 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ec306d5d-b7ec-4ab7-8712-fd0f0c27311a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6559\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6559\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u00e1o (religion, instruct/order, education)"}, {"front": "gi\u00e1o (religion, instruct/order, education)", "id": "1426325273234", "back": "gi\u00e1o (religion, instruct/order, education)  <hr id=answer>  \u6559 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ec306d5d-b7ec-4ab7-8712-fd0f0c27311a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6559\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6559\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5ba4", "id": "1426325520797", "back": "\u5ba4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dbe67362-9144-4a04-97ae-91b05d4371f5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5ba4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5ba4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ea5t (room/bureau, apartment/home, wife)"}, {"front": "th\u1ea5t (room/bureau, apartment/home, wife)", "id": "1426325520798", "back": "th\u1ea5t (room/bureau, apartment/home, wife)  <hr id=answer>  \u5ba4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dbe67362-9144-4a04-97ae-91b05d4371f5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5ba4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5ba4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u524d", "id": "1426325676767", "back": "\u524d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1ad2acfa-d477-4768-b1bc-35c82f79a535/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u524d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u524d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u1ec1n (front, forward, future)"}, {"front": "ti\u1ec1n (front, forward, future)", "id": "1426325676768", "back": "ti\u1ec1n (front, forward, future)  <hr id=answer>  \u524d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1ad2acfa-d477-4768-b1bc-35c82f79a535/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u524d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u524d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c31", "id": "1426325908409", "back": "\u5c31 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b7ad0857-64da-44e1-a699-a3af07eb7c04/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c31\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c31\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ef1u (right at/exactly, even if/although, assume/achieve)"}, {"front": "t\u1ef1u (right at/exactly, even if/although, assume/achieve)", "id": "1426325908410", "back": "t\u1ef1u (right at/exactly, even if/although, assume/achieve)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c31 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b7ad0857-64da-44e1-a699-a3af07eb7c04/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c31\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c31\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65c1", "id": "1426326244506", "back": "\u65c1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6daa9f81-1c10-4fec-8654-4daf31ec8b96/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65c1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65c1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00e0ng (side, not straight)"}, {"front": "b\u00e0ng (side, not straight)", "id": "1426326244507", "back": "b\u00e0ng (side, not straight)  <hr id=answer>  \u65c1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6daa9f81-1c10-4fec-8654-4daf31ec8b96/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65c1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65c1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5802", "id": "1426326454708", "back": "\u5802 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0bde96d2-7fbb-4a32-9f80-f311bef755c6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5802\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5802\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u01b0\u1eddng (hall, office/business place, another's mother, same paternal grandfather, venerable)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u01b0\u1eddng (hall, office/business place, another's mother, same paternal grandfather, venerable)", "id": "1426326454709", "back": "\u0111\u01b0\u1eddng (hall, office/business place, another's mother, same paternal grandfather, venerable)  <hr id=answer>  \u5802 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0bde96d2-7fbb-4a32-9f80-f311bef755c6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5802\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5802\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8def", "id": "1426326677475", "back": "\u8def <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bc99baf0-7055-4dfe-bd58-53db2aafb475/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8def\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8def\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1ed9 (road/way, side/direction, kind/sort)"}, {"front": "l\u1ed9 (road/way, side/direction, kind/sort)", "id": "1426326677476", "back": "l\u1ed9 (road/way, side/direction, kind/sort)  <hr id=answer>  \u8def <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bc99baf0-7055-4dfe-bd58-53db2aafb475/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8def\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8def\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6253", "id": "1426326822100", "back": "\u6253 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a1c9a80d-80a8-4cf5-93a8-939fefeb278b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6253\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6253\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ea3 (strike, do/make/etc., from)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ea3 (strike, do/make/etc., from)", "id": "1426326822101", "back": "\u0111\u1ea3 (strike, do/make/etc., from)  <hr id=answer>  \u6253 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a1c9a80d-80a8-4cf5-93a8-939fefeb278b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6253\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6253\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9645", "id": "1426326962897", "back": "\u9645 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cc471105-c6cf-452d-986a-8510b453fc24/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9645\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9645\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ebf (border, inter-/among/between, meet/fortune)"}, {"front": "t\u1ebf (border, inter-/among/between, meet/fortune)", "id": "1426326962898", "back": "t\u1ebf (border, inter-/among/between, meet/fortune)  <hr id=answer>  \u9645 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cc471105-c6cf-452d-986a-8510b453fc24/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9645\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9645\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5395", "id": "1426327060983", "back": "\u5395 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/102ca49d-ecc7-4b05-933e-a7411c9d1e5f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5395\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5395\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u00ed (lavatory/latrine)&nbsp;<div>tr\u1eafc (mingle with)</div><div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5ec1</div>"}, {"front": "x\u00ed (lavatory/latrine)&nbsp;<div>tr\u1eafc (mingle with)</div><div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5ec1</div>", "id": "1426327060984", "back": "x\u00ed (lavatory/latrine)&nbsp;<div>tr\u1eafc (mingle with)</div><div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u5ec1</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5395 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/102ca49d-ecc7-4b05-933e-a7411c9d1e5f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5395\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5395\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6240", "id": "1426327286731", "back": "\u6240 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2489ad64-9c45-4b13-8381-d30a12b96eef/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6240\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6240\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u1edf (place/location, unit for room/building, which/those that)"}, {"front": "s\u1edf (place/location, unit for room/building, which/those that)", "id": "1426327286732", "back": "s\u1edf (place/location, unit for room/building, which/those that)  <hr id=answer>  \u6240 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2489ad64-9c45-4b13-8381-d30a12b96eef/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6240\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6240\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9762", "id": "1426327453475", "back": "\u9762 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cfe91d83-2d5a-43ba-874e-42772db176de/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9762\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9762\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  di\u1ec7n (face, surface/side, situation, unit for something flat)<div>mi\u1ebfn (noodle, flour/dough)</div>"}, {"front": "di\u1ec7n (face, surface/side, situation, unit for something flat)<div>mi\u1ebfn (noodle, flour/dough)</div>", "id": "1426327453476", "back": "di\u1ec7n (face, surface/side, situation, unit for something flat)<div>mi\u1ebfn (noodle, flour/dough)</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u9762 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cfe91d83-2d5a-43ba-874e-42772db176de/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9762\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9762\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e97", "id": "1426584024563", "back": "\u5e97 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cf097cb2-990b-4b65-b1ad-61e838dfe9b3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e97\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e97\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111i\u1ebfm (shop/store, inn/hotel, commercial establishment)"}, {"front": "\u0111i\u1ebfm (shop/store, inn/hotel, commercial establishment)", "id": "1426584024564", "back": "\u0111i\u1ebfm (shop/store, inn/hotel, commercial establishment)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e97 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cf097cb2-990b-4b65-b1ad-61e838dfe9b3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e97\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e97\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5546", "id": "1426584192862", "back": "\u5546 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0bf650a7-03ce-4671-8f9a-e95701180689/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5546\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5546\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u01b0\u01a1ng (trade, discuss/exchange, math division)"}, {"front": "th\u01b0\u01a1ng (trade, discuss/exchange, math division)", "id": "1426584192863", "back": "th\u01b0\u01a1ng (trade, discuss/exchange, math division)  <hr id=answer>  \u5546 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0bf650a7-03ce-4671-8f9a-e95701180689/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5546\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5546\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c1a", "id": "1426584432075", "back": "\u5c1a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c557da08-ad34-4ced-899a-c1c1faf1e42b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c1a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c1a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u01b0\u1ee3ng (uphold/honor/look after, yet/still, show off)"}, {"front": "th\u01b0\u1ee3ng (uphold/honor/look after, yet/still, show off)", "id": "1426584432076", "back": "th\u01b0\u1ee3ng (uphold/honor/look after, yet/still, show off)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c1a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c557da08-ad34-4ced-899a-c1c1faf1e42b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c1a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c1a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5219", "id": "1426584716840", "back": "\u5219 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e17ad97f-3eac-4c81-997e-f37ffb1094c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5219\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5219\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1eafc (law/rule, unit for writings, imitate/follow, if..then)"}, {"front": "t\u1eafc (law/rule, unit for writings, imitate/follow, if..then)", "id": "1426584716841", "back": "t\u1eafc (law/rule, unit for writings, imitate/follow, if..then)  <hr id=answer>  \u5219 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e17ad97f-3eac-4c81-997e-f37ffb1094c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5219\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5219\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c24", "id": "1426584849852", "back": "\u5c24 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0511902a-2320-4e97-b6ae-ca70a9643b7c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c24\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c24\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u01b0u (outstanding/special, error, feel bitter against/blame)&nbsp;"}, {"front": "v\u01b0u (outstanding/special, error, feel bitter against/blame)&nbsp;", "id": "1426584849853", "back": "v\u01b0u (outstanding/special, error, feel bitter against/blame)&nbsp;  <hr id=answer>  \u5c24 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0511902a-2320-4e97-b6ae-ca70a9643b7c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c24\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c24\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u81f3", "id": "1426584991075", "back": "\u81f3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d3ca6e78-8343-44bc-aee3-8d667b9fd5dc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u81f3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u81f3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u00ed (reach/arrive at, extremely/most)"}, {"front": "ch\u00ed (reach/arrive at, extremely/most)", "id": "1426584991076", "back": "ch\u00ed (reach/arrive at, extremely/most)  <hr id=answer>  \u81f3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d3ca6e78-8343-44bc-aee3-8d667b9fd5dc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u81f3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u81f3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7ae0", "id": "1428014850962", "back": "\u7ae0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c576c5a1-d42c-436a-9cce-cc4c2d9ec65f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ae0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ae0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u01b0\u01a1ng (chapter, last name, emblem/seal)"}, {"front": "ch\u01b0\u01a1ng (chapter, last name, emblem/seal)", "id": "1428014850963", "back": "ch\u01b0\u01a1ng (chapter, last name, emblem/seal)  <hr id=answer>  \u7ae0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c576c5a1-d42c-436a-9cce-cc4c2d9ec65f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ae0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ae0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u559d", "id": "1428014958584", "back": "\u559d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/baf667a6-da57-4d67-a20e-738f8ea16290/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u559d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u559d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u00e1t (drink, shout)"}, {"front": "h\u00e1t (drink, shout)", "id": "1428014958585", "back": "h\u00e1t (drink, shout)  <hr id=answer>  \u559d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/baf667a6-da57-4d67-a20e-738f8ea16290/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u559d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u559d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5496", "id": "1428015039250", "back": "\u5496 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/91fa0faa-2cea-4820-82ca-1a16736a8748/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5496\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5496\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u00e0/ca (c\u00e0 ph\u00ea)"}, {"front": "gi\u00e0/ca (c\u00e0 ph\u00ea)", "id": "1428015039251", "back": "gi\u00e0/ca (c\u00e0 ph\u00ea)  <hr id=answer>  \u5496 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/91fa0faa-2cea-4820-82ca-1a16736a8748/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5496\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5496\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5561", "id": "1428015103207", "back": "\u5561 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b829a1bd-6ff9-408e-a91a-3af92027941d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5561\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5561\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u00ea (in coffee, morphine)"}, {"front": "ph\u00ea (in coffee, morphine)", "id": "1428015103208", "back": "ph\u00ea (in coffee, morphine)  <hr id=answer>  \u5561 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b829a1bd-6ff9-408e-a91a-3af92027941d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5561\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5561\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u514b", "id": "1428015248703", "back": "\u514b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/461017cb-28b3-4972-a339-b66d2ff5e92a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u514b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u514b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u1eafc (win/overcome, gram, limit)"}, {"front": "kh\u1eafc (win/overcome, gram, limit)", "id": "1428015248704", "back": "kh\u1eafc (win/overcome, gram, limit)  <hr id=answer>  \u514b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/461017cb-28b3-4972-a339-b66d2ff5e92a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u514b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u514b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u739b", "id": "1428015394889", "back": "\u739b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/730f72fd-0ed8-401f-80f9-d8df15e0642b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u739b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u739b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u00e3 (m\u00e3 n\u00e3o)"}, {"front": "m\u00e3 (m\u00e3 n\u00e3o)", "id": "1428015394890", "back": "m\u00e3 (m\u00e3 n\u00e3o)  <hr id=answer>  \u739b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/730f72fd-0ed8-401f-80f9-d8df15e0642b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u739b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u739b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e3d", "id": "1428015563847", "back": "\u4e3d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/875e789a-f8e1-4201-b888-6627b2ffb3d9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e3d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e3d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1ec7 (beautiful, dual) , li (Cao Li)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9e97</div>"}, {"front": "l\u1ec7 (beautiful, dual) , li (Cao Li)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9e97</div>", "id": "1428015563849", "back": "l\u1ec7 (beautiful, dual) , li (Cao Li)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9e97</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e3d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/875e789a-f8e1-4201-b888-6627b2ffb3d9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e3d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e3d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9ea6", "id": "1428015645864", "back": "\u9ea6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ed5deb61-8df1-4cda-809e-60819c6fb00f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9ea6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9ea6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ea1ch (wheat/barley/oat)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9ea5</div>"}, {"front": "m\u1ea1ch (wheat/barley/oat)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9ea5</div>", "id": "1428015645865", "back": "m\u1ea1ch (wheat/barley/oat)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9ea5</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u9ea6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ed5deb61-8df1-4cda-809e-60819c6fb00f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9ea6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9ea6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e24", "id": "1428794723730", "back": "\u4e24 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6b9767fb-ceba-439b-83ac-76198f95c696/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e24\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e24\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u01b0\u1ee1ng, l\u01b0\u1ee3ng&nbsp;(two/pair, both/either, unit of weight)<div><br /><div>&nbsp;\u5169</div></div>"}, {"front": "l\u01b0\u1ee1ng, l\u01b0\u1ee3ng&nbsp;(two/pair, both/either, unit of weight)<div><br /><div>&nbsp;\u5169</div></div>", "id": "1428794723731", "back": "l\u01b0\u1ee1ng, l\u01b0\u1ee3ng&nbsp;(two/pair, both/either, unit of weight)<div><br /><div>&nbsp;\u5169</div></div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e24 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6b9767fb-ceba-439b-83ac-76198f95c696/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e24\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e24\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u66f7", "id": "1428794906304", "back": "\u66f7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/adc6ec39-5cc9-40a3-a723-62f0f2b34e9d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66f7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66f7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ea1t (what / why not / how)"}, {"front": "h\u1ea1t (what / why not / how)", "id": "1428794906305", "back": "h\u1ea1t (what / why not / how)  <hr id=answer>  \u66f7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/adc6ec39-5cc9-40a3-a723-62f0f2b34e9d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66f7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66f7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5230", "id": "1428794994085", "back": "\u5230 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b6c63ac0-2e29-41d3-88f0-aa38cc6c1b35/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5230\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5230\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00e1o (reach/arrive)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00e1o (reach/arrive)", "id": "1428794994086", "back": "\u0111\u00e1o (reach/arrive)  <hr id=answer>  \u5230 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b6c63ac0-2e29-41d3-88f0-aa38cc6c1b35/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5230\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5230\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u975e", "id": "1428795143068", "back": "\u975e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dfd3faa2-e9bc-4e23-b60f-1ee048dd8fd5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u975e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u975e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  phi (not/non, evil/wrong, object/censure, Africa)"}, {"front": "phi (not/non, evil/wrong, object/censure, Africa)", "id": "1428795143069", "back": "phi (not/non, evil/wrong, object/censure, Africa)  <hr id=answer>  \u975e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dfd3faa2-e9bc-4e23-b60f-1ee048dd8fd5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u975e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u975e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u949f", "id": "1428795428160", "back": "\u949f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dcc9a7c3-f574-4aea-9e49-27d234eecffb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u949f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u949f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  chung (bell, clock, time in hour/min)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9418</div>"}, {"front": "chung (bell, clock, time in hour/min)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9418</div>", "id": "1428795428161", "back": "chung (bell, clock, time in hour/min)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9418</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u949f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dcc9a7c3-f574-4aea-9e49-27d234eecffb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u949f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u949f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5dee", "id": "1428795733262", "back": "\u5dee <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/348dc788-508e-4522-af01-97a31a3ddeef/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5dee\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5dee\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  sai (error/mistake, difference/short of, order/orderly)&nbsp;"}, {"front": "sai (error/mistake, difference/short of, order/orderly)&nbsp;", "id": "1428795733263", "back": "sai (error/mistake, difference/short of, order/orderly)&nbsp;  <hr id=answer>  \u5dee <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/348dc788-508e-4522-af01-97a31a3ddeef/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5dee\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5dee\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8fd8", "id": "1428795970011", "back": "\u8fd8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3c523629-76c4-45e7-8ba0-7df8887719db/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fd8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fd8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ho\u00e0n (return/repay, had better, still)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;&nbsp;\u9084</div>"}, {"front": "ho\u00e0n (return/repay, had better, still)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;&nbsp;\u9084</div>", "id": "1428795970012", "back": "ho\u00e0n (return/repay, had better, still)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;&nbsp;\u9084</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8fd8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3c523629-76c4-45e7-8ba0-7df8887719db/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fd8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fd8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u523b", "id": "1428796213280", "back": "\u523b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b0c65e68-a5ec-407f-b437-5b2ad65398f2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u523b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u523b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u1eafc (carve/engrave/cut, quarter of hour/moment, cruel/harsh)"}, {"front": "kh\u1eafc (carve/engrave/cut, quarter of hour/moment, cruel/harsh)", "id": "1428796213281", "back": "kh\u1eafc (carve/engrave/cut, quarter of hour/moment, cruel/harsh)  <hr id=answer>  \u523b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b0c65e68-a5ec-407f-b437-5b2ad65398f2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u523b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u523b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u82e6", "id": "1430560370113", "back": "\u82e6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ad88edb6-695d-4208-bb4b-c5cff3b98bf2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82e6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82e6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u1ed5 (bitter)"}, {"front": "kh\u1ed5 (bitter)", "id": "1430560370114", "back": "kh\u1ed5 (bitter)  <hr id=answer>  \u82e6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ad88edb6-695d-4208-bb4b-c5cff3b98bf2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82e6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82e6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9ad8", "id": "1430560416429", "back": "\u9ad8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b448cb0f-bfa5-4ec7-9aa6-c68a62addd44/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9ad8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9ad8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  cao (tall/high/lofty)"}, {"front": "cao (tall/high/lofty)", "id": "1430560416430", "back": "cao (tall/high/lofty)  <hr id=answer>  \u9ad8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b448cb0f-bfa5-4ec7-9aa6-c68a62addd44/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9ad8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9ad8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u957f", "id": "1430560553831", "back": "\u957f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ae4f753d-aa05-4905-90af-3c62cbe78295/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u957f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u957f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u01b0\u1eddng (long), tr\u01b0\u1edfng (senior/old/chief, increase/grow)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9577</div>"}, {"front": "tr\u01b0\u1eddng (long), tr\u01b0\u1edfng (senior/old/chief, increase/grow)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9577</div>", "id": "1430560553832", "back": "tr\u01b0\u1eddng (long), tr\u01b0\u1edfng (senior/old/chief, increase/grow)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9577</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u957f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ae4f753d-aa05-4905-90af-3c62cbe78295/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u957f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u957f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u76f4", "id": "1430560664508", "back": "\u76f4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9a421452-9423-4a97-b207-5ddee0ffeb84/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76f4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76f4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u1ef1c (straight, just/only)"}, {"front": "tr\u1ef1c (straight, just/only)", "id": "1430560664509", "back": "tr\u1ef1c (straight, just/only)  <hr id=answer>  \u76f4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9a421452-9423-4a97-b207-5ddee0ffeb84/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76f4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76f4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9001", "id": "1430560782777", "back": "\u9001 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/02d50ae9-71c8-43f7-ace5-0c74741e26e4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9001\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9001\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ed1ng (send/deliver, send off/see off)"}, {"front": "t\u1ed1ng (send/deliver, send off/see off)", "id": "1430560782778", "back": "t\u1ed1ng (send/deliver, send off/see off)  <hr id=answer>  \u9001 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/02d50ae9-71c8-43f7-ace5-0c74741e26e4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9001\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9001\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f5b", "id": "1430560837193", "back": "\u4f5b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/da4c2db3-6cd9-4858-8ef8-eeba6140e420/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f5b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f5b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u1eadt (buddha)"}, {"front": "ph\u1eadt (buddha)", "id": "1430560837194", "back": "ph\u1eadt (buddha)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f5b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/da4c2db3-6cd9-4858-8ef8-eeba6140e420/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f5b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f5b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u96f6", "id": "1430560968419", "back": "\u96f6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/94b46bae-0f1e-4336-8030-fbd6a683dbd0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u96f6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u96f6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  linh (zero, light rain)"}, {"front": "linh (zero, light rain)", "id": "1430560968420", "back": "linh (zero, light rain)  <hr id=answer>  \u96f6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/94b46bae-0f1e-4336-8030-fbd6a683dbd0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u96f6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u96f6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ee4", "id": "1431078018863", "back": "\u4ee4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/de460399-7f0c-424d-a34c-aa801aa891a2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ee4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ee4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1ec7nh (command/order, good/nice), linh"}, {"front": "l\u1ec7nh (command/order, good/nice), linh", "id": "1431078018864", "back": "l\u1ec7nh (command/order, good/nice), linh  <hr id=answer>  \u4ee4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/de460399-7f0c-424d-a34c-aa801aa891a2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ee4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ee4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8fde", "id": "1431078163267", "back": "\u8fde <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3455358c-e320-4901-99ff-ea47072d1911/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fde\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fde\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  li\u00ean (connect/continue, company of soldiers)<div>&nbsp;\u9023</div>"}, {"front": "li\u00ean (connect/continue, company of soldiers)<div>&nbsp;\u9023</div>", "id": "1431078163268", "back": "li\u00ean (connect/continue, company of soldiers)<div>&nbsp;\u9023</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8fde <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3455358c-e320-4901-99ff-ea47072d1911/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fde\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fde\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5468", "id": "1431078265286", "back": "\u5468 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/54da807b-9434-494f-84c4-8d626c9d1977/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5468\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5468\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  chu (Zhou dynasty, complete, all around/circle, to aid/provide)"}, {"front": "chu (Zhou dynasty, complete, all around/circle, to aid/provide)", "id": "1431078265288", "back": "chu (Zhou dynasty, complete, all around/circle, to aid/provide)  <hr id=answer>  \u5468 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/54da807b-9434-494f-84c4-8d626c9d1977/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5468\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5468\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6377", "id": "1431078338748", "back": "\u6377 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/02f67a7b-aee5-4931-85e0-0e38422a4e57/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6377\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6377\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u1ec7p (win/triumph, swift/quick, spoil of war)"}, {"front": "ti\u1ec7p (win/triumph, swift/quick, spoil of war)", "id": "1431078338749", "back": "ti\u1ec7p (win/triumph, swift/quick, spoil of war)  <hr id=answer>  \u6377 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/02f67a7b-aee5-4931-85e0-0e38422a4e57/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6377\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6377\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5f3a", "id": "1431078430669", "back": "\u5f3a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7f151a45-c6d9-413e-bd26-6eb5d6cebe3c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f3a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f3a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u01b0\u1eddng (strong), c\u01b0\u1ee1ng (force)<div>&nbsp;\u5f37</div>"}, {"front": "c\u01b0\u1eddng (strong), c\u01b0\u1ee1ng (force)<div>&nbsp;\u5f37</div>", "id": "1431078430670", "back": "c\u01b0\u1eddng (strong), c\u01b0\u1ee1ng (force)<div>&nbsp;\u5f37</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5f3a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/7f151a45-c6d9-413e-bd26-6eb5d6cebe3c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f3a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f3a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8fc7", "id": "1431078615164", "back": "\u8fc7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dea1f24e-d932-4107-b121-51dcc53af665/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fc7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fc7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  qu\u00e1, qua (pass, verbal suffix of past tense, too/excessively)<div><br /></div><div>\u904e</div>"}, {"front": "qu\u00e1, qua (pass, verbal suffix of past tense, too/excessively)<div><br /></div><div>\u904e</div>", "id": "1431078615165", "back": "qu\u00e1, qua (pass, verbal suffix of past tense, too/excessively)<div><br /></div><div>\u904e</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8fc7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dea1f24e-d932-4107-b121-51dcc53af665/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fc7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fc7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5403", "id": "1431078726797", "back": "\u5403 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fd3c7d27-6e9c-48c5-bb32-a9d91542fe55/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5403\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5403\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1eadt (eat/drink, sustain/suffer)"}, {"front": "c\u1eadt (eat/drink, sustain/suffer)", "id": "1431078726798", "back": "c\u1eadt (eat/drink, sustain/suffer)  <hr id=answer>  \u5403 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/fd3c7d27-6e9c-48c5-bb32-a9d91542fe55/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5403\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5403\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u996d", "id": "1431078796383", "back": "\u996d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a23ecb80-12b2-4d0b-87cf-245cedb0c076/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u996d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u996d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  <div>ph\u1ea1n (cooked rice, feed)</div>"}, {"front": "<div>ph\u1ea1n (cooked rice, feed)</div>", "id": "1431078796384", "back": "<div>ph\u1ea1n (cooked rice, feed)</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u996d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a23ecb80-12b2-4d0b-87cf-245cedb0c076/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u996d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u996d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u665a", "id": "1431078873901", "back": "\u665a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6fa99e2a-41a3-468b-8876-6e570588c107/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u665a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u665a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u00e3n (sunset/evening/late)"}, {"front": "v\u00e3n (sunset/evening/late)", "id": "1431078873902", "back": "v\u00e3n (sunset/evening/late)  <hr id=answer>  \u665a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6fa99e2a-41a3-468b-8876-6e570588c107/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u665a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u665a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e8a", "id": "1431078949019", "back": "\u5e8a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bbae0d32-12b1-4758-b611-e8ef749edf53/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e8a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e8a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u00e0ng (bed, numeral for blanket)"}, {"front": "s\u00e0ng (bed, numeral for blanket)", "id": "1431078949020", "back": "s\u00e0ng (bed, numeral for blanket)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e8a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bbae0d32-12b1-4758-b611-e8ef749edf53/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e8a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e8a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6fa1", "id": "1431078982421", "back": "\u6fa1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3e48141d-f9bb-4792-a9bf-422c3b9f48b4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6fa1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6fa1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00e1o, th\u00e1o (wash/bathe)"}, {"front": "t\u00e1o, th\u00e1o (wash/bathe)", "id": "1431078982422", "back": "t\u00e1o, th\u00e1o (wash/bathe)  <hr id=answer>  \u6fa1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3e48141d-f9bb-4792-a9bf-422c3b9f48b4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6fa1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6fa1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6d17", "id": "1431079055040", "back": "\u6d17 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f56d2a65-2b95-4494-8452-b0ce5bbfefc6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d17\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d17\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ea9y (wash/rinse/cleanse)"}, {"front": "t\u1ea9y (wash/rinse/cleanse)", "id": "1431079055041", "back": "t\u1ea9y (wash/rinse/cleanse)  <hr id=answer>  \u6d17 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f56d2a65-2b95-4494-8452-b0ce5bbfefc6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d17\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d17\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6837", "id": "1431079109271", "back": "\u6837 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1b7f2b1d-eaa1-4a66-83f1-39ee807b0a12/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6837\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6837\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u1ea1ng (appearance/style/pattern)"}, {"front": "d\u1ea1ng (appearance/style/pattern)", "id": "1431079109272", "back": "d\u1ea1ng (appearance/style/pattern)  <hr id=answer>  \u6837 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1b7f2b1d-eaa1-4a66-83f1-39ee807b0a12/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6837\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6837\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u600e", "id": "1431079150548", "back": "\u600e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e56a044c-5f41-45e9-91bd-018bd6405f6c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u600e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u600e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u1ea9m (how/why/what)"}, {"front": "ch\u1ea9m (how/why/what)", "id": "1431079150549", "back": "ch\u1ea9m (how/why/what)  <hr id=answer>  \u600e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e56a044c-5f41-45e9-91bd-018bd6405f6c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u600e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u600e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e38", "id": "1431079219486", "back": "\u5e38 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/541f7eee-00e1-4e36-aea3-eef92e989400/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e38\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e38\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u01b0\u1eddng (common, frequent/regular)"}, {"front": "th\u01b0\u1eddng (common, frequent/regular)", "id": "1431079219487", "back": "th\u01b0\u1eddng (common, frequent/regular)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e38 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/541f7eee-00e1-4e36-aea3-eef92e989400/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e38\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e38\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u98ce", "id": "1431079343091", "back": "\u98ce <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9f79ea69-2813-4e83-9355-afde9a60e8d5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u98ce\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u98ce\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  phong (wind, scene, manner/customs)<div>\u98a8</div>"}, {"front": "phong (wind, scene, manner/customs)<div>\u98a8</div>", "id": "1431079343092", "back": "phong (wind, scene, manner/customs)<div>\u98a8</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u98ce <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9f79ea69-2813-4e83-9355-afde9a60e8d5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u98ce\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u98ce\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u51b7", "id": "1431079416211", "back": "\u51b7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2ca5ebb5-3f71-43c4-a321-f7ae40fb73fa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51b7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51b7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u00e3nh (cold, hidden/unknown)"}, {"front": "l\u00e3nh (cold, hidden/unknown)", "id": "1431079416212", "back": "l\u00e3nh (cold, hidden/unknown)  <hr id=answer>  \u51b7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2ca5ebb5-3f71-43c4-a321-f7ae40fb73fa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51b7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51b7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9634", "id": "1431079525821", "back": "\u9634 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/70d09584-5892-4e96-9b32-97ddad29d914/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9634\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9634\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u00e2m (negative/female/dark side)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9670</div>"}, {"front": "\u00e2m (negative/female/dark side)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9670</div>", "id": "1431079525822", "back": "\u00e2m (negative/female/dark side)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9670</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u9634 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/70d09584-5892-4e96-9b32-97ddad29d914/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9634\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9634\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u70ed", "id": "1431079576558", "back": "\u70ed <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c8bfbacf-2f75-472a-b159-8ebd8eb79993/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u70ed\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u70ed\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nhi\u1ec7t (heat)<div>\u71b1</div>"}, {"front": "nhi\u1ec7t (heat)<div>\u71b1</div>", "id": "1431079576559", "back": "nhi\u1ec7t (heat)<div>\u71b1</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u70ed <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c8bfbacf-2f75-472a-b159-8ebd8eb79993/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u70ed\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u70ed\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u554a", "id": "1431079645588", "back": "\u554a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8462356f-4e20-4c1e-af46-01236099ccb3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u554a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u554a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  a (exclamatory particle)"}, {"front": "a (exclamatory particle)", "id": "1431079645589", "back": "a (exclamatory particle)  <hr id=answer>  \u554a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8462356f-4e20-4c1e-af46-01236099ccb3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u554a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u554a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u51ac", "id": "1431079679548", "back": "\u51ac <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/45804bc4-5f0d-422b-bb81-545f1ef524fb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51ac\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51ac\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00f4ng (winter)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00f4ng (winter)", "id": "1431079679549", "back": "\u0111\u00f4ng (winter)  <hr id=answer>  \u51ac <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/45804bc4-5f0d-422b-bb81-545f1ef524fb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51ac\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51ac\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8f83", "id": "1431079778584", "back": "\u8f83 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bb4a7f11-cb67-49c7-bbfc-1dacb4285d3c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8f83\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8f83\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u00e1c (relatively/more or less, clear/obvious, compare)<div>&nbsp;\u8f03</div>"}, {"front": "gi\u00e1c (relatively/more or less, clear/obvious, compare)<div>&nbsp;\u8f03</div>", "id": "1431079778585", "back": "gi\u00e1c (relatively/more or less, clear/obvious, compare)<div>&nbsp;\u8f03</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8f83 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bb4a7f11-cb67-49c7-bbfc-1dacb4285d3c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8f83\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8f83\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6bd4", "id": "1431079900499", "back": "\u6bd4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/273ff9a7-ec73-4598-a1e3-150580cf24f5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bd4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bd4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ec9, b\u00ed, b\u00ec, t\u1ec9 (compare, near/side by side, ratio)"}, {"front": "b\u1ec9, b\u00ed, b\u00ec, t\u1ec9 (compare, near/side by side, ratio)", "id": "1431079900500", "back": "b\u1ec9, b\u00ed, b\u00ec, t\u1ec9 (compare, near/side by side, ratio)  <hr id=answer>  \u6bd4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/273ff9a7-ec73-4598-a1e3-150580cf24f5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bd4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bd4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6625", "id": "1431079992945", "back": "\u6625 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ef78b99f-a7aa-4fda-85ba-5333c940ede9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6625\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6625\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  xu\u00e2n (spring)"}, {"front": "xu\u00e2n (spring)", "id": "1431079992946", "back": "xu\u00e2n (spring)  <hr id=answer>  \u6625 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ef78b99f-a7aa-4fda-85ba-5333c940ede9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6625\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6625\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u590f", "id": "1431080091113", "back": "\u590f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/590ee12c-e934-46cf-a804-0db995e754fa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u590f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u590f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ea1 (summer, Cathay - ancient China)"}, {"front": "h\u1ea1 (summer, Cathay - ancient China)", "id": "1431080091114", "back": "h\u1ea1 (summer, Cathay - ancient China)  <hr id=answer>  \u590f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/590ee12c-e934-46cf-a804-0db995e754fa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u590f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u590f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u51c9", "id": "1431080908000", "back": "\u51c9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1372f4a4-fb35-498b-bb01-14f7914edeac/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51c9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51c9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u01b0\u01a1ng, l\u01b0\u1ee3ng (cool/cold, sad/discouraged)"}, {"front": "l\u01b0\u01a1ng, l\u01b0\u1ee3ng (cool/cold, sad/discouraged)", "id": "1431080908001", "back": "l\u01b0\u01a1ng, l\u01b0\u1ee3ng (cool/cold, sad/discouraged)  <hr id=answer>  \u51c9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1372f4a4-fb35-498b-bb01-14f7914edeac/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51c9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51c9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6700", "id": "1431080971959", "back": "\u6700 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/46970aea-7e7f-43bd-a559-4dcf8c3dd204/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6700\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6700\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ed1i (supreme, very/most/extreme)"}, {"front": "t\u1ed1i (supreme, very/most/extreme)", "id": "1431080971960", "back": "t\u1ed1i (supreme, very/most/extreme)  <hr id=answer>  \u6700 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/46970aea-7e7f-43bd-a559-4dcf8c3dd204/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6700\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6700\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u514d", "id": "1432683358560", "back": "\u514d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8a1f5c6f-6074-4e51-85ac-be66fd4bfc13/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u514d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u514d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  mi\u1ec5n (free/exempt, dismiss, escape)"}, {"front": "mi\u1ec5n (free/exempt, dismiss, escape)", "id": "1432683358561", "back": "mi\u1ec5n (free/exempt, dismiss, escape)  <hr id=answer>  \u514d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8a1f5c6f-6074-4e51-85ac-be66fd4bfc13/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u514d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u514d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6267", "id": "1432683903346", "back": "\u6267 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/11deb25c-c32f-40f4-bd95-8da79a559adf/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6267\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6267\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u1ea5p (hold, maintain/uphold)"}, {"front": "ch\u1ea5p (hold, maintain/uphold)", "id": "1432683903347", "back": "ch\u1ea5p (hold, maintain/uphold)  <hr id=answer>  \u6267 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/11deb25c-c32f-40f4-bd95-8da79a559adf/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6267\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6267\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5999", "id": "1432684481655", "back": "\u5999 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/24fe8289-c306-444e-b0d9-a7c327a7af32/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5999\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5999\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  di\u1ec7u (wonderful)"}, {"front": "di\u1ec7u (wonderful)", "id": "1432684481656", "back": "di\u1ec7u (wonderful)  <hr id=answer>  \u5999 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/24fe8289-c306-444e-b0d9-a7c327a7af32/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5999\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5999\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5766", "id": "1432684593172", "back": "\u5766 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b7d783ee-26ca-4898-b04c-d27b141e0800/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5766\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5766\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ea3n (flat/level, calm, son-in-law, transcription sound for -tan-)"}, {"front": "th\u1ea3n (flat/level, calm, son-in-law, transcription sound for -tan-)", "id": "1432684593173", "back": "th\u1ea3n (flat/level, calm, son-in-law, transcription sound for -tan-)  <hr id=answer>  \u5766 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b7d783ee-26ca-4898-b04c-d27b141e0800/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5766\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5766\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f0a", "id": "1432684811217", "back": "\u4f0a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/de46ec27-aea1-4bc6-9d42-d98c408067ec/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f0a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f0a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  y (he/she, family name, transcription sound for -i-)"}, {"front": "y (he/she, family name, transcription sound for -i-)", "id": "1432684811218", "back": "y (he/she, family name, transcription sound for -i-)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f0a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/de46ec27-aea1-4bc6-9d42-d98c408067ec/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f0a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f0a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u654f", "id": "1432684932148", "back": "\u654f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9640efff-186e-4fd2-bbb2-81e65d55a0f5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u654f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u654f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1eabn (quick/agile, smart/nimble, eager)"}, {"front": "m\u1eabn (quick/agile, smart/nimble, eager)", "id": "1432684932149", "back": "m\u1eabn (quick/agile, smart/nimble, eager)  <hr id=answer>  \u654f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9640efff-186e-4fd2-bbb2-81e65d55a0f5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u654f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u654f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u54c8", "id": "1432685020249", "back": "\u54c8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/216dd192-ac52-46b7-8add-6571ea16e967/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u54c8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u54c8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ha (laughing sound)"}, {"front": "ha (laughing sound)", "id": "1432685020250", "back": "ha (laughing sound)  <hr id=answer>  \u54c8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/216dd192-ac52-46b7-8add-6571ea16e967/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u54c8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u54c8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5f20", "id": "1432685164209", "back": "\u5f20 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e2d71afa-f875-4032-9fa1-b80ee9f4b8b7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f20\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f20\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u01b0\u01a1ng (stretch, display, unit for a stretchable/flat object)"}, {"front": "tr\u01b0\u01a1ng (stretch, display, unit for a stretchable/flat object)", "id": "1432685164210", "back": "tr\u01b0\u01a1ng (stretch, display, unit for a stretchable/flat object)  <hr id=answer>  \u5f20 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e2d71afa-f875-4032-9fa1-b80ee9f4b8b7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f20\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f20\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53d1", "id": "1432685268361", "back": "\u53d1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f6f0059e-fbdd-485c-86ed-17b498eacc32/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53d1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53d1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u00e1t (start/launch)"}, {"front": "ph\u00e1t (start/launch)", "id": "1432685268362", "back": "ph\u00e1t (start/launch)  <hr id=answer>  \u53d1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f6f0059e-fbdd-485c-86ed-17b498eacc32/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53d1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53d1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6bcf", "id": "1432685319374", "back": "\u6bcf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4350f4d6-9be9-4f01-804c-0b081f3645c7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bcf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bcf\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ed7i (every/each)"}, {"front": "m\u1ed7i (every/each)", "id": "1432685319375", "back": "m\u1ed7i (every/each)  <hr id=answer>  \u6bcf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4350f4d6-9be9-4f01-804c-0b081f3645c7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bcf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bcf\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6982", "id": "1432685813506", "back": "\u6982 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5a0da887-cb8a-4091-8a72-26aef60b7fa0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6982\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6982\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u00e1i (general/overall, manner)"}, {"front": "kh\u00e1i (general/overall, manner)", "id": "1432685813507", "back": "kh\u00e1i (general/overall, manner)  <hr id=answer>  \u6982 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5a0da887-cb8a-4091-8a72-26aef60b7fa0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6982\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6982\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e86", "id": "1432685878073", "back": "\u4e86 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0f592361-099b-449d-83d8-3449ef56aebd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e86\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e86\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  li\u1ec5u (complete/end, understand)"}, {"front": "li\u1ec5u (complete/end, understand)", "id": "1432685878074", "back": "li\u1ec5u (complete/end, understand)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e86 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0f592361-099b-449d-83d8-3449ef56aebd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e86\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e86\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5b9a", "id": "1432706592279", "back": "\u5b9a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9606713d-7201-4c41-a3ba-d4bc00753765/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b9a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b9a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ecbnh (fixed, settle, definite)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ecbnh (fixed, settle, definite)", "id": "1432706592280", "back": "\u0111\u1ecbnh (fixed, settle, definite)  <hr id=answer>  \u5b9a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9606713d-7201-4c41-a3ba-d4bc00753765/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b9a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b9a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u559c", "id": "1432706708937", "back": "\u559c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dab55a56-8d6c-43ea-be9c-c5d13335970f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u559c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u559c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ec9 (joy, happy/joyful)"}, {"front": "h\u1ec9 (joy, happy/joyful)", "id": "1432706708938", "back": "h\u1ec9 (joy, happy/joyful)  <hr id=answer>  \u559c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/dab55a56-8d6c-43ea-be9c-c5d13335970f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u559c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u559c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u61d2", "id": "1432706806189", "back": "\u61d2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c07d8a87-91dc-43cd-bbc8-33e38ae693be/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u61d2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u61d2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u00e3n (lazy, disinclined)"}, {"front": "l\u00e3n (lazy, disinclined)", "id": "1432706806190", "back": "l\u00e3n (lazy, disinclined)  <hr id=answer>  \u61d2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c07d8a87-91dc-43cd-bbc8-33e38ae693be/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u61d2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u61d2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9053", "id": "1432707132248", "back": "\u9053 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0f9a226d-7c87-4f4b-95ff-0867f9239395/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9053\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9053\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ea1o (road/path,&nbsp;theory/doctrine,&nbsp;Taoism, unit for long things like a road, unit for layer/law)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ea1o (road/path,&nbsp;theory/doctrine,&nbsp;Taoism, unit for long things like a road, unit for layer/law)", "id": "1432707132249", "back": "\u0111\u1ea1o (road/path,&nbsp;theory/doctrine,&nbsp;Taoism, unit for long things like a road, unit for layer/law)  <hr id=answer>  \u9053 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0f9a226d-7c87-4f4b-95ff-0867f9239395/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9053\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9053\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e94", "id": "1432707277866", "back": "\u5e94 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3f821caa-7622-4385-a9ac-36dfa62b8f9d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e94\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e94\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u01b0ng (shoud/need),&nbsp;\u1ee9ng (respond, comply, assent)"}, {"front": "\u01b0ng (shoud/need),&nbsp;\u1ee9ng (respond, comply, assent)", "id": "1432707277867", "back": "\u01b0ng (shoud/need),&nbsp;\u1ee9ng (respond, comply, assent)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e94 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3f821caa-7622-4385-a9ac-36dfa62b8f9d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e94\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e94\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8be5", "id": "1432707453492", "back": "\u8be5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c4d43ea1-ce52-4767-86a8-49a9a2c8db42/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8be5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8be5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  cai (should, fated to, turn to do sth)"}, {"front": "cai (should, fated to, turn to do sth)", "id": "1432707453493", "back": "cai (should, fated to, turn to do sth)  <hr id=answer>  \u8be5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c4d43ea1-ce52-4767-86a8-49a9a2c8db42/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8be5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8be5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u89c6", "id": "1432707650700", "back": "\u89c6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/54c215e9-3ac0-4001-82e5-259df0ba0ccb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u89c6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u89c6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ecb (look at, watch, look upon)"}, {"front": "th\u1ecb (look at, watch, look upon)", "id": "1432707650701", "back": "th\u1ecb (look at, watch, look upon)  <hr id=answer>  \u89c6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/54c215e9-3ac0-4001-82e5-259df0ba0ccb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u89c6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u89c6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u62a5", "id": "1432707769172", "back": "\u62a5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6b47c96d-d944-4eb1-a3f7-cc764b4681b3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u62a5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u62a5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00e1o (repay/reward, report, newspaper)"}, {"front": "b\u00e1o (repay/reward, report, newspaper)", "id": "1432707769173", "back": "b\u00e1o (repay/reward, report, newspaper)  <hr id=answer>  \u62a5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6b47c96d-d944-4eb1-a3f7-cc764b4681b3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u62a5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u62a5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7eb8", "id": "1432707833715", "back": "\u7eb8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/99ae8c59-5e2c-49e0-8ea1-ac569faddced/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7eb8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7eb8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u1ec9 (paper)"}, {"front": "ch\u1ec9 (paper)", "id": "1432707833716", "back": "ch\u1ec9 (paper)  <hr id=answer>  \u7eb8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/99ae8c59-5e2c-49e0-8ea1-ac569faddced/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7eb8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7eb8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u60ef", "id": "1432708003622", "back": "\u60ef <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e31dafdc-d840-4bd8-83ef-3ae9fe0fa959/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u60ef\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u60ef\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  qu\u00e1n (habit/custom, spoil a child)"}, {"front": "qu\u00e1n (habit/custom, spoil a child)", "id": "1432708003623", "back": "qu\u00e1n (habit/custom, spoil a child)  <hr id=answer>  \u60ef <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e31dafdc-d840-4bd8-83ef-3ae9fe0fa959/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u60ef\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u60ef\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u606f", "id": "1432708147666", "back": "\u606f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/09ffa801-9028-4609-9c32-12379a760e7f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u606f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u606f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ee9c (breath, news/tidings, rest, interest, offspring)"}, {"front": "t\u1ee9c (breath, news/tidings, rest, interest, offspring)", "id": "1432708147667", "back": "t\u1ee9c (breath, news/tidings, rest, interest, offspring)  <hr id=answer>  \u606f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/09ffa801-9028-4609-9c32-12379a760e7f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u606f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u606f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8d56", "id": "1433282661164", "back": "\u8d56 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/457823b5-01e6-4882-99cf-ef3fec01e44b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d56\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d56\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1ea1i (rely/depend on, accuse, bad/no good)"}, {"front": "l\u1ea1i (rely/depend on, accuse, bad/no good)", "id": "1433282661165", "back": "l\u1ea1i (rely/depend on, accuse, bad/no good)  <hr id=answer>  \u8d56 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/457823b5-01e6-4882-99cf-ef3fec01e44b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d56\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d56\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65e2", "id": "1433282768839", "back": "\u65e2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/06947e9f-3a29-418d-8467-e12b3bf152c7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65e2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65e2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  k\u00ed (already/finish)"}, {"front": "k\u00ed (already/finish)", "id": "1433282768840", "back": "k\u00ed (already/finish)  <hr id=answer>  \u65e2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/06947e9f-3a29-418d-8467-e12b3bf152c7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65e2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65e2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8d2f", "id": "1433282913018", "back": "\u8d2f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/407b52d9-6292-4719-adfd-715bf0ae1f04/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d2f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d2f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  qu\u00e1n (string on a thread)"}, {"front": "qu\u00e1n (string on a thread)", "id": "1433282913019", "back": "qu\u00e1n (string on a thread)  <hr id=answer>  \u8d2f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/407b52d9-6292-4719-adfd-715bf0ae1f04/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8d2f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8d2f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c39", "id": "1433283106033", "back": "\u5c39 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/af080d0d-8ebd-40c8-bce0-6c56d491b208/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c39\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c39\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  du\u1eabn, do\u00e3n (govern/rule, family name)"}, {"front": "du\u1eabn, do\u00e3n (govern/rule, family name)", "id": "1433283106034", "back": "du\u1eabn, do\u00e3n (govern/rule, family name)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c39 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/af080d0d-8ebd-40c8-bce0-6c56d491b208/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c39\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c39\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6cb9", "id": "1433283272128", "back": "\u6cb9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f233585c-4f5e-4903-95cc-999faac9309f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6cb9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6cb9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  du (oil/fat/grease/gasoline, sly/greasy, flourishing)"}, {"front": "du (oil/fat/grease/gasoline, sly/greasy, flourishing)", "id": "1433283272129", "back": "du (oil/fat/grease/gasoline, sly/greasy, flourishing)  <hr id=answer>  \u6cb9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/f233585c-4f5e-4903-95cc-999faac9309f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6cb9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6cb9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u540c", "id": "1433283308374", "back": "\u540c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/badc203b-3e43-495b-a8d1-6f69b9e754c3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u540c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u540c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ed3ng (same/equal/common)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ed3ng (same/equal/common)", "id": "1433283308375", "back": "\u0111\u1ed3ng (same/equal/common)  <hr id=answer>  \u540c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/badc203b-3e43-495b-a8d1-6f69b9e754c3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u540c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u540c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5730", "id": "1433283438474", "back": "\u5730 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4e6f61da-7699-48d0-9451-74a932fe8dd4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5730\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5730\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ecba (earth/land, region/local, adjunct with other)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ecba (earth/land, region/local, adjunct with other)", "id": "1433283438475", "back": "\u0111\u1ecba (earth/land, region/local, adjunct with other)  <hr id=answer>  \u5730 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4e6f61da-7699-48d0-9451-74a932fe8dd4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5730\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5730\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e1a", "id": "1433283504454", "back": "\u4e1a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/db71f064-a218-464a-876d-4fba2009fe9e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e1a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e1a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nghi\u1ec7p (work/profession, estate/property)<div><br /></div><div>\u696d&nbsp;</div>"}, {"front": "nghi\u1ec7p (work/profession, estate/property)<div><br /></div><div>\u696d&nbsp;</div>", "id": "1433283504455", "back": "nghi\u1ec7p (work/profession, estate/property)<div><br /></div><div>\u696d&nbsp;</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4e1a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/db71f064-a218-464a-876d-4fba2009fe9e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e1a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e1a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u57ce", "id": "1433283537196", "back": "\u57ce <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b28ba436-0510-4597-9e2e-63c3dd437744/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u57ce\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u57ce\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00e0nh (wall, city)"}, {"front": "th\u00e0nh (wall, city)", "id": "1433283537197", "back": "th\u00e0nh (wall, city)  <hr id=answer>  \u57ce <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b28ba436-0510-4597-9e2e-63c3dd437744/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u57ce\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u57ce\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5168", "id": "1433977211531", "back": "\u5168 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a199c440-5660-4612-9b9f-420d325de304/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5168\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5168\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  to\u00e0n (complete/all, whole)"}, {"front": "to\u00e0n (complete/all, whole)", "id": "1433977211533", "back": "to\u00e0n (complete/all, whole)  <hr id=answer>  \u5168 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a199c440-5660-4612-9b9f-420d325de304/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5168\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5168\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u62a4", "id": "1433977312945", "back": "\u62a4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/10627ac6-2f00-49c1-8c84-b7223599dfaa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u62a4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u62a4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ed9 (protect, defend)<div><br /></div><div>\u8b77</div>"}, {"front": "h\u1ed9 (protect, defend)<div><br /></div><div>\u8b77</div>", "id": "1433977312946", "back": "h\u1ed9 (protect, defend)<div><br /></div><div>\u8b77</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u62a4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/10627ac6-2f00-49c1-8c84-b7223599dfaa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u62a4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u62a4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u56e2", "id": "1433977431193", "back": "\u56e2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e8188b9d-83ab-4522-94b7-e75087509ed3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u56e2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u56e2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111o\u00e0n (sphere/ball, organization, unite)"}, {"front": "\u0111o\u00e0n (sphere/ball, organization, unite)", "id": "1433977431194", "back": "\u0111o\u00e0n (sphere/ball, organization, unite)  <hr id=answer>  \u56e2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e8188b9d-83ab-4522-94b7-e75087509ed3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u56e2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u56e2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7ed3", "id": "1433977546262", "back": "\u7ed3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5cf19cd5-a6c9-4d62-b1e6-246dc014fef4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ed3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ed3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  k\u1ebft (to tie/knot, to form)"}, {"front": "k\u1ebft (to tie/knot, to form)", "id": "1433977546263", "back": "k\u1ebft (to tie/knot, to form)  <hr id=answer>  \u7ed3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/5cf19cd5-a6c9-4d62-b1e6-246dc014fef4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ed3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ed3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6bcb", "id": "1433977596337", "back": "\u6bcb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3ba625a2-8465-4474-ade6-2e1e001bdca0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bcb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bcb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u00f4 (do not/no, family name)"}, {"front": "v\u00f4 (do not/no, family name)", "id": "1433977596338", "back": "v\u00f4 (do not/no, family name)  <hr id=answer>  \u6bcb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3ba625a2-8465-4474-ade6-2e1e001bdca0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bcb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bcb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u524c", "id": "1433977665931", "back": "\u524c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/06dd122d-a8a6-4149-9e10-eff3240fdda9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u524c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u524c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1ea1t (slash open, disagreeable/rebellious)"}, {"front": "l\u1ea1t (slash open, disagreeable/rebellious)", "id": "1433977665932", "back": "l\u1ea1t (slash open, disagreeable/rebellious)  <hr id=answer>  \u524c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/06dd122d-a8a6-4149-9e10-eff3240fdda9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u524c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u524c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ecb", "id": "1436167490192", "back": "\u4ecb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0d8b0781-5a97-4c1b-b51a-0ff495281c7d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ecb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ecb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u1edbi (between, aid, upright/honorable)"}, {"front": "gi\u1edbi (between, aid, upright/honorable)", "id": "1436167490193", "back": "gi\u1edbi (between, aid, upright/honorable)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ecb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0d8b0781-5a97-4c1b-b51a-0ff495281c7d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ecb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ecb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5934", "id": "1436167556344", "back": "\u5934 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b5f80f29-3b3e-4c7b-a027-8f24a6db1eb4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5934\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5934\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ea7u (head)<br /><div>\u982d</div>"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ea7u (head)<br /><div>\u982d</div>", "id": "1436167556345", "back": "\u0111\u1ea7u (head)<br /><div>\u982d</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5934 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b5f80f29-3b3e-4c7b-a027-8f24a6db1eb4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5934\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5934\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9992", "id": "1436167602683", "back": "\u9992 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b425b5c7-92a7-4f12-a61f-2f6332585a29/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9992\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9992\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  man (banh bao)"}, {"front": "man (banh bao)", "id": "1436167602684", "back": "man (banh bao)  <hr id=answer>  \u9992 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b425b5c7-92a7-4f12-a61f-2f6332585a29/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9992\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9992\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7897", "id": "1436167654120", "back": "\u7897 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cac37e00-d799-45f9-9b7f-134100317570/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7897\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7897\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  o\u1ea3n (bowl)"}, {"front": "o\u1ea3n (bowl)", "id": "1436167654121", "back": "o\u1ea3n (bowl)  <hr id=answer>  \u7897 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cac37e00-d799-45f9-9b7f-134100317570/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7897\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7897\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9e21", "id": "1436167706486", "back": "\u9e21 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e023e094-1778-4fbe-9c58-b8a226534882/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9e21\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9e21\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  k\u00ea (chicken)"}, {"front": "k\u00ea (chicken)", "id": "1436167706487", "back": "k\u00ea (chicken)  <hr id=answer>  \u9e21 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e023e094-1778-4fbe-9c58-b8a226534882/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9e21\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9e21\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u86cb", "id": "1436167809042", "back": "\u86cb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6e60e3da-6f72-4f4b-b223-c53741417497/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u86cb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u86cb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ea3n (egg, ti\u1ebfng \u0111\u1ec3 nh\u1ee5c m\u1ea1 khinh ch\u00ea)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ea3n (egg, ti\u1ebfng \u0111\u1ec3 nh\u1ee5c m\u1ea1 khinh ch\u00ea)", "id": "1436167809043", "back": "\u0111\u1ea3n (egg, ti\u1ebfng \u0111\u1ec3 nh\u1ee5c m\u1ea1 khinh ch\u00ea)  <hr id=answer>  \u86cb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6e60e3da-6f72-4f4b-b223-c53741417497/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u86cb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u86cb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6c64", "id": "1436167853883", "back": "\u6c64 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9ba843ed-4c8f-45f9-9fcc-b46f1befa7c0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c64\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c64\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thang (hot water, soup)<div>\u6e6f</div>"}, {"front": "thang (hot water, soup)<div>\u6e6f</div>", "id": "1436167853885", "back": "thang (hot water, soup)<div>\u6e6f</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u6c64 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9ba843ed-4c8f-45f9-9fcc-b46f1befa7c0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c64\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c64\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5564", "id": "1436167930924", "back": "\u5564 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c0381186-410a-4d28-a07e-ae3c3c1e62d4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5564\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5564\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti (bia)"}, {"front": "ti (bia)", "id": "1436167930925", "back": "ti (bia)  <hr id=answer>  \u5564 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c0381186-410a-4d28-a07e-ae3c3c1e62d4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5564\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5564\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e9b", "id": "1436167988193", "back": "\u4e9b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2d6eaa97-d7cf-4c8b-9190-b65818241bd8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e9b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e9b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ta (a small number, a few)"}, {"front": "ta (a small number, a few)", "id": "1436167988194", "back": "ta (a small number, a few)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e9b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2d6eaa97-d7cf-4c8b-9190-b65818241bd8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e9b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e9b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u997a", "id": "1436168089125", "back": "\u997a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cad6b272-826f-4366-a7da-f372b93fa80c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u997a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u997a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u00e1o (stuffed dumpling)"}, {"front": "gi\u00e1o (stuffed dumpling)", "id": "1436168089126", "back": "gi\u00e1o (stuffed dumpling)  <hr id=answer>  \u997a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cad6b272-826f-4366-a7da-f372b93fa80c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u997a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u997a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5305", "id": "1436168191293", "back": "\u5305 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b150b1d7-d9cd-41a7-ab85-b01a60441b9c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5305\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5305\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  bao (contain/surround, a package, guarantee)"}, {"front": "bao (contain/surround, a package, guarantee)", "id": "1436168191294", "back": "bao (contain/surround, a package, guarantee)  <hr id=answer>  \u5305 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b150b1d7-d9cd-41a7-ab85-b01a60441b9c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5305\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5305\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6761", "id": "1436168351998", "back": "\u6761 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b15f9dd1-633b-494c-a1fa-80468da9141e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6761\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6761\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111i\u1ec1u (branch, numerary for narrow/long things, article/clause in law/agreement)"}, {"front": "\u0111i\u1ec1u (branch, numerary for narrow/long things, article/clause in law/agreement)", "id": "1436168352000", "back": "\u0111i\u1ec1u (branch, numerary for narrow/long things, article/clause in law/agreement)  <hr id=answer>  \u6761 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b15f9dd1-633b-494c-a1fa-80468da9141e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6761\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6761\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u673a", "id": "1436168424479", "back": "\u673a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e767528f-04c1-4d99-ac9f-b911a019cda8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u673a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u673a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u01a1 (mechanics / machinery / opportune / opportunity / a crucial point / a pivot / tricky / cunning)"}, {"front": "c\u01a1 (mechanics / machinery / opportune / opportunity / a crucial point / a pivot / tricky / cunning)", "id": "1436168424480", "back": "c\u01a1 (mechanics / machinery / opportune / opportunity / a crucial point / a pivot / tricky / cunning)  <hr id=answer>  \u673a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e767528f-04c1-4d99-ac9f-b911a019cda8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u673a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u673a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u66f0", "id": "1436168496819", "back": "\u66f0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3130cd6a-39ba-4bf4-8420-c4a33f87a7cb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66f0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66f0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  vi\u1ebft (archaic usage - to say / to call / to name)"}, {"front": "vi\u1ebft (archaic usage - to say / to call / to name)", "id": "1436168496820", "back": "vi\u1ebft (archaic usage - to say / to call / to name)  <hr id=answer>  \u66f0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/3130cd6a-39ba-4bf4-8420-c4a33f87a7cb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66f0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66f0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5409", "id": "1436168540980", "back": "\u5409 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8a06069e-3510-4b1f-a2e7-bc281c0a9e33/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5409\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5409\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00e1t (good / lucky / auspicious / propitious / favorable / fortunate)"}, {"front": "c\u00e1t (good / lucky / auspicious / propitious / favorable / fortunate)", "id": "1436168540981", "back": "c\u00e1t (good / lucky / auspicious / propitious / favorable / fortunate)  <hr id=answer>  \u5409 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8a06069e-3510-4b1f-a2e7-bc281c0a9e33/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5409\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5409\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u676f", "id": "1436168633082", "back": "\u676f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b859474c-48dc-4a2c-bd4d-e6a49f60f65e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u676f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u676f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00f4i (ch\u00e9n, cup for winner)"}, {"front": "b\u00f4i (ch\u00e9n, cup for winner)", "id": "1436168633083", "back": "b\u00f4i (ch\u00e9n, cup for winner)  <hr id=answer>  \u676f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b859474c-48dc-4a2c-bd4d-e6a49f60f65e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u676f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u676f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u539f", "id": "1436472971298", "back": "\u539f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/37554b1c-02b2-40d3-9966-460cb99296e2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u539f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u539f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nguy\u00ean (original/primary, plain/field/graveyard)"}, {"front": "nguy\u00ean (original/primary, plain/field/graveyard)", "id": "1436472971299", "back": "nguy\u00ean (original/primary, plain/field/graveyard)  <hr id=answer>  \u539f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/37554b1c-02b2-40d3-9966-460cb99296e2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u539f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u539f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6307", "id": "1436473117090", "back": "\u6307 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8acb8bdd-75bd-4713-9748-a01527105ed7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6307\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6307\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u1ec9 (finger, point/indicate, hope)"}, {"front": "ch\u1ec9 (finger, point/indicate, hope)", "id": "1436473117092", "back": "ch\u1ec9 (finger, point/indicate, hope)  <hr id=answer>  \u6307 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8acb8bdd-75bd-4713-9748-a01527105ed7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6307\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6307\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65e0", "id": "1436473281705", "back": "\u65e0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/85d93155-8695-40dc-bf77-3bc9ad000673/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65e0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65e0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u00f4 (negative/none/without)"}, {"front": "v\u00f4 (negative/none/without)", "id": "1436473281706", "back": "v\u00f4 (negative/none/without)  <hr id=answer>  \u65e0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/85d93155-8695-40dc-bf77-3bc9ad000673/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65e0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65e0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53f0", "id": "1436473497727", "back": "\u53f0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/73993509-e261-4ee8-a3f2-171a66ddda30/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53f0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53f0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00e0i (tower, raised platform, Taiwan)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00e0i (tower, raised platform, Taiwan)", "id": "1436473497728", "back": "\u0111\u00e0i (tower, raised platform, Taiwan)  <hr id=answer>  \u53f0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/73993509-e261-4ee8-a3f2-171a66ddda30/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53f0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53f0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u52a8", "id": "1436473598367", "back": "\u52a8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/665a8002-e49d-4d33-a1ac-60f0bc6e5abc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52a8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52a8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ed9ng (move, motion)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ed9ng (move, motion)", "id": "1436473598368", "back": "\u0111\u1ed9ng (move, motion)  <hr id=answer>  \u52a8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/665a8002-e49d-4d33-a1ac-60f0bc6e5abc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52a8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52a8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8865", "id": "1436473661816", "back": "\u8865 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4a3c174c-1433-4066-ba73-d6d1ffef4f2a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8865\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8865\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ed5 (patch/repair, supplement)"}, {"front": "b\u1ed5 (patch/repair, supplement)", "id": "1436473661817", "back": "b\u1ed5 (patch/repair, supplement)  <hr id=answer>  \u8865 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/4a3c174c-1433-4066-ba73-d6d1ffef4f2a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8865\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8865\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53cd", "id": "1436474869960", "back": "\u53cd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1a5e3f05-ad18-4222-a61a-b8d4e52f6059/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53cd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53cd\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u1ea3n (contrary, turn back, rebel)"}, {"front": "ph\u1ea3n (contrary, turn back, rebel)", "id": "1436474869961", "back": "ph\u1ea3n (contrary, turn back, rebel)  <hr id=answer>  \u53cd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1a5e3f05-ad18-4222-a61a-b8d4e52f6059/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53cd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53cd\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u66fc", "id": "1436474995998", "back": "\u66fc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6c9f9d7a-c364-415c-a8ca-841835ffeebb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66fc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66fc\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ea1n (long/vast, delicate/graceful)"}, {"front": "m\u1ea1n (long/vast, delicate/graceful)", "id": "1436474995999", "back": "m\u1ea1n (long/vast, delicate/graceful)  <hr id=answer>  \u66fc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6c9f9d7a-c364-415c-a8ca-841835ffeebb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66fc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66fc\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5351", "id": "1436475213976", "back": "\u5351 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/74ba1ea5-d797-4286-a897-a610fd285164/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5351\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5351\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti (low/inferior, vile/debased)"}, {"front": "ti (low/inferior, vile/debased)", "id": "1436475213977", "back": "ti (low/inferior, vile/debased)  <hr id=answer>  \u5351 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/74ba1ea5-d797-4286-a897-a610fd285164/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5351\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5351\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6b64", "id": "1436475294519", "back": "\u6b64 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/544383e1-8237-4f79-9890-b58e697b04d9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b64\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b64\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1eed (this, these, here)"}, {"front": "th\u1eed (this, these, here)", "id": "1436475294520", "back": "th\u1eed (this, these, here)  <hr id=answer>  \u6b64 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/544383e1-8237-4f79-9890-b58e697b04d9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b64\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b64\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5b9b", "id": "1436475385223", "back": "\u5b9b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bed42a4a-a03c-4cb0-abff-84a7736a76a8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b9b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b9b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  uy\u1ec3n (as if, crooked/roundabout)"}, {"front": "uy\u1ec3n (as if, crooked/roundabout)", "id": "1436475385224", "back": "uy\u1ec3n (as if, crooked/roundabout)  <hr id=answer>  \u5b9b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bed42a4a-a03c-4cb0-abff-84a7736a76a8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b9b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b9b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u675f", "id": "1436475465897", "back": "\u675f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ae9698e9-4657-487b-a420-36863c4bccfe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u675f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u675f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00fac (control, restrain)&nbsp;"}, {"front": "th\u00fac (control, restrain)&nbsp;", "id": "1436475465899", "back": "th\u00fac (control, restrain)&nbsp;  <hr id=answer>  \u675f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ae9698e9-4657-487b-a420-36863c4bccfe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u675f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u675f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53cc", "id": "1436475536862", "back": "\u53cc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/33b796f8-bba0-4f19-976e-7cdd5f3d80c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53cc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53cc\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  song (pair/couple, two/even)"}, {"front": "song (pair/couple, two/even)", "id": "1436475536863", "back": "song (pair/couple, two/even)  <hr id=answer>  \u53cc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/33b796f8-bba0-4f19-976e-7cdd5f3d80c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53cc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53cc\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65e8", "id": "1436475648247", "back": "\u65e8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b710c123-4927-4fd8-b169-d57c41493b62/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65e8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65e8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u1ec9 (decree/will/intention, delicious/tasty)"}, {"front": "ch\u1ec9 (decree/will/intention, delicious/tasty)", "id": "1436475648249", "back": "ch\u1ec9 (decree/will/intention, delicious/tasty)  <hr id=answer>  \u65e8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/b710c123-4927-4fd8-b169-d57c41493b62/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65e8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65e8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5192", "id": "1436475746965", "back": "\u5192 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/59a4ee67-4387-483d-bff6-c7e1b79085ac/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5192\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5192\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ea1o (imprudent/rash, put forth)"}, {"front": "m\u1ea1o (imprudent/rash, put forth)", "id": "1436475746966", "back": "m\u1ea1o (imprudent/rash, put forth)  <hr id=answer>  \u5192 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/59a4ee67-4387-483d-bff6-c7e1b79085ac/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5192\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5192\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u535c", "id": "1437267608897", "back": "\u535c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/81e0b969-6cdc-4f77-9fc3-d736dbbd41b6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u535c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u535c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ed1c (select)"}, {"front": "b\u1ed1c (select)", "id": "1437267608898", "back": "b\u1ed1c (select)  <hr id=answer>  \u535c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/81e0b969-6cdc-4f77-9fc3-d736dbbd41b6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u535c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u535c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u540e", "id": "1437267651457", "back": "\u540e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/e0376dd6-449c-422e-b10c-d74bc771f596/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u540e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u540e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1eadu (king/queen, after)"}, {"front": "h\u1eadu (king/queen, after)", "id": "1437267651458", "back": "h\u1eadu (king/queen, after)  <hr id=answer>  \u540e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/e0376dd6-449c-422e-b10c-d74bc771f596/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u540e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u540e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7f6a", "id": "1437267693343", "back": "\u7f6a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/d459808b-4497-4117-a036-780d55ca9e1d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7f6a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7f6a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ed9i (crime/mistake, sentence/punishment)"}, {"front": "t\u1ed9i (crime/mistake, sentence/punishment)", "id": "1437267693344", "back": "t\u1ed9i (crime/mistake, sentence/punishment)  <hr id=answer>  \u7f6a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/d459808b-4497-4117-a036-780d55ca9e1d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7f6a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7f6a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ee3", "id": "1437267740201", "back": "\u4ee3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/70b1978f-bf65-4a9c-a608-404fe249a7bb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ee3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ee3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ea1i (time, instead/on behalf)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ea1i (time, instead/on behalf)", "id": "1437267740202", "back": "\u0111\u1ea1i (time, instead/on behalf)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ee3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/70b1978f-bf65-4a9c-a608-404fe249a7bb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ee3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ee3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u66ff", "id": "1437267797199", "back": "\u66ff <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/ea72c734-491e-4595-9680-b3a00936cf9a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66ff\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66ff\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ebf (on behalf, replace, decline)"}, {"front": "th\u1ebf (on behalf, replace, decline)", "id": "1437267797200", "back": "th\u1ebf (on behalf, replace, decline)  <hr id=answer>  \u66ff <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/ea72c734-491e-4595-9680-b3a00936cf9a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66ff\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66ff\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ebf", "id": "1437267832235", "back": "\u4ebf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/211a0410-ad0c-4fa4-82d4-f3bf7b8bf5b5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ebf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ebf\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u1ee9c (m\u1ed9t v\u1ea1n l\u1ea7n m\u1ed9t v\u1ea1n, t\u1ee9c l\u00e0 m\u1ed9t tr\u0103m tri\u1ec7u)"}, {"front": "\u1ee9c (m\u1ed9t v\u1ea1n l\u1ea7n m\u1ed9t v\u1ea1n, t\u1ee9c l\u00e0 m\u1ed9t tr\u0103m tri\u1ec7u)", "id": "1437267832236", "back": "\u1ee9c (m\u1ed9t v\u1ea1n l\u1ea7n m\u1ed9t v\u1ea1n, t\u1ee9c l\u00e0 m\u1ed9t tr\u0103m tri\u1ec7u)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ebf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/211a0410-ad0c-4fa4-82d4-f3bf7b8bf5b5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ebf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ebf\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u89e3", "id": "1437267882927", "back": "\u89e3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/23aeb6e4-ee0e-4d44-8939-d755e47e4077/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u89e3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u89e3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u1ea3i (open, analyze/explain, understand)"}, {"front": "gi\u1ea3i (open, analyze/explain, understand)", "id": "1437267882928", "back": "gi\u1ea3i (open, analyze/explain, understand)  <hr id=answer>  \u89e3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/23aeb6e4-ee0e-4d44-8939-d755e47e4077/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u89e3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u89e3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5386", "id": "1437267944226", "back": "\u5386 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/89655d5c-de3b-41eb-896b-fc4dec1b6a87/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5386\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5386\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1ecbch (experience, history, calendar)"}, {"front": "l\u1ecbch (experience, history, calendar)", "id": "1437267944227", "back": "l\u1ecbch (experience, history, calendar)  <hr id=answer>  \u5386 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/89655d5c-de3b-41eb-896b-fc4dec1b6a87/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5386\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5386\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53f2", "id": "1437267982729", "back": "\u53f2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/2702c222-8b48-4618-9f0c-069b65336946/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53f2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53f2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u1eed (history,&nbsp;M\u1ed9t ch\u1ee9c quan coi v\u1ec1 v\u0103n th\u01b0)"}, {"front": "s\u1eed (history,&nbsp;M\u1ed9t ch\u1ee9c quan coi v\u1ec1 v\u0103n th\u01b0)", "id": "1437267982730", "back": "s\u1eed (history,&nbsp;M\u1ed9t ch\u1ee9c quan coi v\u1ec1 v\u0103n th\u01b0)  <hr id=answer>  \u53f2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/2702c222-8b48-4618-9f0c-069b65336946/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53f2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53f2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u79ef", "id": "1437268019627", "back": "\u79ef <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/a1a7b0ad-752e-41df-bd35-fa4093d01904/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79ef\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79ef\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00edch (accumulate, multiplication/product)"}, {"front": "t\u00edch (accumulate, multiplication/product)", "id": "1437268019628", "back": "t\u00edch (accumulate, multiplication/product)  <hr id=answer>  \u79ef <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/a1a7b0ad-752e-41df-bd35-fa4093d01904/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79ef\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79ef\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9996", "id": "1437268075357", "back": "\u9996 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/c9bf0fa9-fc85-4345-8ca8-50c931d70cab/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9996\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9996\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ee7 (head, leader, first), th\u00fa (confess to crime)"}, {"front": "th\u1ee7 (head, leader, first), th\u00fa (confess to crime)", "id": "1437268075358", "back": "th\u1ee7 (head, leader, first), th\u00fa (confess to crime)  <hr id=answer>  \u9996 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/c9bf0fa9-fc85-4345-8ca8-50c931d70cab/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9996\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9996\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u542c", "id": "1437268139042", "back": "\u542c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/5c9faf99-69ce-481a-b50a-2066bf6ae972/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u542c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u542c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00ednh (listen/hear, obey, translation of \"tin\")<div><br /></div><div>\u807d</div>"}, {"front": "th\u00ednh (listen/hear, obey, translation of \"tin\")<div><br /></div><div>\u807d</div>", "id": "1437268139043", "back": "th\u00ednh (listen/hear, obey, translation of \"tin\")<div><br /></div><div>\u807d</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u542c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/5c9faf99-69ce-481a-b50a-2066bf6ae972/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u542c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u542c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e50", "id": "1437268164327", "back": "\u4e50 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/ffc7f37a-5488-4039-a352-52f669f74647/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e50\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e50\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nh\u1ea1c (music)"}, {"front": "nh\u1ea1c (music)", "id": "1437268164328", "back": "nh\u1ea1c (music)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e50 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/ffc7f37a-5488-4039-a352-52f669f74647/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e50\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e50\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5178", "id": "1437268204874", "back": "\u5178 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/b42db661-7c9e-4a0b-8abb-933d425fc172/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5178\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5178\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111i\u1ec3n (book, standard/example/classic)"}, {"front": "\u0111i\u1ec3n (book, standard/example/classic)", "id": "1437268204875", "back": "\u0111i\u1ec3n (book, standard/example/classic)  <hr id=answer>  \u5178 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/b42db661-7c9e-4a0b-8abb-933d425fc172/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5178\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5178\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7ecf", "id": "1437268382650", "back": "\u7ecf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/2435b586-d384-47c9-9006-4aa299a94e2c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ecf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ecf\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kinh (law, book/bible, longitude line, organize/business)"}, {"front": "kinh (law, book/bible, longitude line, organize/business)", "id": "1437268382651", "back": "kinh (law, book/bible, longitude line, organize/business)  <hr id=answer>  \u7ecf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/2435b586-d384-47c9-9006-4aa299a94e2c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ecf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ecf\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7279", "id": "1437268413648", "back": "\u7279 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/e82655d9-b5fc-4ef3-afba-dcd99814d79d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7279\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7279\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1eb7c (male, special, transcription for -t-)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1eb7c (male, special, transcription for -t-)", "id": "1437268413649", "back": "\u0111\u1eb7c (male, special, transcription for -t-)  <hr id=answer>  \u7279 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/e82655d9-b5fc-4ef3-afba-dcd99814d79d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7279\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7279\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e13", "id": "1437268487919", "back": "\u4e13 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/fd6646fd-20aa-46c1-afed-5985ab2b3923/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e13\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e13\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  chuy\u00ean (focus/specialize, sole/only)"}, {"front": "chuy\u00ean (focus/specialize, sole/only)", "id": "1437268487920", "back": "chuy\u00ean (focus/specialize, sole/only)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e13 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/fd6646fd-20aa-46c1-afed-5985ab2b3923/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e13\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e13\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e9a", "id": "1437268524458", "back": "\u4e9a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/06907ae9-dd14-40fc-8a04-979c8765e5ce/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e9a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e9a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u00e1 (inferior, Asia)"}, {"front": "\u00e1 (inferior, Asia)", "id": "1437268524459", "back": "\u00e1 (inferior, Asia)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e9a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/06907ae9-dd14-40fc-8a04-979c8765e5ce/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e9a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e9a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6d32", "id": "1437268543869", "back": "\u6d32 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/b5506849-d892-4bb4-a622-512356338e26/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d32\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d32\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u00e2u (continent)"}, {"front": "ch\u00e2u (continent)", "id": "1437268543870", "back": "ch\u00e2u (continent)  <hr id=answer>  \u6d32 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/b5506849-d892-4bb4-a622-512356338e26/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d32\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d32\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7528", "id": "1437268580491", "back": "\u7528 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/777f2479-7da0-4d3e-98b1-02903f44e5d8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7528\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7528\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u1ee5ng (use)"}, {"front": "d\u1ee5ng (use)", "id": "1437268580492", "back": "d\u1ee5ng (use)  <hr id=answer>  \u7528 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/777f2479-7da0-4d3e-98b1-02903f44e5d8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7528\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7528\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u752c", "id": "1437268665644", "back": "\u752c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/bf7f6e84-5296-49e9-b774-bd203cefbaa1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u752c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u752c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u0169ng (L\u1ed1i gi\u1eefa, ng\u00e0y x\u01b0a quan \u0111i, \u0111\u1eafp \u0111\u01b0\u1eddng cao h\u01a1n hai b\u00ean g\u1ecdi l\u00e0 d\u0169ng \u0111\u1ea1o)"}, {"front": "d\u0169ng (L\u1ed1i gi\u1eefa, ng\u00e0y x\u01b0a quan \u0111i, \u0111\u1eafp \u0111\u01b0\u1eddng cao h\u01a1n hai b\u00ean g\u1ecdi l\u00e0 d\u0169ng \u0111\u1ea1o)", "id": "1437268665645", "back": "d\u0169ng (L\u1ed1i gi\u1eefa, ng\u00e0y x\u01b0a quan \u0111i, \u0111\u1eafp \u0111\u01b0\u1eddng cao h\u01a1n hai b\u00ean g\u1ecdi l\u00e0 d\u0169ng \u0111\u1ea1o)  <hr id=answer>  \u752c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/bf7f6e84-5296-49e9-b774-bd203cefbaa1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u752c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u752c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u58f0", "id": "1437268715649", "back": "\u58f0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/ac2bed4b-d213-4c0d-b956-90674b8f1555/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u58f0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u58f0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thanh (sound, explain/declare)"}, {"front": "thanh (sound, explain/declare)", "id": "1437268715650", "back": "thanh (sound, explain/declare)  <hr id=answer>  \u58f0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/ac2bed4b-d213-4c0d-b956-90674b8f1555/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u58f0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u58f0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5dde", "id": "1437892370416", "back": "\u5dde <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/d54da6f6-0225-4ed2-93bb-32e4e5f4ef2e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5dde\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5dde\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u00e2u (province/area/district)"}, {"front": "ch\u00e2u (province/area/district)", "id": "1437892370417", "back": "ch\u00e2u (province/area/district)  <hr id=answer>  \u5dde <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/d54da6f6-0225-4ed2-93bb-32e4e5f4ef2e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5dde\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5dde\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u722a", "id": "1437892626398", "back": "\u722a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/0e64ed7d-651a-4903-b184-f2fbed32d65f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u722a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u722a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u1ea3o (nail, animal leg/claw)"}, {"front": "tr\u1ea3o (nail, animal leg/claw)", "id": "1437892626399", "back": "tr\u1ea3o (nail, animal leg/claw)  <hr id=answer>  \u722a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/0e64ed7d-651a-4903-b184-f2fbed32d65f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u722a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u722a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c14", "id": "1437892945385", "back": "\u5c14 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f656b1b6-1e78-43e1-904b-63e920a5e56a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c14\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c14\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nh\u0129 (thus, so; transcription for -er-)"}, {"front": "nh\u0129 (thus, so; transcription for -er-)", "id": "1437892945386", "back": "nh\u0129 (thus, so; transcription for -er-)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c14 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f656b1b6-1e78-43e1-904b-63e920a5e56a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c14\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c14\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5bfa", "id": "1437893002356", "back": "\u5bfa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/4ce38263-cdb7-4b21-a582-87fecea7b1e2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bfa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bfa\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ef1 (temple, palace)"}, {"front": "t\u1ef1 (temple, palace)", "id": "1437893002357", "back": "t\u1ef1 (temple, palace)  <hr id=answer>  \u5bfa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/4ce38263-cdb7-4b21-a582-87fecea7b1e2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bfa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bfa\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u836f", "id": "1437893055063", "back": "\u836f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/7c0e6b4b-9b4b-4652-b07c-b7ccefba724d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u836f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u836f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u01b0\u1ee3c (medication, chemicals)<div>\u85e5</div>"}, {"front": "d\u01b0\u1ee3c (medication, chemicals)<div>\u85e5</div>", "id": "1437893055064", "back": "d\u01b0\u1ee3c (medication, chemicals)<div>\u85e5</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u836f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/7c0e6b4b-9b4b-4652-b07c-b7ccefba724d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u836f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u836f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u82f9", "id": "1437893086891", "back": "\u82f9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/bf5361de-8b0d-42a8-a9ce-b6c1c6b20ce9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82f9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82f9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00ecnh (apple)"}, {"front": "b\u00ecnh (apple)", "id": "1437893086892", "back": "b\u00ecnh (apple)  <hr id=answer>  \u82f9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/bf5361de-8b0d-42a8-a9ce-b6c1c6b20ce9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82f9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82f9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u94b1", "id": "1437893110672", "back": "\u94b1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/6df0f610-0b54-42f0-8445-ff11894b2557/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u94b1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u94b1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u1ec1n (money)"}, {"front": "ti\u1ec1n (money)", "id": "1437893110673", "back": "ti\u1ec1n (money)  <hr id=answer>  \u94b1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/6df0f610-0b54-42f0-8445-ff11894b2557/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u94b1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u94b1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5757", "id": "1437893165037", "back": "\u5757 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/23a95637-f23c-4cd0-a18a-42d32291477f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5757\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5757\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u1ed1i (H\u00f2n/t\u1ea3ng/c\u1ee5c,&nbsp;\u0110\u1ed3ng b\u1ea1c)"}, {"front": "kh\u1ed1i (H\u00f2n/t\u1ea3ng/c\u1ee5c,&nbsp;\u0110\u1ed3ng b\u1ea1c)", "id": "1437893165038", "back": "kh\u1ed1i (H\u00f2n/t\u1ea3ng/c\u1ee5c,&nbsp;\u0110\u1ed3ng b\u1ea1c)  <hr id=answer>  \u5757 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/23a95637-f23c-4cd0-a18a-42d32291477f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5757\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5757\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6bdb", "id": "1437893297610", "back": "\u6bdb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/84b20f90-d223-4084-ba06-8b54d9cd9365/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bdb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bdb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  mao (hair)"}, {"front": "mao (hair)", "id": "1437893297611", "back": "mao (hair)  <hr id=answer>  \u6bdb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/84b20f90-d223-4084-ba06-8b54d9cd9365/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bdb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bdb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6a58", "id": "1437893325458", "back": "\u6a58 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/69514623-5235-444b-8e90-aa052aed2272/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6a58\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6a58\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  qu\u1ea5t (qu\u00fdt)"}, {"front": "qu\u1ea5t (qu\u00fdt)", "id": "1437893325459", "back": "qu\u1ea5t (qu\u00fdt)  <hr id=answer>  \u6a58 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/69514623-5235-444b-8e90-aa052aed2272/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6a58\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6a58\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7ed9", "id": "1437893377347", "back": "\u7ed9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/c3d4a9a5-bf3b-40a9-8235-10fdbc725e03/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ed9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ed9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ea5p (grant/provide/give)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea5p (grant/provide/give)", "id": "1437893377348", "back": "c\u1ea5p (grant/provide/give)  <hr id=answer>  \u7ed9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/c3d4a9a5-bf3b-40a9-8235-10fdbc725e03/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ed9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ed9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u627e", "id": "1437893402187", "back": "\u627e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/5c25a458-f1fe-4d2c-a65e-960233ccec17/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u627e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u627e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u1ea3o (search, give change)"}, {"front": "tr\u1ea3o (search, give change)", "id": "1437893402188", "back": "tr\u1ea3o (search, give change)  <hr id=answer>  \u627e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/5c25a458-f1fe-4d2c-a65e-960233ccec17/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u627e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u627e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8549", "id": "1437893442407", "back": "\u8549 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/7f800984-52e7-44f2-ae6f-4e09479dec00/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8549\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8549\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u00eau (G\u1ecdi t\u1eaft c\u1ee7a ba ti\u00eau: c\u00e2y chu\u1ed1i)"}, {"front": "ti\u00eau (G\u1ecdi t\u1eaft c\u1ee7a ba ti\u00eau: c\u00e2y chu\u1ed1i)", "id": "1437893442408", "back": "ti\u00eau (G\u1ecdi t\u1eaft c\u1ee7a ba ti\u00eau: c\u00e2y chu\u1ed1i)  <hr id=answer>  \u8549 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/7f800984-52e7-44f2-ae6f-4e09479dec00/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8549\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8549\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8461", "id": "1437893478099", "back": "\u8461 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/1f9295de-fb47-4a69-a14d-4ff6070a6deb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8461\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8461\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ed3 (grape, Portugal)"}, {"front": "b\u1ed3 (grape, Portugal)", "id": "1437893478100", "back": "b\u1ed3 (grape, Portugal)  <hr id=answer>  \u8461 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/1f9295de-fb47-4a69-a14d-4ff6070a6deb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8461\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8461\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8404", "id": "1437893546247", "back": "\u8404 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/b6421414-99d9-4206-ad1f-08a4ef0fb45d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8404\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8404\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00e0o (grape, Portugal)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00e0o (grape, Portugal)", "id": "1437893546248", "back": "\u0111\u00e0o (grape, Portugal)  <hr id=answer>  \u8404 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/b6421414-99d9-4206-ad1f-08a4ef0fb45d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8404\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8404\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u74dc", "id": "1437893796680", "back": "\u74dc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/96ef16b5-b574-4a9b-bc7c-7b5594c8b6f3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u74dc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u74dc\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  qua (D\u01b0a, m\u01b0\u1edbp, b\u1ea7u, b\u00ed; transcription sound; 16-year-old)"}, {"front": "qua (D\u01b0a, m\u01b0\u1edbp, b\u1ea7u, b\u00ed; transcription sound; 16-year-old)", "id": "1437893796681", "back": "qua (D\u01b0a, m\u01b0\u1edbp, b\u1ea7u, b\u00ed; transcription sound; 16-year-old)  <hr id=answer>  \u74dc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/96ef16b5-b574-4a9b-bc7c-7b5594c8b6f3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u74dc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u74dc\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u68a8", "id": "1437893845549", "back": "\u68a8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/dad38a90-118e-4be4-8208-4da33bff1a70/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u68a8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u68a8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u00ea (pear)"}, {"front": "l\u00ea (pear)", "id": "1437893845550", "back": "l\u00ea (pear)  <hr id=answer>  \u68a8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/dad38a90-118e-4be4-8208-4da33bff1a70/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u68a8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u68a8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6843", "id": "1437894575447", "back": "\u6843 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/84a98e1b-a990-4276-a003-0746b0b1e1ba/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6843\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6843\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00e0o (peach)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00e0o (peach)", "id": "1437894575448", "back": "\u0111\u00e0o (peach)  <hr id=answer>  \u6843 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/84a98e1b-a990-4276-a003-0746b0b1e1ba/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6843\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6843\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8393", "id": "1437894604695", "back": "\u8393 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/e1019f38-93f2-44a4-aafb-479e97c1b159/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8393\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8393\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u00f4i (Th\u1ea3o m\u00f4i: strawberry)"}, {"front": "m\u00f4i (Th\u1ea3o m\u00f4i: strawberry)", "id": "1437894604696", "back": "m\u00f4i (Th\u1ea3o m\u00f4i: strawberry)  <hr id=answer>  \u8393 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/e1019f38-93f2-44a4-aafb-479e97c1b159/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8393\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8393\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8c46", "id": "1437894627998", "back": "\u8c46 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/74f17acb-488a-4112-97fb-3adc14ccbb19/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c46\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c46\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1eadu (pea)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1eadu (pea)", "id": "1437894627999", "back": "\u0111\u1eadu (pea)  <hr id=answer>  \u8c46 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/74f17acb-488a-4112-97fb-3adc14ccbb19/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c46\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c46\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8304", "id": "1437894700572", "back": "\u8304 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/d2709b63-e088-4a24-9349-b0087a03869e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8304\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8304\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gia (ba gia: tomato, transcription sound)"}, {"front": "gia (ba gia: tomato, transcription sound)", "id": "1437894700573", "back": "gia (ba gia: tomato, transcription sound)  <hr id=answer>  \u8304 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/d2709b63-e088-4a24-9349-b0087a03869e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8304\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8304\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u89d2", "id": "1437894815478", "back": "\u89d2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/78eb19ca-594a-4c90-9ef6-b55154323aae/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u89d2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u89d2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u00e1c (horn, angle/-gon,&nbsp;L\u01b0\u1ee3ng t\u1eeb: \u0111\u1ebfm s\u1ed1 tr\u00e2u, b\u00f2,&nbsp;h\u00e0o, c\u1eafc,&nbsp;c\u00f4ng v\u0103n)"}, {"front": "gi\u00e1c (horn, angle/-gon,&nbsp;L\u01b0\u1ee3ng t\u1eeb: \u0111\u1ebfm s\u1ed1 tr\u00e2u, b\u00f2,&nbsp;h\u00e0o, c\u1eafc,&nbsp;c\u00f4ng v\u0103n)", "id": "1437894815479", "back": "gi\u00e1c (horn, angle/-gon,&nbsp;L\u01b0\u1ee3ng t\u1eeb: \u0111\u1ebfm s\u1ed1 tr\u00e2u, b\u00f2,&nbsp;h\u00e0o, c\u1eafc,&nbsp;c\u00f4ng v\u0103n)  <hr id=answer>  \u89d2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/78eb19ca-594a-4c90-9ef6-b55154323aae/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u89d2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u89d2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f20", "id": "1437894922465", "back": "\u4f20 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/450ef584-dfe4-4444-8774-4ddf3e5bdbcd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f20\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f20\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  truy\u1ec1n (transfer, pass along), truy\u1ec7n (V\u0103n gi\u1ea3i th\u00edch,&nbsp;V\u0103n k\u1ec3 chuy\u1ec7n)"}, {"front": "truy\u1ec1n (transfer, pass along), truy\u1ec7n (V\u0103n gi\u1ea3i th\u00edch,&nbsp;V\u0103n k\u1ec3 chuy\u1ec7n)", "id": "1437894922466", "back": "truy\u1ec1n (transfer, pass along), truy\u1ec7n (V\u0103n gi\u1ea3i th\u00edch,&nbsp;V\u0103n k\u1ec3 chuy\u1ec7n)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f20 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/450ef584-dfe4-4444-8774-4ddf3e5bdbcd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f20\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f20\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u578b", "id": "1437894952178", "back": "\u578b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/dc0e0674-a26f-4b2f-bb4e-abe5bb629fc8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u578b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u578b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u00ecnh (shape/form/model)"}, {"front": "h\u00ecnh (shape/form/model)", "id": "1437894952179", "back": "h\u00ecnh (shape/form/model)  <hr id=answer>  \u578b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/dc0e0674-a26f-4b2f-bb4e-abe5bb629fc8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u578b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u578b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6c0f", "id": "1437895031245", "back": "\u6c0f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/567fc8ac-bb37-4f3f-a044-6f40ae0d0a6f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c0f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c0f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ecb (middle name for women; suffix for some names)"}, {"front": "th\u1ecb (middle name for women; suffix for some names)", "id": "1437895031247", "back": "th\u1ecb (middle name for women; suffix for some names)  <hr id=answer>  \u6c0f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/567fc8ac-bb37-4f3f-a044-6f40ae0d0a6f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c0f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c0f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9093", "id": "1437895055536", "back": "\u9093 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/fec69cab-5413-4aa1-8ad8-2f506e688719/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9093\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9093\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1eb7ng (last name)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1eb7ng (last name)", "id": "1437895055537", "back": "\u0111\u1eb7ng (last name)  <hr id=answer>  \u9093 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/fec69cab-5413-4aa1-8ad8-2f506e688719/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9093\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9093\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5cfb", "id": "1437895131025", "back": "\u5cfb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/d9d4df8c-4338-4e8d-9fa5-118a085ab2d5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5cfb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5cfb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tu\u1ea5n (Cao, L\u1edbn)"}, {"front": "tu\u1ea5n (Cao, L\u1edbn)", "id": "1437895131026", "back": "tu\u1ea5n (Cao, L\u1edbn)  <hr id=answer>  \u5cfb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/d9d4df8c-4338-4e8d-9fa5-118a085ab2d5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5cfb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5cfb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u601d", "id": "1439192243192", "back": "\u601d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/416dfea8-4ce5-481a-9547-3569fd584c1a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u601d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u601d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u01b0, t\u1ee9 (think/feeling, meaning)"}, {"front": "t\u01b0, t\u1ee9 (think/feeling, meaning)", "id": "1439192243194", "back": "t\u01b0, t\u1ee9 (think/feeling, meaning)  <hr id=answer>  \u601d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/416dfea8-4ce5-481a-9547-3569fd584c1a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u601d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u601d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7ea2", "id": "1439192289020", "back": "\u7ea2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/323ba54b-21b8-4d1c-b653-62b9f18931c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ea2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ea2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ed3ng (red)"}, {"front": "h\u1ed3ng (red)", "id": "1439192289021", "back": "h\u1ed3ng (red)  <hr id=answer>  \u7ea2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/323ba54b-21b8-4d1c-b653-62b9f18931c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ea2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ea2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u67ff", "id": "1439192313712", "back": "\u67ff <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/bf1a2a74-9979-4962-b4c8-d166b25e6541/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u67ff\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u67ff\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ecb (C\u00e2y h\u1ed3ng)"}, {"front": "th\u1ecb (C\u00e2y h\u1ed3ng)", "id": "1439192313713", "back": "th\u1ecb (C\u00e2y h\u1ed3ng)  <hr id=answer>  \u67ff <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/bf1a2a74-9979-4962-b4c8-d166b25e6541/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u67ff\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u67ff\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u83dc", "id": "1439192363522", "back": "\u83dc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/143d6020-1ffe-4956-a6ff-19991f5d86a9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u83dc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u83dc\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00e1i (dish/food, rau c\u1ecf \u0103n \u0111\u01b0\u1ee3c)"}, {"front": "th\u00e1i (dish/food, rau c\u1ecf \u0103n \u0111\u01b0\u1ee3c)", "id": "1439192363523", "back": "th\u00e1i (dish/food, rau c\u1ecf \u0103n \u0111\u01b0\u1ee3c)  <hr id=answer>  \u83dc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/143d6020-1ffe-4956-a6ff-19991f5d86a9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u83dc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u83dc\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8471", "id": "1439192387776", "back": "\u8471 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a5c7f176-03fd-4683-8f82-32b3f52526dd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8471\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8471\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00f4ng (H\u00e0nh)"}, {"front": "th\u00f4ng (H\u00e0nh)", "id": "1439192387777", "back": "th\u00f4ng (H\u00e0nh)  <hr id=answer>  \u8471 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a5c7f176-03fd-4683-8f82-32b3f52526dd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8471\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8471\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5211", "id": "1439192510583", "back": "\u5211 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/9a996c7b-3c2f-4be5-a0ad-94b6f104462d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5211\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5211\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u00ecnh (punishment, law/crime)"}, {"front": "h\u00ecnh (punishment, law/crime)", "id": "1439192510584", "back": "h\u00ecnh (punishment, law/crime)  <hr id=answer>  \u5211 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/9a996c7b-3c2f-4be5-a0ad-94b6f104462d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5211\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5211\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u77db", "id": "1439192548492", "back": "\u77db <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/16ca1f9a-0dd8-4391-b263-32312236d7f6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u77db\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u77db\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u00e2u (gi\u00e1o, c\u00e1n d\u00e0i c\u00f3 m\u0169i nh\u1ecdn)"}, {"front": "m\u00e2u (gi\u00e1o, c\u00e1n d\u00e0i c\u00f3 m\u0169i nh\u1ecdn)", "id": "1439192548494", "back": "m\u00e2u (gi\u00e1o, c\u00e1n d\u00e0i c\u00f3 m\u0169i nh\u1ecdn)  <hr id=answer>  \u77db <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/16ca1f9a-0dd8-4391-b263-32312236d7f6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u77db\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u77db\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u77de", "id": "1439192589260", "back": "\u77de <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5054dbb9-ab32-4b41-af69-605a43c89c34/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u77de\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u77de\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  du\u1eadt (R\u1ef1c r\u1ee1, t\u1ed1t \u0111\u1eb9p)"}, {"front": "du\u1eadt (R\u1ef1c r\u1ee1, t\u1ed1t \u0111\u1eb9p)", "id": "1439192589261", "back": "du\u1eadt (R\u1ef1c r\u1ee1, t\u1ed1t \u0111\u1eb9p)  <hr id=answer>  \u77de <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5054dbb9-ab32-4b41-af69-605a43c89c34/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u77de\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u77de\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5146", "id": "1439192666130", "back": "\u5146 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d77a4663-5ca8-404c-8e73-e509c5915727/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5146\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5146\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tri\u1ec7u (million;&nbsp;v\u1eb1n hi\u1ec7n ra tr\u00ean mai r\u00f9a,&nbsp;\u0110i\u1ec1m)"}, {"front": "tri\u1ec7u (million;&nbsp;v\u1eb1n hi\u1ec7n ra tr\u00ean mai r\u00f9a,&nbsp;\u0110i\u1ec1m)", "id": "1439192666131", "back": "tri\u1ec7u (million;&nbsp;v\u1eb1n hi\u1ec7n ra tr\u00ean mai r\u00f9a,&nbsp;\u0110i\u1ec1m)  <hr id=answer>  \u5146 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d77a4663-5ca8-404c-8e73-e509c5915727/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5146\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5146\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5199", "id": "1439192719133", "back": "\u5199 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/342b8723-fb4f-47ba-8b40-3e4a02c56df2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5199\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5199\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ea3 (Mi\u00eau t\u1ea3; writing)"}, {"front": "t\u1ea3 (Mi\u00eau t\u1ea3; writing)", "id": "1439192719134", "back": "t\u1ea3 (Mi\u00eau t\u1ea3; writing)  <hr id=answer>  \u5199 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/342b8723-fb4f-47ba-8b40-3e4a02c56df2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5199\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5199\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8ba4", "id": "1439192752589", "back": "\u8ba4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/89e6e01c-745e-4f7c-a98a-92ba9b43f6d8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8ba4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8ba4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nh\u1eadn (recognize, admit)<div>\u8a8d</div>"}, {"front": "nh\u1eadn (recognize, admit)<div>\u8a8d</div>", "id": "1439192752590", "back": "nh\u1eadn (recognize, admit)<div>\u8a8d</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8ba4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/89e6e01c-745e-4f7c-a98a-92ba9b43f6d8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8ba4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8ba4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8282", "id": "1439192886634", "back": "\u8282 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/39c6d838-2034-4b06-8928-e1f5c79418e7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8282\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8282\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u1ebft (holiday;&nbsp;L\u1ec5 nghi; details; section/period/part)<div>\u7bc0</div>"}, {"front": "ti\u1ebft (holiday;&nbsp;L\u1ec5 nghi; details; section/period/part)<div>\u7bc0</div>", "id": "1439192886635", "back": "ti\u1ebft (holiday;&nbsp;L\u1ec5 nghi; details; section/period/part)<div>\u7bc0</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8282 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/39c6d838-2034-4b06-8928-e1f5c79418e7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8282\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8282\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5df3", "id": "1439192923191", "back": "\u5df3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/71da0233-f8a6-4924-8c1a-6c273eeb62cb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5df3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5df3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ecb (chi th\u1ee9 s\u00e1u trong m\u01b0\u1eddi hai chi;&nbsp;ch\u00edn gi\u1edd s\u00e1ng \u0111\u1ebfn m\u01b0\u1eddi m\u1ed9t gi\u1edd tr\u01b0a)"}, {"front": "t\u1ecb (chi th\u1ee9 s\u00e1u trong m\u01b0\u1eddi hai chi;&nbsp;ch\u00edn gi\u1edd s\u00e1ng \u0111\u1ebfn m\u01b0\u1eddi m\u1ed9t gi\u1edd tr\u01b0a)", "id": "1439192923192", "back": "t\u1ecb (chi th\u1ee9 s\u00e1u trong m\u01b0\u1eddi hai chi;&nbsp;ch\u00edn gi\u1edd s\u00e1ng \u0111\u1ebfn m\u01b0\u1eddi m\u1ed9t gi\u1edd tr\u01b0a)  <hr id=answer>  \u5df3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/71da0233-f8a6-4924-8c1a-6c273eeb62cb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5df3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5df3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7126", "id": "1439192976693", "back": "\u7126 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/ee656939-30bc-4148-8bdd-91ea7649f367/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7126\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7126\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u00eau (B\u1ecb ch\u00e1y, b\u1ecb s\u00e9m l\u1eeda; last name)"}, {"front": "ti\u00eau (B\u1ecb ch\u00e1y, b\u1ecb s\u00e9m l\u1eeda; last name)", "id": "1439192976694", "back": "ti\u00eau (B\u1ecb ch\u00e1y, b\u1ecb s\u00e9m l\u1eeda; last name)  <hr id=answer>  \u7126 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/ee656939-30bc-4148-8bdd-91ea7649f367/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7126\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7126\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u505a", "id": "1439193040197", "back": "\u505a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/1958d313-0816-4205-a49f-801b1749d2e9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u505a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u505a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ed1 (do/make)"}, {"front": "t\u1ed1 (do/make)", "id": "1439193040198", "back": "t\u1ed1 (do/make)  <hr id=answer>  \u505a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/1958d313-0816-4205-a49f-801b1749d2e9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u505a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u505a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bba", "id": "1439193082234", "back": "\u8bba <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/cc5bc2e7-03aa-4d05-b369-21d7739c1757/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bba\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bba\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  lu\u1eadn (discuss, theory)<div>\u8ad6</div>"}, {"front": "lu\u1eadn (discuss, theory)<div>\u8ad6</div>", "id": "1439193082235", "back": "lu\u1eadn (discuss, theory)<div>\u8ad6</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8bba <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/cc5bc2e7-03aa-4d05-b369-21d7739c1757/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bba\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bba\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7591", "id": "1439193135184", "back": "\u7591 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/102c85e2-722a-4507-aa67-4208e1d038e4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7591\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7591\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nghi (suspicious, questioning)"}, {"front": "nghi (suspicious, questioning)", "id": "1439193135185", "back": "nghi (suspicious, questioning)  <hr id=answer>  \u7591 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/102c85e2-722a-4507-aa67-4208e1d038e4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7591\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7591\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e5e", "id": "1439193181132", "back": "\u4e5e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/667be6df-8501-4591-b1a0-2c889cca6726/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e5e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e5e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u1ea5t (beg)"}, {"front": "kh\u1ea5t (beg)", "id": "1439193181133", "back": "kh\u1ea5t (beg)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e5e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/667be6df-8501-4591-b1a0-2c889cca6726/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e5e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e5e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5408", "id": "1439193257599", "back": "\u5408 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/0a254a47-70ea-4902-972d-60e983a7b7d6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5408\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5408\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ee3p (unite, join, gather)"}, {"front": "h\u1ee3p (unite, join, gather)", "id": "1439193257600", "back": "h\u1ee3p (unite, join, gather)  <hr id=answer>  \u5408 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/0a254a47-70ea-4902-972d-60e983a7b7d6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5408\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5408\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u530d", "id": "1439193345806", "back": "\u530d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5960dfed-f3dc-41d5-a2e7-a234aeed29d4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u530d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u530d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ed3 (B\u00f2 (tay ch\u00e2n b\u00f2 l\u00ea tr\u00ean m\u1eb7t \u0111\u1ea5t))"}, {"front": "b\u1ed3 (B\u00f2 (tay ch\u00e2n b\u00f2 l\u00ea tr\u00ean m\u1eb7t \u0111\u1ea5t))", "id": "1439193345807", "back": "b\u1ed3 (B\u00f2 (tay ch\u00e2n b\u00f2 l\u00ea tr\u00ean m\u1eb7t \u0111\u1ea5t))  <hr id=answer>  \u530d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5960dfed-f3dc-41d5-a2e7-a234aeed29d4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u530d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u530d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4eb2", "id": "1439193379798", "back": "\u4eb2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f2322a4b-47e6-4e75-af1e-ce5fdafa539c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4eb2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4eb2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00e2n (relative/related)<div>\u89aa</div>"}, {"front": "th\u00e2n (relative/related)<div>\u89aa</div>", "id": "1439193379799", "back": "th\u00e2n (relative/related)<div>\u89aa</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4eb2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f2322a4b-47e6-4e75-af1e-ce5fdafa539c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4eb2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4eb2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5b69", "id": "1439193416491", "back": "\u5b69 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/bdf1eb18-302a-4d48-a681-c2662c3bb029/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b69\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b69\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u00e0i (child/kid)"}, {"front": "h\u00e0i (child/kid)", "id": "1439193416492", "back": "h\u00e0i (child/kid)  <hr id=answer>  \u5b69 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/bdf1eb18-302a-4d48-a681-c2662c3bb029/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b69\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b69\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u72d7", "id": "1439193436958", "back": "\u72d7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/c7929308-a397-4538-aee9-524a83606ed5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u72d7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u72d7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ea9u (dog)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea9u (dog)", "id": "1439193436959", "back": "c\u1ea9u (dog)  <hr id=answer>  \u72d7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/c7929308-a397-4538-aee9-524a83606ed5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u72d7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u72d7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u732b", "id": "1439193457536", "back": "\u732b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f66ef371-9479-4b87-8992-e505f9bc46a2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u732b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u732b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  mi\u00eau (cat)"}, {"front": "mi\u00eau (cat)", "id": "1439193457537", "back": "mi\u00eau (cat)  <hr id=answer>  \u732b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f66ef371-9479-4b87-8992-e505f9bc46a2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u732b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u732b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f5c", "id": "1439193501516", "back": "\u4f5c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/852b0d81-55c4-40ab-9699-3fb5dd899f7c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f5c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f5c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00e1c (do/make/execute)"}, {"front": "t\u00e1c (do/make/execute)", "id": "1439193501517", "back": "t\u00e1c (do/make/execute)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f5c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/852b0d81-55c4-40ab-9699-3fb5dd899f7c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f5c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f5c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u533b", "id": "1439193548724", "back": "\u533b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/059889f4-eacd-41be-933c-b18248731bad/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u533b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u533b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  y (medical/medicine)<div>\u91ab</div>"}, {"front": "y (medical/medicine)<div>\u91ab</div>", "id": "1439193548725", "back": "y (medical/medicine)<div>\u91ab</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u533b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/059889f4-eacd-41be-933c-b18248731bad/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u533b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u533b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5019", "id": "1439193632137", "back": "\u5019 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/9fe0a608-0175-4d57-baf1-26151cc399fa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5019\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5019\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1eadu (wait/expect; visit/greet; B\u00f3i;&nbsp;Kh\u00ed h\u1eadu; th\u00e1m v\u1ecdng)"}, {"front": "h\u1eadu (wait/expect; visit/greet; B\u00f3i;&nbsp;Kh\u00ed h\u1eadu; th\u00e1m v\u1ecdng)", "id": "1439193632138", "back": "h\u1eadu (wait/expect; visit/greet; B\u00f3i;&nbsp;Kh\u00ed h\u1eadu; th\u00e1m v\u1ecdng)  <hr id=answer>  \u5019 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/9fe0a608-0175-4d57-baf1-26151cc399fa/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5019\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5019\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8dd1", "id": "1439193664781", "back": "\u8dd1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/223374dd-b5c2-4cdf-968d-5d54d4d82b63/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8dd1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8dd1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00e0o (flee, go/run)"}, {"front": "b\u00e0o (flee, go/run)", "id": "1439193664782", "back": "b\u00e0o (flee, go/run)  <hr id=answer>  \u8dd1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/223374dd-b5c2-4cdf-968d-5d54d4d82b63/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8dd1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8dd1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7a7a", "id": "1439193739169", "back": "\u7a7a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/58572497-db1e-46e8-b817-237aa97ac600/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7a7a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7a7a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u00f4ng (empty/vacuum, sky/universe)"}, {"front": "kh\u00f4ng (empty/vacuum, sky/universe)", "id": "1439193739170", "back": "kh\u00f4ng (empty/vacuum, sky/universe)  <hr id=answer>  \u7a7a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/58572497-db1e-46e8-b817-237aa97ac600/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7a7a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7a7a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5f71", "id": "1439193770023", "back": "\u5f71 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/8f63d02b-8959-4d74-a17d-261c57cd1fbf/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f71\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f71\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u1ea3nh (picture)"}, {"front": "\u1ea3nh (picture)", "id": "1439193770024", "back": "\u1ea3nh (picture)  <hr id=answer>  \u5f71 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/8f63d02b-8959-4d74-a17d-261c57cd1fbf/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f71\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f71\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4fbf", "id": "1439193824289", "back": "\u4fbf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/4676367c-9996-40da-9536-476e9d8a3404/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4fbf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4fbf\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u1ec7n (ordinary/plain, convenient)"}, {"front": "ti\u1ec7n (ordinary/plain, convenient)", "id": "1439193824290", "back": "ti\u1ec7n (ordinary/plain, convenient)  <hr id=answer>  \u4fbf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/4676367c-9996-40da-9536-476e9d8a3404/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4fbf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4fbf\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5b9c", "id": "1439193890409", "back": "\u5b9c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/520058fa-aafb-41cb-8697-aa3afcb94a09/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b9c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b9c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nghi (harmony, suitable)"}, {"front": "nghi (harmony, suitable)", "id": "1439193890410", "back": "nghi (harmony, suitable)  <hr id=answer>  \u5b9c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/520058fa-aafb-41cb-8697-aa3afcb94a09/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b9c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b9c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8111", "id": "1439193922140", "back": "\u8111 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/26db1833-bcc1-4912-b316-84c3f749f780/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8111\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8111\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  n\u00e3o (brain)<div>\u8166&nbsp;</div>"}, {"front": "n\u00e3o (brain)<div>\u8166&nbsp;</div>", "id": "1439193922141", "back": "n\u00e3o (brain)<div>\u8166&nbsp;</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8111 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/26db1833-bcc1-4912-b316-84c3f749f780/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8111\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8111\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bfb", "id": "1439329772767", "back": "\u8bfb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/fe1e1807-4229-49d1-b435-96eba212904f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bfb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bfb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ed9c (read/study)<div>\u8b80</div>"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ed9c (read/study)<div>\u8b80</div>", "id": "1439329772768", "back": "\u0111\u1ed9c (read/study)<div>\u8b80</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8bfb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/fe1e1807-4229-49d1-b435-96eba212904f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bfb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bfb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7ec3", "id": "1439329807473", "back": "\u7ec3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/6a3b8d68-19cc-4b30-b1c5-9c2754fe9a6b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ec3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ec3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  luy\u1ec7n (practice)"}, {"front": "luy\u1ec7n (practice)", "id": "1439329807474", "back": "luy\u1ec7n (practice)  <hr id=answer>  \u7ec3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/6a3b8d68-19cc-4b30-b1c5-9c2754fe9a6b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ec3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ec3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5b83", "id": "1439329883645", "back": "\u5b83 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e5ed04e2-a536-46f1-8ced-014c471aaea3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b83\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b83\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tha (it, pronoun for things), \u0111\u00e0 (camel)"}, {"front": "tha (it, pronoun for things), \u0111\u00e0 (camel)", "id": "1439329883646", "back": "tha (it, pronoun for things), \u0111\u00e0 (camel)  <hr id=answer>  \u5b83 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e5ed04e2-a536-46f1-8ced-014c471aaea3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b83\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b83\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u52a9", "id": "1439329909381", "back": "\u52a9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/8c263482-704c-4cc6-93ae-e57b1d6bd1a4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52a9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52a9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u1ee3 (help/assist)"}, {"front": "tr\u1ee3 (help/assist)", "id": "1439329909382", "back": "tr\u1ee3 (help/assist)  <hr id=answer>  \u52a9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/8c263482-704c-4cc6-93ae-e57b1d6bd1a4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52a9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52a9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9662", "id": "1439329973542", "back": "\u9662 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/c921e2f0-b502-4308-b58d-d59ccaad584c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9662\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9662\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  vi\u1ec7n (yard with wall, room, building, academy)"}, {"front": "vi\u1ec7n (yard with wall, room, building, academy)", "id": "1439329973543", "back": "vi\u1ec7n (yard with wall, room, building, academy)  <hr id=answer>  \u9662 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/c921e2f0-b502-4308-b58d-d59ccaad584c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9662\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9662\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u79bb", "id": "1439330032159", "back": "\u79bb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/9459c30b-ad98-4a00-a103-35c9a21c258b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79bb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79bb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  li (split, leave)<div>\u96e2</div>"}, {"front": "li (split, leave)<div>\u96e2</div>", "id": "1439330032160", "back": "li (split, leave)<div>\u96e2</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u79bb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/9459c30b-ad98-4a00-a103-35c9a21c258b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79bb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79bb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5f80", "id": "1439330114039", "back": "\u5f80 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/ec5a2d68-2406-4de9-8262-27c82e834638/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f80\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f80\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u00e3ng (go toward/visit; past/gone)"}, {"front": "v\u00e3ng (go toward/visit; past/gone)", "id": "1439330114040", "back": "v\u00e3ng (go toward/visit; past/gone)  <hr id=answer>  \u5f80 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/ec5a2d68-2406-4de9-8262-27c82e834638/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f80\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f80\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8857", "id": "1439330193953", "back": "\u8857 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/26d86da2-4879-4dac-a888-806bf64e60d1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8857\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8857\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nhai (street/boulevard)"}, {"front": "nhai (street/boulevard)", "id": "1439330193954", "back": "nhai (street/boulevard)  <hr id=answer>  \u8857 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/26d86da2-4879-4dac-a888-806bf64e60d1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8857\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8857\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8fd1", "id": "1439330222389", "back": "\u8fd1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a1580d47-0ee4-4ecf-9dca-d472eb3c3914/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fd1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fd1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1eadn (near)"}, {"front": "c\u1eadn (near)", "id": "1439330222390", "back": "c\u1eadn (near)  <hr id=answer>  \u8fd1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a1580d47-0ee4-4ecf-9dca-d472eb3c3914/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fd1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fd1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f4f", "id": "1439330348092", "back": "\u4f4f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/c6f37a32-7eca-44f1-b503-686ba4f12ed4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f4f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f4f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u1ee5, tr\u00fa (stay/live)"}, {"front": "tr\u1ee5, tr\u00fa (stay/live)", "id": "1439330348093", "back": "tr\u1ee5, tr\u00fa (stay/live)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f4f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/c6f37a32-7eca-44f1-b503-686ba4f12ed4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f4f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f4f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u94c1", "id": "1439330416188", "back": "\u94c1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/aa3bc84e-43e1-4913-a912-de46d7301a58/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u94c1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u94c1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thi\u1ebft (iron)<div>\u9435</div>"}, {"front": "thi\u1ebft (iron)<div>\u9435</div>", "id": "1439330416189", "back": "thi\u1ebft (iron)<div>\u9435</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u94c1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/aa3bc84e-43e1-4913-a912-de46d7301a58/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u94c1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u94c1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5df2", "id": "1439330505816", "back": "\u5df2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/68e0d7d0-a93d-4a26-a1ba-d75da700b383/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5df2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5df2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u0129 (already/finished/done; then, afterwards)"}, {"front": "d\u0129 (already/finished/done; then, afterwards)", "id": "1439330505817", "back": "d\u0129 (already/finished/done; then, afterwards)  <hr id=answer>  \u5df2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/68e0d7d0-a93d-4a26-a1ba-d75da700b383/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5df2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5df2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6d77", "id": "1439330539859", "back": "\u6d77 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/620b4e8b-b780-4413-9bf6-1d172839b0c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d77\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d77\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ea3i (sea)"}, {"front": "h\u1ea3i (sea)", "id": "1439330539860", "back": "h\u1ea3i (sea)  <hr id=answer>  \u6d77 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/620b4e8b-b780-4413-9bf6-1d172839b0c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d77\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d77\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6d3b", "id": "1439330585561", "back": "\u6d3b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/60ee55eb-4512-4984-a553-4acf9303d064/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d3b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d3b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ho\u1ea1t (lively, active)"}, {"front": "ho\u1ea1t (lively, active)", "id": "1439330585562", "back": "ho\u1ea1t (lively, active)  <hr id=answer>  \u6d3b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/60ee55eb-4512-4984-a553-4acf9303d064/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d3b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d3b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8fd0", "id": "1439330641707", "back": "\u8fd0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d5cdbc7b-e1e1-48e5-be33-db8b474ede5a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fd0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fd0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u1eadn (move, transport)<div>\u904b</div>"}, {"front": "v\u1eadn (move, transport)<div>\u904b</div>", "id": "1439330641708", "back": "v\u1eadn (move, transport)<div>\u904b</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8fd0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d5cdbc7b-e1e1-48e5-be33-db8b474ede5a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8fd0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8fd0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5f97", "id": "1439514222031", "back": "\u5f97 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b3b819c2-1aa2-41ef-87a6-97c4e8bf8d94/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f97\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f97\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1eafc (get, win/achieve)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1eafc (get, win/achieve)", "id": "1439514222032", "back": "\u0111\u1eafc (get, win/achieve)  <hr id=answer>  \u5f97 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b3b819c2-1aa2-41ef-87a6-97c4e8bf8d94/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f97\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f97\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6c7d", "id": "1439514240937", "back": "\u6c7d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5ab6ed0e-25be-42aa-9f0c-269b6dea8186/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c7d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c7d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u00ed (steam)"}, {"front": "kh\u00ed (steam)", "id": "1439514240938", "back": "kh\u00ed (steam)  <hr id=answer>  \u6c7d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5ab6ed0e-25be-42aa-9f0c-269b6dea8186/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c7d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c7d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6216", "id": "1439514449654", "back": "\u6216 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/dc800a22-9e5f-4aa8-9141-61577f284077/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6216\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6216\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ho\u1eb7c (or, maybe, if)"}, {"front": "ho\u1eb7c (or, maybe, if)", "id": "1439514449655", "back": "ho\u1eb7c (or, maybe, if)  <hr id=answer>  \u6216 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/dc800a22-9e5f-4aa8-9141-61577f284077/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6216\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6216\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7ad9", "id": "1439514475447", "back": "\u7ad9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/fd3d8ea3-fd79-4865-8be7-1b0b00b6ec26/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ad9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ad9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u1ea1m (station, stand)"}, {"front": "tr\u1ea1m (station, stand)", "id": "1439514475448", "back": "tr\u1ea1m (station, stand)  <hr id=answer>  \u7ad9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/fd3d8ea3-fd79-4865-8be7-1b0b00b6ec26/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ad9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ad9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u666e", "id": "1439514501929", "back": "\u666e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/37f2bad6-6be7-40ff-8534-5f7a2c467330/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u666e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u666e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u1ed5 (common/general/universal; Prussia)"}, {"front": "ph\u1ed5 (common/general/universal; Prussia)", "id": "1439514501930", "back": "ph\u1ed5 (common/general/universal; Prussia)  <hr id=answer>  \u666e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/37f2bad6-6be7-40ff-8534-5f7a2c467330/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u666e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u666e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u901a", "id": "1439514554091", "back": "\u901a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/bafefc2b-d9aa-4afe-86ac-86fba6b54a50/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u901a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u901a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00f4ng (passage, know/knowledgeable)"}, {"front": "th\u00f4ng (passage, know/knowledgeable)", "id": "1439514554092", "back": "th\u00f4ng (passage, know/knowledgeable)  <hr id=answer>  \u901a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/bafefc2b-d9aa-4afe-86ac-86fba6b54a50/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u901a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u901a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6e2f", "id": "1439514580918", "back": "\u6e2f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a3afb899-708a-4898-9a4d-121c70b5ea30/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6e2f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6e2f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ea3ng (harbor, Hong Kong)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea3ng (harbor, Hong Kong)", "id": "1439514580919", "back": "c\u1ea3ng (harbor, Hong Kong)  <hr id=answer>  \u6e2f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a3afb899-708a-4898-9a4d-121c70b5ea30/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6e2f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6e2f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u61c2", "id": "1439514610753", "back": "\u61c2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b4a92402-ab95-4f30-9429-ba4b8a1abefc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u61c2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u61c2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ed5ng (understand)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ed5ng (understand)", "id": "1439514610754", "back": "\u0111\u1ed5ng (understand)  <hr id=answer>  \u61c2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b4a92402-ab95-4f30-9429-ba4b8a1abefc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u61c2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u61c2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8c03", "id": "1439514728803", "back": "\u8c03 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/867633e8-4a19-40ee-a055-55fb17711798/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c03\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c03\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111i\u1ec1u, \u0111i\u1ec7u (arrange/transfer/move, investigate, tune/tone/melody)"}, {"front": "\u0111i\u1ec1u, \u0111i\u1ec7u (arrange/transfer/move, investigate, tune/tone/melody)", "id": "1439514728804", "back": "\u0111i\u1ec1u, \u0111i\u1ec7u (arrange/transfer/move, investigate, tune/tone/melody)  <hr id=answer>  \u8c03 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/867633e8-4a19-40ee-a055-55fb17711798/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c03\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c03\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u62fc", "id": "1439514762314", "back": "\u62fc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e7beff75-8bf7-4293-b62e-892d7160eb52/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u62fc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u62fc\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00ednh (connect, arrange, piece together, spell, at the risk of one's life)"}, {"front": "b\u00ednh (connect, arrange, piece together, spell, at the risk of one's life)", "id": "1439514762315", "back": "b\u00ednh (connect, arrange, piece together, spell, at the risk of one's life)  <hr id=answer>  \u62fc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e7beff75-8bf7-4293-b62e-892d7160eb52/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u62fc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u62fc\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7b2c", "id": "1439798020356", "back": "\u7b2c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/879269bb-cd2f-4745-b9ea-0ab0fd815a65/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b2c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b2c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ec7 (rank)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ec7 (rank)", "id": "1439798020357", "back": "\u0111\u1ec7 (rank)  <hr id=answer>  \u7b2c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/879269bb-cd2f-4745-b9ea-0ab0fd815a65/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b2c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b2c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u611f", "id": "1439798067298", "back": "\u611f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/36078213-3111-4a04-84a3-9f2067717881/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u611f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u611f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ea3m (feeling)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea3m (feeling)", "id": "1439798067299", "back": "c\u1ea3m (feeling)  <hr id=answer>  \u611f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/36078213-3111-4a04-84a3-9f2067717881/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u611f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u611f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5174", "id": "1439800453851", "back": "\u5174 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/09280041-7085-4f30-9cfa-4b0f35619198/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5174\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5174\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u01b0ng, h\u1ee9ng (prosper, interest)<div>\u8208</div>"}, {"front": "h\u01b0ng, h\u1ee9ng (prosper, interest)<div>\u8208</div>", "id": "1439800453852", "back": "h\u01b0ng, h\u1ee9ng (prosper, interest)<div>\u8208</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5174 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/09280041-7085-4f30-9cfa-4b0f35619198/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5174\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5174\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8da3", "id": "1440320360549", "back": "\u8da3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/8c6de2c6-b262-4ba7-9682-a81706196976/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8da3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8da3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00fa (interest)"}, {"front": "th\u00fa (interest)", "id": "1440320360550", "back": "th\u00fa (interest)  <hr id=answer>  \u8da3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/8c6de2c6-b262-4ba7-9682-a81706196976/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8da3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8da3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9a8c", "id": "1440320434128", "back": "\u9a8c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e9c1d706-008d-4640-a955-ee6e0f5ddff3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9a8c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9a8c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nghi\u1ec7m (evidence, examine, testing/symptom)<div><br /><div>\u9a57</div></div>"}, {"front": "nghi\u1ec7m (evidence, examine, testing/symptom)<div><br /><div>\u9a57</div></div>", "id": "1440320434129", "back": "nghi\u1ec7m (evidence, examine, testing/symptom)<div><br /><div>\u9a57</div></div>  <hr id=answer>  \u9a8c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e9c1d706-008d-4640-a955-ee6e0f5ddff3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9a8c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9a8c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6d41", "id": "1440320533723", "back": "\u6d41 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/4554d1d2-3156-4e79-a63c-edad81b90b58/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d41\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d41\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u01b0u (stream, flow, class)"}, {"front": "l\u01b0u (stream, flow, class)", "id": "1440320533724", "back": "l\u01b0u (stream, flow, class)  <hr id=answer>  \u6d41 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/4554d1d2-3156-4e79-a63c-edad81b90b58/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d41\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d41\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5efa", "id": "1440320582758", "back": "\u5efa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/96b0e9f6-f8b0-4fa2-bf43-89fc59485da7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5efa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5efa\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ki\u1ebfn (architect, build)"}, {"front": "ki\u1ebfn (architect, build)", "id": "1440320582759", "back": "ki\u1ebfn (architect, build)  <hr id=answer>  \u5efa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/96b0e9f6-f8b0-4fa2-bf43-89fc59485da7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5efa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5efa\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bae", "id": "1440320611088", "back": "\u8bae <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/c35cbb8d-5384-4cec-87e2-101ccea2d9a4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bae\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bae\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u8b70 ngh\u1ecb (discuss)"}, {"front": "\u8b70 ngh\u1ecb (discuss)", "id": "1440320611089", "back": "\u8b70 ngh\u1ecb (discuss)  <hr id=answer>  \u8bae <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/c35cbb8d-5384-4cec-87e2-101ccea2d9a4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bae\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bae\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8ddf", "id": "1440320706371", "back": "\u8ddf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/20ae96d6-5877-4628-85eb-d94d87b7c7d2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8ddf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8ddf\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00e2n, ng\u00e2n (heel, follow, toward)"}, {"front": "c\u00e2n, ng\u00e2n (heel, follow, toward)", "id": "1440320706372", "back": "c\u00e2n, ng\u00e2n (heel, follow, toward)  <hr id=answer>  \u8ddf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/20ae96d6-5877-4628-85eb-d94d87b7c7d2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8ddf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8ddf\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bc9", "id": "1440320765108", "back": "\u8bc9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/314f2344-4877-4f9c-9074-da2e92d5536f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bc9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bc9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  <div>\u8a34 t\u1ed1 (accuse, tell)</div>"}, {"front": "<div>\u8a34 t\u1ed1 (accuse, tell)</div>", "id": "1440320765109", "back": "<div>\u8a34 t\u1ed1 (accuse, tell)</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8bc9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/314f2344-4877-4f9c-9074-da2e92d5536f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bc9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bc9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bb2", "id": "1440320816054", "back": "\u8bb2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/27b86bc9-5573-406a-8b12-8511a22e1012/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bb2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bb2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u8b1b gi\u1ea3ng (explain)"}, {"front": "\u8b1b gi\u1ea3ng (explain)", "id": "1440320816055", "back": "\u8b1b gi\u1ea3ng (explain)  <hr id=answer>  \u8bb2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/27b86bc9-5573-406a-8b12-8511a22e1012/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bb2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bb2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9519", "id": "1440320872085", "back": "\u9519 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/634049e6-31f4-4810-8b8f-7eed94e12882/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9519\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9519\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00e1c (mistake)"}, {"front": "th\u00e1c (mistake)", "id": "1440320872086", "back": "th\u00e1c (mistake)  <hr id=answer>  \u9519 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/634049e6-31f4-4810-8b8f-7eed94e12882/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9519\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9519\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6539", "id": "1440320903605", "back": "\u6539 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/aa1b1e17-27b3-4559-b9dd-714a144eb368/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6539\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6539\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ea3i (change)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea3i (change)", "id": "1440320903606", "back": "c\u1ea3i (change)  <hr id=answer>  \u6539 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/aa1b1e17-27b3-4559-b9dd-714a144eb368/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6539\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6539\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8f85", "id": "1440320961924", "back": "\u8f85 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/170feb8e-c250-4a10-8690-e12abec62bd2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8f85\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8f85\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u1ee5 (assist/help)"}, {"front": "ph\u1ee5 (assist/help)", "id": "1440320961925", "back": "ph\u1ee5 (assist/help)  <hr id=answer>  \u8f85 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/170feb8e-c250-4a10-8690-e12abec62bd2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8f85\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8f85\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5bfc", "id": "1440321115694", "back": "\u5bfc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/6e56cdce-7c25-4135-a3f9-73d5a6cbe1e5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bfc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bfc\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  <div>\u5c0e \u0111\u1ea1o (guide)</div>"}, {"front": "<div>\u5c0e \u0111\u1ea1o (guide)</div>", "id": "1440321115696", "back": "<div>\u5c0e \u0111\u1ea1o (guide)</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5bfc <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/6e56cdce-7c25-4135-a3f9-73d5a6cbe1e5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bfc\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bfc\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6c42", "id": "1440321415255", "back": "\u6c42 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a5c4d9a0-4b1a-488f-987b-9a4edf485ba9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c42\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c42\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ea7u (seek)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea7u (seek)", "id": "1440321415256", "back": "c\u1ea7u (seek)  <hr id=answer>  \u6c42 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a5c4d9a0-4b1a-488f-987b-9a4edf485ba9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c42\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c42\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u786e", "id": "1440321467424", "back": "\u786e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/05eff281-41bb-4136-b913-f8e03328628b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u786e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u786e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u00e1c (verify, true/certain/solid)"}, {"front": "x\u00e1c (verify, true/certain/solid)", "id": "1440321467425", "back": "x\u00e1c (verify, true/certain/solid)  <hr id=answer>  \u786e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/05eff281-41bb-4136-b913-f8e03328628b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u786e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u786e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7406", "id": "1440321546592", "back": "\u7406 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/fe6b9845-ac2a-4ac4-94b8-0bdd645b9469/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7406\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7406\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u00ed (take care, reason/logic, physics/natural law)"}, {"front": "l\u00ed (take care, reason/logic, physics/natural law)", "id": "1440321546593", "back": "l\u00ed (take care, reason/logic, physics/natural law)  <hr id=answer>  \u7406 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/fe6b9845-ac2a-4ac4-94b8-0bdd645b9469/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7406\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7406\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6b4c", "id": "1440321564171", "back": "\u6b4c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/df503395-caf5-41cc-b051-f15e228adf03/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b4c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b4c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ca (sing, song)"}, {"front": "ca (sing, song)", "id": "1440321564172", "back": "ca (sing, song)  <hr id=answer>  \u6b4c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/df503395-caf5-41cc-b051-f15e228adf03/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b4c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b4c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f46", "id": "1440321621826", "back": "\u4f46 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/83585a52-7b29-43c0-84a7-bad19c433c67/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f46\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f46\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00e3n (but)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00e3n (but)", "id": "1440321621827", "back": "\u0111\u00e3n (but)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f46 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/83585a52-7b29-43c0-84a7-bad19c433c67/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f46\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f46\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5531", "id": "1440321649766", "back": "\u5531 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f36f549d-12b1-4e46-b456-ef407381551a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5531\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5531\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u01b0\u1edbng (sing, shout/announce)"}, {"front": "x\u01b0\u1edbng (sing, shout/announce)", "id": "1440321649767", "back": "x\u01b0\u1edbng (sing, shout/announce)  <hr id=answer>  \u5531 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f36f549d-12b1-4e46-b456-ef407381551a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5531\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5531\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4fd7", "id": "1440321696553", "back": "\u4fd7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/6d5ee592-0699-4d97-9ffc-36c54fbd82db/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4fd7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4fd7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ee5c (customs, vulgar)"}, {"front": "t\u1ee5c (customs, vulgar)", "id": "1440321696555", "back": "t\u1ee5c (customs, vulgar)  <hr id=answer>  \u4fd7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/6d5ee592-0699-4d97-9ffc-36c54fbd82db/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4fd7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4fd7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u66f2", "id": "1440321741324", "back": "\u66f2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5130dbcd-64d5-4b21-b8ac-792f4e12e3b6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66f2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66f2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u00fac (turn, bend; numerary for song)"}, {"front": "kh\u00fac (turn, bend; numerary for song)", "id": "1440321741325", "back": "kh\u00fac (turn, bend; numerary for song)  <hr id=answer>  \u66f2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5130dbcd-64d5-4b21-b8ac-792f4e12e3b6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66f2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66f2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5bb9", "id": "1440321876621", "back": "\u5bb9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/70c0ac6a-ea64-4011-907a-54da4a7152be/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bb9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bb9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  dong, dung (contain; face/beauty)"}, {"front": "dong, dung (contain; face/beauty)", "id": "1440321876622", "back": "dong, dung (contain; face/beauty)  <hr id=answer>  \u5bb9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/70c0ac6a-ea64-4011-907a-54da4a7152be/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5bb9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5bb9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u826e", "id": "1440376076855", "back": "\u826e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b5323f72-4e48-45cd-a54f-395d30dbef9f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u826e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u826e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ea5n (blunt, tough, chewy, one of the Eight Trigrams \u516b\u5366 (symbolizing mountain))"}, {"front": "c\u1ea5n (blunt, tough, chewy, one of the Eight Trigrams \u516b\u5366 (symbolizing mountain))", "id": "1440376076856", "back": "c\u1ea5n (blunt, tough, chewy, one of the Eight Trigrams \u516b\u5366 (symbolizing mountain))  <hr id=answer>  \u826e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b5323f72-4e48-45cd-a54f-395d30dbef9f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u826e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u826e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6613", "id": "1440405144541", "back": "\u6613 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b1aa9e2c-ee44-441f-9f55-1090b446dce7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6613\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6613\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u1ecbch (change), d\u1ecb (easy)"}, {"front": "d\u1ecbch (change), d\u1ecb (easy)", "id": "1440405144542", "back": "d\u1ecbch (change), d\u1ecb (easy)  <hr id=answer>  \u6613 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b1aa9e2c-ee44-441f-9f55-1090b446dce7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6613\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6613\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6e7e", "id": "1440405190936", "back": "\u6e7e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/eef6f910-8e58-4022-a7e7-3812ddd7166e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6e7e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6e7e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u7063 loan (bay)"}, {"front": "\u7063 loan (bay)", "id": "1440405190937", "back": "\u7063 loan (bay)  <hr id=answer>  \u6e7e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/eef6f910-8e58-4022-a7e7-3812ddd7166e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6e7e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6e7e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9898", "id": "1440405245902", "back": "\u9898 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/0cf7a76f-6a20-4b3c-be76-7180899d102c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9898\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9898\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ec1 (forehead, headline, topic/essay)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ec1 (forehead, headline, topic/essay)", "id": "1440405245903", "back": "\u0111\u1ec1 (forehead, headline, topic/essay)  <hr id=answer>  \u9898 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/0cf7a76f-6a20-4b3c-be76-7180899d102c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9898\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9898\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4eae", "id": "1440405298407", "back": "\u4eae <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/4e0da3f8-f9e3-4450-9493-723cef9457b5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4eae\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4eae\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u01b0\u1ee3ng (light, clear)"}, {"front": "l\u01b0\u1ee3ng (light, clear)", "id": "1440405298408", "back": "l\u01b0\u1ee3ng (light, clear)  <hr id=answer>  \u4eae <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/4e0da3f8-f9e3-4450-9493-723cef9457b5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4eae\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4eae\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8868", "id": "1440405349885", "back": "\u8868 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/effcdace-deb2-4621-b435-7783f6a078bc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8868\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8868\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  bi\u1ec3u (outside, speak/announce)"}, {"front": "bi\u1ec3u (outside, speak/announce)", "id": "1440405349886", "back": "bi\u1ec3u (outside, speak/announce)  <hr id=answer>  \u8868 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/effcdace-deb2-4621-b435-7783f6a078bc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8868\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8868\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u653e", "id": "1440405401892", "back": "\u653e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7a3570e2-044c-434b-9887-9e4f885ce9be/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u653e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u653e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u00f3ng (send/throw)"}, {"front": "ph\u00f3ng (send/throw)", "id": "1440405401893", "back": "ph\u00f3ng (send/throw)  <hr id=answer>  \u653e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7a3570e2-044c-434b-9887-9e4f885ce9be/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u653e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u653e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5047", "id": "1440405485460", "back": "\u5047 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b4722bea-54a9-4084-91c3-c4b27f888822/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5047\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5047\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u1ea3 (fake)"}, {"front": "gi\u1ea3 (fake)", "id": "1440405485461", "back": "gi\u1ea3 (fake)  <hr id=answer>  \u5047 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b4722bea-54a9-4084-91c3-c4b27f888822/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5047\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5047\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9ec4", "id": "1440405555648", "back": "\u9ec4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f88a150f-2225-42a7-85ed-c70583add3c6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9ec4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9ec4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u9ec3 ho\u00e0ng (yellow/king color; last name)"}, {"front": "\u9ec3 ho\u00e0ng (yellow/king color; last name)", "id": "1440405555649", "back": "\u9ec3 ho\u00e0ng (yellow/king color; last name)  <hr id=answer>  \u9ec4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f88a150f-2225-42a7-85ed-c70583add3c6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9ec4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9ec4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u666f", "id": "1440405608200", "back": "\u666f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/86fb5886-ac20-4b04-a6f9-ba0b265146ef/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u666f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u666f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ea3nh (scene, situation)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea3nh (scene, situation)", "id": "1440405608201", "back": "c\u1ea3nh (scene, situation)  <hr id=answer>  \u666f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/86fb5886-ac20-4b04-a6f9-ba0b265146ef/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u666f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u666f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7167", "id": "1440405674359", "back": "\u7167 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/16eb0735-5e64-4e7e-a5dd-7287392d4d6a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7167\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7167\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  chi\u1ebfu (shine, following/according to)"}, {"front": "chi\u1ebfu (shine, following/according to)", "id": "1440405674360", "back": "chi\u1ebfu (shine, following/according to)  <hr id=answer>  \u7167 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/16eb0735-5e64-4e7e-a5dd-7287392d4d6a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7167\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7167\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6162", "id": "1440621122643", "back": "\u6162 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/86875687-2506-4cf1-8177-67574f76bdcf/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6162\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6162\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1ea1n (arrogant, lazy/slow)"}, {"front": "m\u1ea1n (arrogant, lazy/slow)", "id": "1440621122645", "back": "m\u1ea1n (arrogant, lazy/slow)  <hr id=answer>  \u6162 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/86875687-2506-4cf1-8177-67574f76bdcf/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6162\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6162\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7968", "id": "1440621194471", "back": "\u7968 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/0a1dff4f-42cd-4045-8c29-acb0b3b3ce26/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7968\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7968\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  phi\u1ebfu (ticket), phi\u00eau (light/lofty)"}, {"front": "phi\u1ebfu (ticket), phi\u00eau (light/lofty)", "id": "1440621194472", "back": "phi\u1ebfu (ticket), phi\u00eau (light/lofty)  <hr id=answer>  \u7968 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/0a1dff4f-42cd-4045-8c29-acb0b3b3ce26/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7968\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7968\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ef7", "id": "1440621278804", "back": "\u4ef7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/be46efe9-6daa-45e3-8100-29c4e61c18ec/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ef7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ef7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u1edbi, gi\u00e1 (price/value)"}, {"front": "gi\u1edbi, gi\u00e1 (price/value)", "id": "1440621278805", "back": "gi\u1edbi, gi\u00e1 (price/value)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ef7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/be46efe9-6daa-45e3-8100-29c4e61c18ec/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ef7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ef7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u529e", "id": "1440621403826", "back": "\u529e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/7c5d03c0-cfd0-46e6-8850-53fcc8a8aedc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u529e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u529e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u8fa6 b\u1ea1n, bi\u1ec7n (do/execute)"}, {"front": "\u8fa6 b\u1ea1n, bi\u1ec7n (do/execute)", "id": "1440621403827", "back": "\u8fa6 b\u1ea1n, bi\u1ec7n (do/execute)  <hr id=answer>  \u529e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/7c5d03c0-cfd0-46e6-8850-53fcc8a8aedc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u529e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u529e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65c5", "id": "1440621451534", "back": "\u65c5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/44264132-7495-4829-b8bc-ba58af569855/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65c5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65c5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1eef (division/army, travel)"}, {"front": "l\u1eef (division/army, travel)", "id": "1440621451535", "back": "l\u1eef (division/army, travel)  <hr id=answer>  \u65c5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/44264132-7495-4829-b8bc-ba58af569855/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65c5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65c5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u51b3", "id": "1440621643557", "back": "\u51b3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/7a555ed8-2ad0-4412-8e43-a1f454ee421e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51b3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51b3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  quy\u1ebft (decide, cut/open)"}, {"front": "quy\u1ebft (decide, cut/open)", "id": "1440621643558", "back": "quy\u1ebft (decide, cut/open)  <hr id=answer>  \u51b3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/7a555ed8-2ad0-4412-8e43-a1f454ee421e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u51b3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u51b3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u73a9", "id": "1440621679499", "back": "\u73a9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/d4c78089-7d7e-4cf4-a16a-1548e8e07e46/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u73a9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u73a9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ngo\u1ea1n (play, triffle with)"}, {"front": "ngo\u1ea1n (play, triffle with)", "id": "1440621679500", "back": "ngo\u1ea1n (play, triffle with)  <hr id=answer>  \u73a9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/d4c78089-7d7e-4cf4-a16a-1548e8e07e46/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u73a9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u73a9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6c5f", "id": "1440621723446", "back": "\u6c5f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/13c52f9c-4002-4a41-97c7-658500971405/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c5f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c5f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  giang (big river)"}, {"front": "giang (big river)", "id": "1440621723447", "back": "giang (big river)  <hr id=answer>  \u6c5f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/13c52f9c-4002-4a41-97c7-658500971405/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6c5f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6c5f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8239", "id": "1440621750957", "back": "\u8239 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/ef71d507-b7d4-45f4-8686-5532bbb563e6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8239\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8239\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thuy\u1ec1n (ship/boat)"}, {"front": "thuy\u1ec1n (ship/boat)", "id": "1440621750958", "back": "thuy\u1ec1n (ship/boat)  <hr id=answer>  \u8239 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/ef71d507-b7d4-45f4-8686-5532bbb563e6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8239\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8239\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9644", "id": "1440621931878", "back": "\u9644 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/ce3be824-0d25-4887-8941-6e90315c3e52/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9644\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9644\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u1ee5 (to add, to attach, to be close to, to be attached, to adhere to, to append, to rely on)"}, {"front": "ph\u1ee5 (to add, to attach, to be close to, to be attached, to adhere to, to append, to rely on)", "id": "1440621931879", "back": "ph\u1ee5 (to add, to attach, to be close to, to be attached, to adhere to, to append, to rely on)  <hr id=answer>  \u9644 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/ce3be824-0d25-4887-8941-6e90315c3e52/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9644\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9644\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7eff", "id": "1440621981899", "back": "\u7eff <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/a7df12c6-97cf-4286-b7e3-0d36e3d5a47c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7eff\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7eff\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u7da0 l\u1ee5c (green, chlorine)"}, {"front": "\u7da0 l\u1ee5c (green, chlorine)", "id": "1440621981900", "back": "\u7da0 l\u1ee5c (green, chlorine)  <hr id=answer>  \u7eff <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/a7df12c6-97cf-4286-b7e3-0d36e3d5a47c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7eff\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7eff\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u706f", "id": "1440622001457", "back": "\u706f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/1f2a813b-414d-487a-b53f-f77ebdc28ec7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u706f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u706f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u71c8 \u0111\u0103ng (light)"}, {"front": "\u71c8 \u0111\u0103ng (light)", "id": "1440622001458", "back": "\u71c8 \u0111\u0103ng (light)  <hr id=answer>  \u706f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/1f2a813b-414d-487a-b53f-f77ebdc28ec7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u706f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u706f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5411", "id": "1440656787548", "back": "\u5411 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/df07885c-11ce-4096-8e90-5ee6114408b7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5411\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5411\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u01b0\u1edbng (direction, old/former/in the past)"}, {"front": "h\u01b0\u1edbng (direction, old/former/in the past)", "id": "1440656787552", "back": "h\u01b0\u1edbng (direction, old/former/in the past)  <hr id=answer>  \u5411 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/df07885c-11ce-4096-8e90-5ee6114408b7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5411\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5411\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u62d0", "id": "1440656826418", "back": "\u62d0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/8a4c0ccb-77ba-4eb6-a2a4-85d565266473/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u62d0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u62d0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  qu\u1ea3i (to kidnap, to abduct, to turn, crutch)"}, {"front": "qu\u1ea3i (to kidnap, to abduct, to turn, crutch)", "id": "1440656826420", "back": "qu\u1ea3i (to kidnap, to abduct, to turn, crutch)  <hr id=answer>  \u62d0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/8a4c0ccb-77ba-4eb6-a2a4-85d565266473/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u62d0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u62d0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5f2f", "id": "1440656880522", "back": "\u5f2f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/793eb867-5a8a-459a-a2db-cd078cff7086/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f2f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f2f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u5f4e loan (bend/bow)"}, {"front": "\u5f4e loan (bend/bow)", "id": "1440656880523", "back": "\u5f4e loan (bend/bow)  <hr id=answer>  \u5f2f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/793eb867-5a8a-459a-a2db-cd078cff7086/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f2f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f2f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u573a", "id": "1440656954182", "back": "\u573a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/3b474e34-9b1c-44a0-b740-2079cafa9394/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u573a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u573a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u5834 tr\u00e0ng, tr\u01b0\u1eddng (field, stage/show)"}, {"front": "\u5834 tr\u00e0ng, tr\u01b0\u1eddng (field, stage/show)", "id": "1440656954183", "back": "\u5834 tr\u00e0ng, tr\u01b0\u1eddng (field, stage/show)  <hr id=answer>  \u573a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/3b474e34-9b1c-44a0-b740-2079cafa9394/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u573a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u573a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6e05", "id": "1440657046583", "back": "\u6e05 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/4bb21c02-31a5-4860-ab88-5825d33a9c99/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6e05\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6e05\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thanh (clear, quiet, cool)"}, {"front": "thanh (clear, quiet, cool)", "id": "1440657046584", "back": "thanh (clear, quiet, cool)  <hr id=answer>  \u6e05 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/4bb21c02-31a5-4860-ab88-5825d33a9c99/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6e05\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6e05\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u695a", "id": "1440657111565", "back": "\u695a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/afc0b865-c7ae-411d-a15a-30751806ba1a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u695a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u695a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u1edf (pain, orderly/clear, last name/ancient country name)"}, {"front": "s\u1edf (pain, orderly/clear, last name/ancient country name)", "id": "1440657111566", "back": "s\u1edf (pain, orderly/clear, last name/ancient country name)  <hr id=answer>  \u695a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/afc0b865-c7ae-411d-a15a-30751806ba1a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u695a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u695a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5212", "id": "1440657227088", "back": "\u5212 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/fb1c2553-06f8-4195-9b51-d66da1c22954/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5212\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5212\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  hoa (row/paddle; worth/profitable), ho\u1ea1ch (divide/plan),&nbsp;h\u1ecda (drawing)"}, {"front": "hoa (row/paddle; worth/profitable), ho\u1ea1ch (divide/plan),&nbsp;h\u1ecda (drawing)", "id": "1440657227089", "back": "hoa (row/paddle; worth/profitable), ho\u1ea1ch (divide/plan),&nbsp;h\u1ecda (drawing)  <hr id=answer>  \u5212 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/fb1c2553-06f8-4195-9b51-d66da1c22954/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5212\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5212\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u80de", "id": "1440657314515", "back": "\u80de <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/b62ec6d2-dea2-43d8-9533-91e4b3af8272/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u80de\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u80de\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00e0o (amniotic sac)"}, {"front": "b\u00e0o (amniotic sac)", "id": "1440657314516", "back": "b\u00e0o (amniotic sac)  <hr id=answer>  \u80de <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/b62ec6d2-dea2-43d8-9533-91e4b3af8272/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u80de\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u80de\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5951", "id": "1440658989635", "back": "\u5951 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/4fe3d2c3-ca33-4425-b791-275fd4508529/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5951\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5951\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u1ebf (contract, deed/title)"}, {"front": "kh\u1ebf (contract, deed/title)", "id": "1440658989637", "back": "kh\u1ebf (contract, deed/title)  <hr id=answer>  \u5951 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/4fe3d2c3-ca33-4425-b791-275fd4508529/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5951\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5951\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u82b9", "id": "1440659026471", "back": "\u82b9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/12bb7fa9-52c3-4173-a115-026bc5d20cc1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82b9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82b9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ea7n (Rau c\u1ea7n Petroselinum crispum)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea7n (Rau c\u1ea7n Petroselinum crispum)", "id": "1440659026473", "back": "c\u1ea7n (Rau c\u1ea7n Petroselinum crispum)  <hr id=answer>  \u82b9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/12bb7fa9-52c3-4173-a115-026bc5d20cc1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u82b9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u82b9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6545", "id": "1440659150005", "back": "\u6545 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/880f38f6-8eca-43be-89d4-5196c9dd73b7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6545\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6545\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ed1 (origin/original; deceased/old, attempt/try)"}, {"front": "c\u1ed1 (origin/original; deceased/old, attempt/try)", "id": "1440659150006", "back": "c\u1ed1 (origin/original; deceased/old, attempt/try)  <hr id=answer>  \u6545 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/880f38f6-8eca-43be-89d4-5196c9dd73b7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6545\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6545\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5373", "id": "1440659260108", "back": "\u5373 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/5db57a48-3fb4-49ed-9a4f-d99340c39768/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5373\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5373\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ee9c (near/now; Th\u00ec. D\u00f9ng nh\u01b0 t\u1eafc \u5247)"}, {"front": "t\u1ee9c (near/now; Th\u00ec. D\u00f9ng nh\u01b0 t\u1eafc \u5247)", "id": "1440659260109", "back": "t\u1ee9c (near/now; Th\u00ec. D\u00f9ng nh\u01b0 t\u1eafc \u5247)  <hr id=answer>  \u5373 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/5db57a48-3fb4-49ed-9a4f-d99340c39768/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5373\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5373\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ea6", "id": "1440659313045", "back": "\u4ea6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/307b82aa-6a05-4666-8602-5185985abbfe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ea6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ea6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  di\u1ec7c (also)"}, {"front": "di\u1ec7c (also)", "id": "1440659313046", "back": "di\u1ec7c (also)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ea6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/307b82aa-6a05-4666-8602-5185985abbfe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ea6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ea6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u66f4", "id": "1440659433037", "back": "\u66f4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f226c185-d3d8-450e-a455-0e665e7802c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66f4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66f4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  canh (more, improve, change, time period), c\u00e1nh (also, completely)"}, {"front": "canh (more, improve, change, time period), c\u00e1nh (also, completely)", "id": "1440659433038", "back": "canh (more, improve, change, time period), c\u00e1nh (also, completely)  <hr id=answer>  \u66f4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f226c185-d3d8-450e-a455-0e665e7802c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66f4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66f4\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53e5", "id": "1440659491122", "back": "\u53e5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/70c20fa5-d971-45d4-bd74-47cd94536e48/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53e5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53e5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00fa, c\u00e2u (sentence, hook)"}, {"front": "c\u00fa, c\u00e2u (sentence, hook)", "id": "1440659491123", "back": "c\u00fa, c\u00e2u (sentence, hook)  <hr id=answer>  \u53e5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/70c20fa5-d971-45d4-bd74-47cd94536e48/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53e5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53e5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u91c7", "id": "1440659535917", "back": "\u91c7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/6fff5989-98e7-4f30-8a3e-c386f46aca54/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u91c7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u91c7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ea3i, th\u00e1i (gather/harvest)"}, {"front": "th\u1ea3i, th\u00e1i (gather/harvest)", "id": "1440659535918", "back": "th\u1ea3i, th\u00e1i (gather/harvest)  <hr id=answer>  \u91c7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/6fff5989-98e7-4f30-8a3e-c386f46aca54/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u91c7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u91c7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ed1", "id": "1440659608045", "back": "\u4ed1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/c42e6ec0-fbe8-4cde-afc4-fb0406dd9c34/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ed1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ed1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u4f96 lu\u00e2n, l\u00f4n (order)"}, {"front": "\u4f96 lu\u00e2n, l\u00f4n (order)", "id": "1440659608046", "back": "\u4f96 lu\u00e2n, l\u00f4n (order)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ed1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/c42e6ec0-fbe8-4cde-afc4-fb0406dd9c34/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ed1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ed1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u67ec", "id": "1440659764512", "back": "\u67ec <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/c17142f0-9656-46b1-a134-5d31fe53b0c8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u67ec\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u67ec\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  gi\u1ea3n (Th\u01b0 t\u1eeb, thi\u1ebfp. \u00a7 Th\u00f4ng gi\u1ea3n \u7c21)"}, {"front": "gi\u1ea3n (Th\u01b0 t\u1eeb, thi\u1ebfp. \u00a7 Th\u00f4ng gi\u1ea3n \u7c21)", "id": "1440659764513", "back": "gi\u1ea3n (Th\u01b0 t\u1eeb, thi\u1ebfp. \u00a7 Th\u00f4ng gi\u1ea3n \u7c21)  <hr id=answer>  \u67ec <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/c17142f0-9656-46b1-a134-5d31fe53b0c8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u67ec\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u67ec\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5b8c", "id": "1440659854232", "back": "\u5b8c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/4739dd08-85f9-4076-af7c-cd04d5516bba/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b8c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b8c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ho\u00e0n (perfect, complete; submit/lose)"}, {"front": "ho\u00e0n (perfect, complete; submit/lose)", "id": "1440659854233", "back": "ho\u00e0n (perfect, complete; submit/lose)  <hr id=answer>  \u5b8c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/4739dd08-85f9-4076-af7c-cd04d5516bba/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b8c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b8c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e76", "id": "1440660162471", "back": "\u5e76 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/627e5515-cdde-4de5-aadb-e6a97def56b0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e76\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e76\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ecbnh (together, also) t\u00ednh (combine/annex)"}, {"front": "t\u1ecbnh (together, also) t\u00ednh (combine/annex)", "id": "1440660162472", "back": "t\u1ecbnh (together, also) t\u00ednh (combine/annex)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e76 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/627e5515-cdde-4de5-aadb-e6a97def56b0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e76\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e76\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8463", "id": "1440660210105", "back": "\u8463 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f4b5fe29-422d-4166-8e17-410a8b1404c6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8463\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8463\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ed5ng (last name, manage)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ed5ng (last name, manage)", "id": "1440660210106", "back": "\u0111\u1ed5ng (last name, manage)  <hr id=answer>  \u8463 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f4b5fe29-422d-4166-8e17-410a8b1404c6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8463\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8463\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5df7", "id": "1440660228359", "back": "\u5df7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/ad71c987-3b63-4f26-a161-6eecb9110426/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5df7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5df7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ea1ng (alley)"}, {"front": "h\u1ea1ng (alley)", "id": "1440660228360", "back": "h\u1ea1ng (alley)  <hr id=answer>  \u5df7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/ad71c987-3b63-4f26-a161-6eecb9110426/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5df7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5df7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u91cd", "id": "1440660301659", "back": "\u91cd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/0397577d-ea61-4d4d-9313-b174168a4828/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u91cd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u91cd\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u1ecdng (heavy), tr\u00f9ng (repeat/duplicate)"}, {"front": "tr\u1ecdng (heavy), tr\u00f9ng (repeat/duplicate)", "id": "1440660301660", "back": "tr\u1ecdng (heavy), tr\u00f9ng (repeat/duplicate)  <hr id=answer>  \u91cd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/0397577d-ea61-4d4d-9313-b174168a4828/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u91cd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u91cd\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u54b8", "id": "1440660385334", "back": "\u54b8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/deed423f-4cf0-43b2-bb3c-725b66ce08ec/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u54b8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u54b8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u00e0m (salted; all, common)"}, {"front": "h\u00e0m (salted; all, common)", "id": "1440660385335", "back": "h\u00e0m (salted; all, common)  <hr id=answer>  \u54b8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/deed423f-4cf0-43b2-bb3c-725b66ce08ec/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u54b8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u54b8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u620c", "id": "1440660430247", "back": "\u620c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f462548e-0318-47a2-a9d6-5b3084536fa9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u620c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u620c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tu\u1ea5t (11th branch, 7 pm - 9 pm)"}, {"front": "tu\u1ea5t (11th branch, 7 pm - 9 pm)", "id": "1440660430248", "back": "tu\u1ea5t (11th branch, 7 pm - 9 pm)  <hr id=answer>  \u620c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f462548e-0318-47a2-a9d6-5b3084536fa9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u620c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u620c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u996e", "id": "1440660500860", "back": "\u996e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/512fb9d7-511d-47b1-952a-e0d3e734f18f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u996e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u996e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u1ea9m (drink)"}, {"front": "\u1ea9m (drink)", "id": "1440660500861", "back": "\u1ea9m (drink)  <hr id=answer>  \u996e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/512fb9d7-511d-47b1-952a-e0d3e734f18f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u996e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u996e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8c37", "id": "1440660529033", "back": "\u8c37 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f38d6ae3-d6b4-498d-9566-a8a16df4a605/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c37\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c37\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ed1c (grain, valley)"}, {"front": "c\u1ed1c (grain, valley)", "id": "1440660529034", "back": "c\u1ed1c (grain, valley)  <hr id=answer>  \u8c37 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f38d6ae3-d6b4-498d-9566-a8a16df4a605/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c37\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c37\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65a5", "id": "1440660586699", "back": "\u65a5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/a49678a5-e5f6-4e1c-9f11-ef553f0e47c1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65a5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65a5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u00edch (criticize, use/spend)"}, {"front": "x\u00edch (criticize, use/spend)", "id": "1440660586700", "back": "x\u00edch (criticize, use/spend)  <hr id=answer>  \u65a5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/a49678a5-e5f6-4e1c-9f11-ef553f0e47c1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65a5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65a5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6b21", "id": "1440660630445", "back": "\u6b21 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/855b39b6-8cae-4751-b078-fa7dc4d6586b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b21\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b21\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u1ee9 (secondary/inferior)"}, {"front": "th\u1ee9 (secondary/inferior)", "id": "1440660630446", "back": "th\u1ee9 (secondary/inferior)  <hr id=answer>  \u6b21 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/855b39b6-8cae-4751-b078-fa7dc4d6586b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b21\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b21\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6614", "id": "1440660713988", "back": "\u6614 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/eec8829f-477b-490b-a4eb-4259668644c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6614\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6614\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00edch (old day)"}, {"front": "t\u00edch (old day)", "id": "1440660713989", "back": "t\u00edch (old day)  <hr id=answer>  \u6614 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/eec8829f-477b-490b-a4eb-4259668644c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6614\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6614\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u752b", "id": "1440660767781", "back": "\u752b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/202ce629-8faf-4245-a52c-6644c11a536f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u752b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u752b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u1ee7 (Ti\u1ebfng g\u1ecdi t\u00f4n qu\u00fd c\u1ee7a \u0111\u00e0n \u00f4ng, just recently)"}, {"front": "ph\u1ee7 (Ti\u1ebfng g\u1ecdi t\u00f4n qu\u00fd c\u1ee7a \u0111\u00e0n \u00f4ng, just recently)", "id": "1440660767782", "back": "ph\u1ee7 (Ti\u1ebfng g\u1ecdi t\u00f4n qu\u00fd c\u1ee7a \u0111\u00e0n \u00f4ng, just recently)  <hr id=answer>  \u752b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/202ce629-8faf-4245-a52c-6644c11a536f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u752b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u752b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u660c", "id": "1440660842358", "back": "\u660c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/1d485f8d-dbd7-4a9f-a823-4405204a060a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u660c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u660c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u01b0\u01a1ng (straightforward/proper, good; prosperous)"}, {"front": "x\u01b0\u01a1ng (straightforward/proper, good; prosperous)", "id": "1440660842359", "back": "x\u01b0\u01a1ng (straightforward/proper, good; prosperous)  <hr id=answer>  \u660c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/1d485f8d-dbd7-4a9f-a823-4405204a060a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u660c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u660c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u662d", "id": "1440660962762", "back": "\u662d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/92fcabf5-5f95-40b3-82f5-81ed23f740a0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u662d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u662d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  chi\u00eau (bright, light)"}, {"front": "chi\u00eau (bright, light)", "id": "1440660962763", "back": "chi\u00eau (bright, light)  <hr id=answer>  \u662d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/92fcabf5-5f95-40b3-82f5-81ed23f740a0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u662d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u662d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53ec", "id": "1440661037197", "back": "\u53ec <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/8e1891e1-a2eb-443b-99ba-bb051eb8ab03/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53ec\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53ec\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tri\u1ec7u (summon, invite)"}, {"front": "tri\u1ec7u (summon, invite)", "id": "1440661037198", "back": "tri\u1ec7u (summon, invite)  <hr id=answer>  \u53ec <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/8e1891e1-a2eb-443b-99ba-bb051eb8ab03/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53ec\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53ec\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u76fe", "id": "1440661072248", "back": "\u76fe <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/b92db717-cce9-41be-b12e-125a28f24ed7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76fe\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76fe\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thu\u1eabn (shield, support)"}, {"front": "thu\u1eabn (shield, support)", "id": "1440661072249", "back": "thu\u1eabn (shield, support)  <hr id=answer>  \u76fe <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/b92db717-cce9-41be-b12e-125a28f24ed7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76fe\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76fe\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6cb3", "id": "1441410523255", "back": "\u6cb3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/48c57891-aa8d-4fd0-9cc8-5600ef3bad60/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6cb3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6cb3\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u00e0 (river)"}, {"front": "h\u00e0 (river)", "id": "1441410523256", "back": "h\u00e0 (river)  <hr id=answer>  \u6cb3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/48c57891-aa8d-4fd0-9cc8-5600ef3bad60/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6cb3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6cb3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u592c", "id": "1441410579826", "back": "\u592c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/0d98c15c-0244-42cb-94f4-65af9cd97b7a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u592c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u592c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  Qu\u1ebb Qu\u00e1i, ngh\u0129a l\u00e0 quy\u1ebft h\u1eb3n."}, {"front": "Qu\u1ebb Qu\u00e1i, ngh\u0129a l\u00e0 quy\u1ebft h\u1eb3n.", "id": "1441410579827", "back": "Qu\u1ebb Qu\u00e1i, ngh\u0129a l\u00e0 quy\u1ebft h\u1eb3n.  <hr id=answer>  \u592c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/0d98c15c-0244-42cb-94f4-65af9cd97b7a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u592c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u592c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6f02", "id": "1441410668294", "back": "\u6f02 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/571d7381-e89d-4f62-a2d6-3d2e38292c7f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6f02\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6f02\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  phi\u00eau (to float, to drift, be tossed about, to bleach(piao3), elegant(piao4), polished(piao4))"}, {"front": "phi\u00eau (to float, to drift, be tossed about, to bleach(piao3), elegant(piao4), polished(piao4))", "id": "1441410668295", "back": "phi\u00eau (to float, to drift, be tossed about, to bleach(piao3), elegant(piao4), polished(piao4))  <hr id=answer>  \u6f02 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/571d7381-e89d-4f62-a2d6-3d2e38292c7f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6f02\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6f02\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5f55", "id": "1441410726048", "back": "\u5f55 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/11379c51-44c2-4871-a7c8-121363015b63/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f55\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f55\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u9304 l\u1ee5c (copy/record, select/hire)"}, {"front": "\u9304 l\u1ee5c (copy/record, select/hire)", "id": "1441410726049", "back": "\u9304 l\u1ee5c (copy/record, select/hire)  <hr id=answer>  \u5f55 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/11379c51-44c2-4871-a7c8-121363015b63/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f55\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f55\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u867d", "id": "1441410782436", "back": "\u867d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f26b2bff-ddf8-4aa8-b16b-c9cac780ffd0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u867d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u867d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u96d6 tuy (however)"}, {"front": "\u96d6 tuy (however)", "id": "1441410782437", "back": "\u96d6 tuy (however)  <hr id=answer>  \u867d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f26b2bff-ddf8-4aa8-b16b-c9cac780ffd0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u867d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u867d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ed8", "id": "1441410833686", "back": "\u4ed8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/613f0f31-a451-464b-a2df-55e4a3e17a94/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ed8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ed8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u00f3 (give/delegate, spend)"}, {"front": "ph\u00f3 (give/delegate, spend)", "id": "1441410833687", "back": "ph\u00f3 (give/delegate, spend)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ed8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/613f0f31-a451-464b-a2df-55e4a3e17a94/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ed8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ed8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53e6", "id": "1441410863208", "back": "\u53e6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/544ce55e-472f-48dc-b56d-6859173d6b25/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53e6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53e6\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u00e1nh (other)"}, {"front": "l\u00e1nh (other)", "id": "1441410863209", "back": "l\u00e1nh (other)  <hr id=answer>  \u53e6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/544ce55e-472f-48dc-b56d-6859173d6b25/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53e6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53e6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bef", "id": "1441410911638", "back": "\u8bef <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/53ab87a1-ec67-4ed4-80cd-de9929a4434e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bef\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bef\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ng\u1ed9 (mistake, confused)"}, {"front": "ng\u1ed9 (mistake, confused)", "id": "1441410911639", "back": "ng\u1ed9 (mistake, confused)  <hr id=answer>  \u8bef <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/53ab87a1-ec67-4ed4-80cd-de9929a4434e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bef\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bef\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53a8", "id": "1441410999611", "back": "\u53a8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/78601038-6855-4694-9b19-4b004f7a2506/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53a8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53a8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u5eda tr\u00f9 (kitchen; chest)"}, {"front": "\u5eda tr\u00f9 (kitchen; chest)", "id": "1441410999612", "back": "\u5eda tr\u00f9 (kitchen; chest)  <hr id=answer>  \u53a8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/78601038-6855-4694-9b19-4b004f7a2506/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53a8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53a8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u623f", "id": "1441411033277", "back": "\u623f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/fd7f1972-89f2-41fb-af32-c755da2cb495/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u623f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u623f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u00f2ng (room)"}, {"front": "ph\u00f2ng (room)", "id": "1441411033278", "back": "ph\u00f2ng (room)  <hr id=answer>  \u623f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/fd7f1972-89f2-41fb-af32-c755da2cb495/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u623f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u623f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6696", "id": "1441411055803", "back": "\u6696 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/ce1d43d3-6316-49c5-9818-683c8ff55c0f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6696\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6696\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  no\u00e3n (warm)"}, {"front": "no\u00e3n (warm)", "id": "1441411055804", "back": "no\u00e3n (warm)  <hr id=answer>  \u6696 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/ce1d43d3-6316-49c5-9818-683c8ff55c0f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6696\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6696\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6652", "id": "1441411083293", "back": "\u6652 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e9e4382b-d0ef-49ad-b535-ad0401478583/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6652\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6652\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u00e1i (hang to dry)"}, {"front": "s\u00e1i (hang to dry)", "id": "1441411083294", "back": "s\u00e1i (hang to dry)  <hr id=answer>  \u6652 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e9e4382b-d0ef-49ad-b535-ad0401478583/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6652\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6652\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9633", "id": "1441411111276", "back": "\u9633 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/9c9bd011-3fe1-4821-abe8-cc0d4d111f91/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9633\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9633\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u01b0\u01a1ng (sun, positive, male)"}, {"front": "d\u01b0\u01a1ng (sun, positive, male)", "id": "1441411111277", "back": "d\u01b0\u01a1ng (sun, positive, male)  <hr id=answer>  \u9633 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/9c9bd011-3fe1-4821-abe8-cc0d4d111f91/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9633\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9633\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8212", "id": "1441411208816", "back": "\u8212 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7c7130f7-c207-4faf-a159-009d0778bc0d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8212\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8212\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u01b0 (flex/relax)"}, {"front": "th\u01b0 (flex/relax)", "id": "1441411208817", "back": "th\u01b0 (flex/relax)  <hr id=answer>  \u8212 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7c7130f7-c207-4faf-a159-009d0778bc0d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8212\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8212\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u670d", "id": "1441411548691", "back": "\u670d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d4ac842f-e8bc-46ae-abb5-d29eeb1925d1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u670d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u670d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ph\u1ee5c (clothes; do/follow)"}, {"front": "ph\u1ee5c (clothes; do/follow)", "id": "1441411548692", "back": "ph\u1ee5c (clothes; do/follow)  <hr id=answer>  \u670d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d4ac842f-e8bc-46ae-abb5-d29eeb1925d1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u670d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u670d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7740", "id": "1441411909234", "back": "\u7740 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e80dcccf-3dbf-4ea3-90ec-273e40a4651a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7740\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7740\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u8457 tr\u1ee9 (write, clear), tr\u01b0\u1edbc (in progress), tr\u1eef<div>to catch, to receive, to suffer, to make move, to take action, auxiliary word (always behind verb)</div>"}, {"front": "\u8457 tr\u1ee9 (write, clear), tr\u01b0\u1edbc (in progress), tr\u1eef<div>to catch, to receive, to suffer, to make move, to take action, auxiliary word (always behind verb)</div>", "id": "1441411909237", "back": "\u8457 tr\u1ee9 (write, clear), tr\u01b0\u1edbc (in progress), tr\u1eef<div>to catch, to receive, to suffer, to make move, to take action, auxiliary word (always behind verb)</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u7740 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e80dcccf-3dbf-4ea3-90ec-273e40a4651a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7740\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7740\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7403", "id": "1441411960994", "back": "\u7403 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/dd05ba83-32ef-4e45-9323-3d1f92083eff/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7403\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7403\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ea7u (ball, numerary for ball-shaped)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea7u (ball, numerary for ball-shaped)", "id": "1441411961025", "back": "c\u1ea7u (ball, numerary for ball-shaped)  <hr id=answer>  \u7403 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/dd05ba83-32ef-4e45-9323-3d1f92083eff/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7403\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7403\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e0c", "id": "1441411990780", "back": "\u5e0c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/98659981-188b-4dc3-939e-b599bb2891c8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e0c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e0c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  hi (rare, unlikely)"}, {"front": "hi (rare, unlikely)", "id": "1441411990782", "back": "hi (rare, unlikely)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e0c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/98659981-188b-4dc3-939e-b599bb2891c8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e0c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e0c\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u671b", "id": "1441412036950", "back": "\u671b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7658c813-9365-4b43-9807-758a0d309ec1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u671b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u671b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u1ecdng (look toward, wish)"}, {"front": "v\u1ecdng (look toward, wish)", "id": "1441412036956", "back": "v\u1ecdng (look toward, wish)  <hr id=answer>  \u671b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7658c813-9365-4b43-9807-758a0d309ec1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u671b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u671b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5434", "id": "1442735721703", "back": "\u5434 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/be453e9e-d6d4-45a7-9dbd-fba4baf6c6c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5434\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5434\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u5433 ng\u00f4 (surname Wu, province of Jiangsu, name of Southern China states at different historical periods)"}, {"front": "\u5433 ng\u00f4 (surname Wu, province of Jiangsu, name of Southern China states at different historical periods)", "id": "1442735721704", "back": "\u5433 ng\u00f4 (surname Wu, province of Jiangsu, name of Southern China states at different historical periods)  <hr id=answer>  \u5434 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/be453e9e-d6d4-45a7-9dbd-fba4baf6c6c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5434\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5434\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7136", "id": "1442735862514", "back": "\u7136 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/0cc90639-40e5-4561-91e9-990d3b63d529/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7136\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7136\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nhi\u00ean (but, such)"}, {"front": "nhi\u00ean (but, such)", "id": "1442735862515", "back": "nhi\u00ean (but, such)  <hr id=answer>  \u7136 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/0cc90639-40e5-4561-91e9-990d3b63d529/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7136\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7136\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u820d", "id": "1442735898910", "back": "\u820d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/87d70a7c-5dc5-432e-b173-83868ecf54d0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u820d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u820d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u00e1 (house/housing)"}, {"front": "x\u00e1 (house/housing)", "id": "1442735898911", "back": "x\u00e1 (house/housing)  <hr id=answer>  \u820d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/87d70a7c-5dc5-432e-b173-83868ecf54d0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u820d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u820d\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e88", "id": "1442735975574", "back": "\u4e88 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b6620cf5-cb2c-4c78-95eb-d31236ba5e22/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e88\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e88\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  d\u1eef (Cho, Khen ng\u1ee3i), d\u01b0 (Ta, t\u00f4i)"}, {"front": "d\u1eef (Cho, Khen ng\u1ee3i), d\u01b0 (Ta, t\u00f4i)", "id": "1442735975575", "back": "d\u1eef (Cho, Khen ng\u1ee3i), d\u01b0 (Ta, t\u00f4i)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e88 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b6620cf5-cb2c-4c78-95eb-d31236ba5e22/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e88\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e88\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e03", "id": "1442736022879", "back": "\u5e03 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a1d548c4-0ee2-43a5-8cf6-4d29e04bd89b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e03\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e03\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ed1 (V\u1ea3i, arrange)"}, {"front": "b\u1ed1 (V\u1ea3i, arrange)", "id": "1442736022880", "back": "b\u1ed1 (V\u1ea3i, arrange)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e03 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a1d548c4-0ee2-43a5-8cf6-4d29e04bd89b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e03\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e03\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7230", "id": "1442736085754", "back": "\u7230 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b00604eb-791c-4fd8-b113-072f0621065e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7230\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7230\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  vi\u00ean (then, therefore)"}, {"front": "vi\u00ean (then, therefore)", "id": "1442736085755", "back": "vi\u00ean (then, therefore)  <hr id=answer>  \u7230 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b00604eb-791c-4fd8-b113-072f0621065e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7230\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7230\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6362", "id": "1442736146138", "back": "\u6362 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7c4c83e8-8fde-423b-a624-a10a1186d8b4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6362\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6362\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u63db ho\u00e1n (exchange, change)"}, {"front": "\u63db ho\u00e1n (exchange, change)", "id": "1442736146139", "back": "\u63db ho\u00e1n (exchange, change)  <hr id=answer>  \u6362 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7c4c83e8-8fde-423b-a624-a10a1186d8b4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6362\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6362\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e01", "id": "1442736195070", "back": "\u5e01 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/006fc60b-fa43-430c-9125-cc47c9c24338/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e01\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e01\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u5e63 t\u1ec7 (money)"}, {"front": "\u5e63 t\u1ec7 (money)", "id": "1442736195071", "back": "\u5e63 t\u1ec7 (money)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e01 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/006fc60b-fa43-430c-9125-cc47c9c24338/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e01\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e01\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u56fe", "id": "1442736250067", "back": "\u56fe <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d0f145ce-ed10-4f35-92a5-182a6f1afd99/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u56fe\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u56fe\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u5716 \u0111\u1ed3 (drawing, plan/ambition)"}, {"front": "\u5716 \u0111\u1ed3 (drawing, plan/ambition)", "id": "1442736250068", "back": "\u5716 \u0111\u1ed3 (drawing, plan/ambition)  <hr id=answer>  \u56fe <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d0f145ce-ed10-4f35-92a5-182a6f1afd99/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u56fe\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u56fe\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9986", "id": "1442736302767", "back": "\u9986 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/98a06e47-4453-4878-a65a-c4b102bf05c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9986\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9986\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u9928 qu\u00e1n (business/office/building)"}, {"front": "\u9928 qu\u00e1n (business/office/building)", "id": "1442736302768", "back": "\u9928 qu\u00e1n (business/office/building)  <hr id=answer>  \u9986 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/98a06e47-4453-4878-a65a-c4b102bf05c5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9986\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9986\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7b49", "id": "1442736539152", "back": "\u7b49 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/2fec503a-60ad-43a7-9f9d-4c0130730412/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b49\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b49\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1eb3ng (wait, degree/rank/class, plural word c\u00e1c/ch\u00fang)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1eb3ng (wait, degree/rank/class, plural word c\u00e1c/ch\u00fang)", "id": "1442736539153", "back": "\u0111\u1eb3ng (wait, degree/rank/class, plural word c\u00e1c/ch\u00fang)  <hr id=answer>  \u7b49 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/2fec503a-60ad-43a7-9f9d-4c0130730412/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b49\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b49\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6570", "id": "1442736600572", "back": "\u6570 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/03d60541-019d-4b85-a955-1055c4eaacb9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6570\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6570\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u1ed5, s\u1ed1, s\u00e1c, x\u00fac (count, number, fate)<div>\u6578</div>"}, {"front": "s\u1ed5, s\u1ed1, s\u00e1c, x\u00fac (count, number, fate)<div>\u6578</div>", "id": "1442736600573", "back": "s\u1ed5, s\u1ed1, s\u00e1c, x\u00fac (count, number, fate)<div>\u6578</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u6570 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/03d60541-019d-4b85-a955-1055c4eaacb9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6570\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6570\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9551", "id": "1442736619450", "back": "\u9551 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f144ce1c-713a-4668-a2b2-e292a0ca91a5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9551\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9551\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u938a b\u00e0ng, b\u1ea3ng (pound)"}, {"front": "\u938a b\u00e0ng, b\u1ea3ng (pound)", "id": "1442736619451", "back": "\u938a b\u00e0ng, b\u1ea3ng (pound)  <hr id=answer>  \u9551 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f144ce1c-713a-4668-a2b2-e292a0ca91a5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9551\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9551\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6b27", "id": "1442736668246", "back": "\u6b27 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f83c8fac-06fb-4e36-9689-f16b2cf8b5e4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b27\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b27\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u6b50 \u00e2u (Europe)"}, {"front": "\u6b50 \u00e2u (Europe)", "id": "1442736668247", "back": "\u6b50 \u00e2u (Europe)  <hr id=answer>  \u6b27 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/f83c8fac-06fb-4e36-9689-f16b2cf8b5e4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b27\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b27\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u90ce", "id": "1442736719105", "back": "\u90ce <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/1ecf2236-cb75-4223-976b-3f451ce9d7c4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u90ce\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u90ce\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  lang (M\u0129 x\u01b0ng d\u00f9ng cho \u0111\u00e0n \u00f4ng)"}, {"front": "lang (M\u0129 x\u01b0ng d\u00f9ng cho \u0111\u00e0n \u00f4ng)", "id": "1442736719106", "back": "lang (M\u0129 x\u01b0ng d\u00f9ng cho \u0111\u00e0n \u00f4ng)  <hr id=answer>  \u90ce <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/1ecf2236-cb75-4223-976b-3f451ce9d7c4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u90ce\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u90ce\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8425", "id": "1442736778571", "back": "\u8425 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d28a5360-f3e5-4fb0-bed9-6174aaf106a6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8425\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8425\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u71df doanh (army base, business/manage)"}, {"front": "\u71df doanh (army base, business/manage)", "id": "1442736778572", "back": "\u71df doanh (army base, business/manage)  <hr id=answer>  \u8425 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d28a5360-f3e5-4fb0-bed9-6174aaf106a6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8425\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8425\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5458", "id": "1442736876730", "back": "\u5458 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a2192ae2-fc35-4437-a39f-5241e0b092c4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5458\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5458\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u54e1 vi\u00ean (person/member, measure word for certain kinds of people such as army generals)"}, {"front": "\u54e1 vi\u00ean (person/member, measure word for certain kinds of people such as army generals)", "id": "1442736876731", "back": "\u54e1 vi\u00ean (person/member, measure word for certain kinds of people such as army generals)  <hr id=answer>  \u5458 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a2192ae2-fc35-4437-a39f-5241e0b092c4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5458\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5458\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6000", "id": "1442736958707", "back": "\u6000 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/192b48b6-d0b8-4dba-b11a-3509575e87af/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6000\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6000\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u61f7 ho\u00e0i (recall, pregnant/contain, heart, bosom, to think of, to cherish, mind)"}, {"front": "\u61f7 ho\u00e0i (recall, pregnant/contain, heart, bosom, to think of, to cherish, mind)", "id": "1442736958708", "back": "\u61f7 ho\u00e0i (recall, pregnant/contain, heart, bosom, to think of, to cherish, mind)  <hr id=answer>  \u6000 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/192b48b6-d0b8-4dba-b11a-3509575e87af/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6000\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6000\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ec7", "id": "1442736997054", "back": "\u4ec7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/237b3726-d742-4839-a18a-b92721e308d3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ec7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ec7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1eebu (feud/animosity)"}, {"front": "c\u1eebu (feud/animosity)", "id": "1442736997055", "back": "c\u1eebu (feud/animosity)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ec7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/237b3726-d742-4839-a18a-b92721e308d3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ec7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ec7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6068", "id": "1442737016754", "back": "\u6068 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/edbdcf15-e120-4dc2-a59b-9ce00ff0397c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6068\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6068\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1eadn (hate)"}, {"front": "h\u1eadn (hate)", "id": "1442737016755", "back": "h\u1eadn (hate)  <hr id=answer>  \u6068 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/edbdcf15-e120-4dc2-a59b-9ce00ff0397c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6068\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6068\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5b98", "id": "1443945426620", "back": "\u5b98 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a69112ca-1dd0-4959-91ce-f3780c05bcfd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b98\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b98\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  quan (official, body organ)"}, {"front": "quan (official, body organ)", "id": "1443945426621", "back": "quan (official, body organ)  <hr id=answer>  \u5b98 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a69112ca-1dd0-4959-91ce-f3780c05bcfd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b98\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b98\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5a04&nbsp;", "id": "1443945476832", "back": "\u5a04&nbsp; <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d1d41c30-aa61-4931-b795-80917f945183/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5a04&nbsp;\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5a04&nbsp;\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u5a41 l\u00e2u, l\u0169, lu&nbsp;(a star, last name Lou)"}, {"front": "\u5a41 l\u00e2u, l\u0169, lu&nbsp;(a star, last name Lou)", "id": "1443945476833", "back": "\u5a41 l\u00e2u, l\u0169, lu&nbsp;(a star, last name Lou)  <hr id=answer>  \u5a04&nbsp; <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d1d41c30-aa61-4931-b795-80917f945183/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5a04&nbsp;\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5a04&nbsp;\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u533a", "id": "1443945535062", "back": "\u533a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/41ca6c0a-9bdb-414d-96d1-5c12fefb5ae8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u533a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u533a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u5340 khu, \u00e2u (region)"}, {"front": "\u5340 khu, \u00e2u (region)", "id": "1443945535063", "back": "\u5340 khu, \u00e2u (region)  <hr id=answer>  \u533a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/41ca6c0a-9bdb-414d-96d1-5c12fefb5ae8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u533a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u533a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ec1", "id": "1443945567068", "back": "\u4ec1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e3f2e0c0-c0fc-492a-88ae-e7ee2f118890/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ec1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ec1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nh\u00e2n (humane)"}, {"front": "nh\u00e2n (humane)", "id": "1443945567069", "back": "nh\u00e2n (humane)  <hr id=answer>  \u4ec1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e3f2e0c0-c0fc-492a-88ae-e7ee2f118890/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ec1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ec1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5510", "id": "1443945642804", "back": "\u5510 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/ccbdcf03-9ff3-4710-a60c-afcf9af146e0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5510\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5510\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u01b0\u1eddng (Chinese dynasty)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u01b0\u1eddng (Chinese dynasty)", "id": "1443945642806", "back": "\u0111\u01b0\u1eddng (Chinese dynasty)  <hr id=answer>  \u5510 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/ccbdcf03-9ff3-4710-a60c-afcf9af146e0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5510\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5510\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5012", "id": "1443945673089", "back": "\u5012 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/c7dc0065-5f0f-4600-93c8-71ac0527bf78/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5012\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5012\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ea3o (turn/rotate)<div><br /></div><div>to fall, to collapse, to topple, to fail, to pour, to go bankrupt, to change (trains or buses), to move around, to sell, to speculate (buying and selling), profiteer)</div>"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ea3o (turn/rotate)<div><br /></div><div>to fall, to collapse, to topple, to fail, to pour, to go bankrupt, to change (trains or buses), to move around, to sell, to speculate (buying and selling), profiteer)</div>", "id": "1443945673090", "back": "\u0111\u1ea3o (turn/rotate)<div><br /></div><div>to fall, to collapse, to topple, to fail, to pour, to go bankrupt, to change (trains or buses), to move around, to sell, to speculate (buying and selling), profiteer)</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5012 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/c7dc0065-5f0f-4600-93c8-71ac0527bf78/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5012\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5012\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53d8", "id": "1443945701397", "back": "\u53d8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d8723f31-6980-4283-9716-f904b698996b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53d8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53d8\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u8b8a bi\u1ebfn, bi\u1ec7n (change)"}, {"front": "\u8b8a bi\u1ebfn, bi\u1ec7n (change)", "id": "1443945701398", "back": "\u8b8a bi\u1ebfn, bi\u1ec7n (change)  <hr id=answer>  \u53d8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d8723f31-6980-4283-9716-f904b698996b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53d8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53d8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9526", "id": "1443945747971", "back": "\u9526 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/cde13457-ea2d-4968-ad83-5fc68bac624a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9526\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9526\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ea9m (G\u1ea5m;&nbsp;Nhi\u1ec1u th\u1ee9, nhi\u1ec1u m\u00f3n)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea9m (G\u1ea5m;&nbsp;Nhi\u1ec1u th\u1ee9, nhi\u1ec1u m\u00f3n)", "id": "1443945747972", "back": "c\u1ea9m (G\u1ea5m;&nbsp;Nhi\u1ec1u th\u1ee9, nhi\u1ec1u m\u00f3n)  <hr id=answer>  \u9526 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/cde13457-ea2d-4968-ad83-5fc68bac624a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9526\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9526\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f65", "id": "1443945782763", "back": "\u4f65 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a51e1813-f4c2-4149-b444-510f2c3e4da0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f65\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f65\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u50c9 thi\u00eam (all)"}, {"front": "\u50c9 thi\u00eam (all)", "id": "1443945782764", "back": "\u50c9 thi\u00eam (all)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f65 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a51e1813-f4c2-4149-b444-510f2c3e4da0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f65\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f65\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7eaa", "id": "1443945838551", "back": "\u7eaa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/9ec9a7a3-b52b-4a5a-9226-ccf7336605c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7eaa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7eaa\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  k\u1ec9 (record, law/rule/discipline, age/era/period)"}, {"front": "k\u1ec9 (record, law/rule/discipline, age/era/period)", "id": "1443945838552", "back": "k\u1ec9 (record, law/rule/discipline, age/era/period)  <hr id=answer>  \u7eaa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/9ec9a7a3-b52b-4a5a-9226-ccf7336605c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7eaa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7eaa\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u67e5", "id": "1443945863684", "back": "\u67e5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/02720cb4-7a69-4443-997f-91fc3347ab37/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u67e5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u67e5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tra (look up, investigate)"}, {"front": "tra (look up, investigate)", "id": "1443945863685", "back": "tra (look up, investigate)  <hr id=answer>  \u67e5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/02720cb4-7a69-4443-997f-91fc3347ab37/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u67e5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u67e5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u89c2", "id": "1443945950413", "back": "\u89c2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a7ab155a-a558-45f1-a99f-bb6ca40f9e71/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u89c2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u89c2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  quan (watch/view)"}, {"front": "quan (watch/view)", "id": "1443945950414", "back": "quan (watch/view)  <hr id=answer>  \u89c2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a7ab155a-a558-45f1-a99f-bb6ca40f9e71/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u89c2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u89c2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6b7b", "id": "1443945974809", "back": "\u6b7b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5ba02b69-e688-481b-b092-cf8882bbedbc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b7b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b7b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1eed (death/die)"}, {"front": "t\u1eed (death/die)", "id": "1443945974810", "back": "t\u1eed (death/die)  <hr id=answer>  \u6b7b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5ba02b69-e688-481b-b092-cf8882bbedbc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b7b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b7b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4efb", "id": "1448523433258", "back": "\u4efb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/107370d9-aa06-4904-b967-3dcf9cee2e2d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4efb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4efb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nh\u1eadm/nhi\u1ec7m (assign/appoint, office/responsiblity, last name Ren)"}, {"front": "nh\u1eadm/nhi\u1ec7m (assign/appoint, office/responsiblity, last name Ren)", "id": "1448523433260", "back": "nh\u1eadm/nhi\u1ec7m (assign/appoint, office/responsiblity, last name Ren)  <hr id=answer>  \u4efb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/107370d9-aa06-4904-b967-3dcf9cee2e2d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4efb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4efb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ece", "id": "1448523495633", "back": "\u4ece <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/487b4fea-eff5-4325-a77f-cede327d1d1d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ece\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ece\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00f2ng (from)<div>\u5f9e</div>"}, {"front": "t\u00f2ng (from)<div>\u5f9e</div>", "id": "1448523495634", "back": "t\u00f2ng (from)<div>\u5f9e</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4ece <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/487b4fea-eff5-4325-a77f-cede327d1d1d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ece\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ece\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5440", "id": "1448523529979", "back": "\u5440 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/dbfab595-454e-4a6c-af2e-c37df4c27c13/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5440\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5440\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nha (exclamation word)"}, {"front": "nha (exclamation word)", "id": "1448523529980", "back": "nha (exclamation word)  <hr id=answer>  \u5440 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/dbfab595-454e-4a6c-af2e-c37df4c27c13/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5440\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5440\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u753b", "id": "1448523589782", "back": "\u753b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/590730a0-d433-4000-8908-c3613b4e1b7f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u753b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u753b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  h\u1ecda (drawing)"}, {"front": "h\u1ecda (drawing)", "id": "1448523589783", "back": "h\u1ecda (drawing)  <hr id=answer>  \u753b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/590730a0-d433-4000-8908-c3613b4e1b7f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u753b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u753b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c55", "id": "1448523634969", "back": "\u5c55 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/4900ffa9-f527-4230-b99c-bfa0126a9ee0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c55\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c55\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tri\u1ec3n (expand, show/display)"}, {"front": "tri\u1ec3n (expand, show/display)", "id": "1448523634970", "back": "tri\u1ec3n (expand, show/display)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c55 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/4900ffa9-f527-4230-b99c-bfa0126a9ee0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c55\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c55\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6bd5", "id": "1448523706533", "back": "\u6bd5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/4c632905-cfa7-4342-a88a-1317f0ce9945/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bd5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bd5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ea5t (complete/finish, graduate)"}, {"front": "t\u1ea5t (complete/finish, graduate)", "id": "1448523706534", "back": "t\u1ea5t (complete/finish, graduate)  <hr id=answer>  \u6bd5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/4c632905-cfa7-4342-a88a-1317f0ce9945/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6bd5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6bd5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7a0b", "id": "1448523757312", "back": "\u7a0b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5bcf0939-1da9-4bea-b80a-db2c0c8af3a8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7a0b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7a0b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u00ecnh (journey/trip, schedule/agenda, rule/order, procedure/sequence)"}, {"front": "tr\u00ecnh (journey/trip, schedule/agenda, rule/order, procedure/sequence)", "id": "1448523757313", "back": "tr\u00ecnh (journey/trip, schedule/agenda, rule/order, procedure/sequence)  <hr id=answer>  \u7a0b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5bcf0939-1da9-4bea-b80a-db2c0c8af3a8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7a0b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7a0b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7b51", "id": "1448523797754", "back": "\u7b51 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/039efceb-1c00-4bd5-afcd-c13cce1c019c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b51\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b51\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u00fac (build/building)<div>\u7bc9</div>"}, {"front": "tr\u00fac (build/building)<div>\u7bc9</div>", "id": "1448523797755", "back": "tr\u00fac (build/building)<div>\u7bc9</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u7b51 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/039efceb-1c00-4bd5-afcd-c13cce1c019c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b51\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b51\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8bbe", "id": "1448523831059", "back": "\u8bbe <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7f4d6121-b146-4f7d-8d51-42c7f00d2fc1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bbe\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bbe\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thi\u1ebft (design/build, found/set up)"}, {"front": "thi\u1ebft (design/build, found/set up)", "id": "1448523831060", "back": "thi\u1ebft (design/build, found/set up)  <hr id=answer>  \u8bbe <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7f4d6121-b146-4f7d-8d51-42c7f00d2fc1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bbe\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bbe\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8272", "id": "1448523845035", "back": "\u8272 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e3527c2c-b8ac-4ae3-a18b-ac5cb3d86c7d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8272\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8272\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u1eafc"}, {"front": "s\u1eafc", "id": "1448523845036", "back": "s\u1eafc  <hr id=answer>  \u8272 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e3527c2c-b8ac-4ae3-a18b-ac5cb3d86c7d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8272\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8272\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5ea7", "id": "1448523895682", "back": "\u5ea7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/22438c96-2387-47fe-9e6a-4e3078d67af4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5ea7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5ea7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ecda, t\u00f2a (numerary for building/moutain/large solid things, seat/base/stand)"}, {"front": "t\u1ecda, t\u00f2a (numerary for building/moutain/large solid things, seat/base/stand)", "id": "1448523895683", "back": "t\u1ecda, t\u00f2a (numerary for building/moutain/large solid things, seat/base/stand)  <hr id=answer>  \u5ea7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/22438c96-2387-47fe-9e6a-4e3078d67af4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5ea7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5ea7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6865", "id": "1448523926243", "back": "\u6865 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/0acf279b-d370-43b8-acea-f07d9dd7be8f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6865\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6865\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ki\u1ec1u (bridge)<div><br /></div><div>\u6a4b</div>"}, {"front": "ki\u1ec1u (bridge)<div><br /></div><div>\u6a4b</div>", "id": "1448523926244", "back": "ki\u1ec1u (bridge)<div><br /></div><div>\u6a4b</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u6865 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/0acf279b-d370-43b8-acea-f07d9dd7be8f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6865\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6865\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7b54", "id": "1448523962183", "back": "\u7b54 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/65887fc9-46d6-4e05-b11a-ef0ee5065bbe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b54\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b54\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00e1p (respond, requite)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00e1p (respond, requite)", "id": "1448523962184", "back": "\u0111\u00e1p (respond, requite)  <hr id=answer>  \u7b54 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/65887fc9-46d6-4e05-b11a-ef0ee5065bbe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b54\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b54\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65b0", "id": "1448523978963", "back": "\u65b0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/83003903-db30-4595-aab7-5e1c649f29b9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65b0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65b0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00e2n (new)"}, {"front": "t\u00e2n (new)", "id": "1448523978964", "back": "t\u00e2n (new)  <hr id=answer>  \u65b0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/83003903-db30-4595-aab7-5e1c649f29b9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65b0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65b0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5170", "id": "1448524010723", "back": "\u5170 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/558c01a3-39f2-47ff-9cc0-2f5b9c31f7b6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5170\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5170\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  lan (orchid)<div><br /></div><div>\u862d</div>"}, {"front": "lan (orchid)<div><br /></div><div>\u862d</div>", "id": "1448524010724", "back": "lan (orchid)<div><br /></div><div>\u862d</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5170 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/558c01a3-39f2-47ff-9cc0-2f5b9c31f7b6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5170\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5170\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9648", "id": "1448524072946", "back": "\u9648 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/1c46e1be-0ae8-451c-80b4-0a611aa27490/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9648\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9648\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u1ea7n (last name, explain/tell)"}, {"front": "tr\u1ea7n (last name, explain/tell)", "id": "1448524072947", "back": "tr\u1ea7n (last name, explain/tell)  <hr id=answer>  \u9648 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/1c46e1be-0ae8-451c-80b4-0a611aa27490/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9648\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9648\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c04", "id": "1448524183579", "back": "\u5c04 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d90e3cb7-bd65-49e1-92a4-f4031c1af0a6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c04\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c04\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u1ea1 (shoot)"}, {"front": "x\u1ea1 (shoot)", "id": "1448524183580", "back": "x\u1ea1 (shoot)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c04 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d90e3cb7-bd65-49e1-92a4-f4031c1af0a6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c04\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c04\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7531", "id": "1448524233642", "back": "\u7531 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d9196c1c-8ce5-4955-92d4-a8e1934addbe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7531\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7531\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  do (from/by, because)"}, {"front": "do (from/by, because)", "id": "1448524233643", "back": "do (from/by, because)  <hr id=answer>  \u7531 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d9196c1c-8ce5-4955-92d4-a8e1934addbe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7531\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7531\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5723", "id": "1448524249779", "back": "\u5723 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/aae8ea48-8416-4638-b7c6-d192f062111e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5723\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5723\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00e1nh<div>\u8056</div>"}, {"front": "th\u00e1nh<div>\u8056</div>", "id": "1448524249780", "back": "th\u00e1nh<div>\u8056</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u5723 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/aae8ea48-8416-4638-b7c6-d192f062111e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5723\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5723\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u94a9", "id": "1448524283587", "back": "\u94a9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/29dc9d42-e5a2-4cfc-b214-d9c91e6cf614/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u94a9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u94a9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00e2u (hook)"}, {"front": "c\u00e2u (hook)", "id": "1448524283588", "back": "c\u00e2u (hook)  <hr id=answer>  \u94a9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/29dc9d42-e5a2-4cfc-b214-d9c91e6cf614/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u94a9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u94a9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6487", "id": "1448524349557", "back": "\u6487 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/ea165fa6-9b63-43ed-a1e0-2cd1e3e0c533/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6487\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6487\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  phi\u1ebft (\u4e3f left-falling stroke, throw)"}, {"front": "phi\u1ebft (\u4e3f left-falling stroke, throw)", "id": "1448524349558", "back": "phi\u1ebft (\u4e3f left-falling stroke, throw)  <hr id=answer>  \u6487 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/ea165fa6-9b63-43ed-a1e0-2cd1e3e0c533/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6487\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6487\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e08", "id": "1448524382501", "back": "\u4e08 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/2189d32c-3350-4cab-9d60-116486c4ad21/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e08\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e08\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u01b0\u1ee3ng (old unit of length)"}, {"front": "tr\u01b0\u1ee3ng (old unit of length)", "id": "1448524382502", "back": "tr\u01b0\u1ee3ng (old unit of length)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e08 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/2189d32c-3350-4cab-9d60-116486c4ad21/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e08\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e08\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e1b", "id": "1448524424960", "back": "\u5e1b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/73d46f7e-52ea-405c-a394-3583fc79e7b5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e1b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e1b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ea1ch (silk)"}, {"front": "b\u1ea1ch (silk)", "id": "1448524424961", "back": "b\u1ea1ch (silk)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e1b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/73d46f7e-52ea-405c-a394-3583fc79e7b5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e1b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e1b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u63d0", "id": "1448524474843", "back": "\u63d0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/1c9f5005-6edb-45f1-8aa3-386fd90e4ede/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u63d0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u63d0\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ec1 (propose, mention/nominate, upwards character stroke(calligraphy))"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ec1 (propose, mention/nominate, upwards character stroke(calligraphy))", "id": "1448524474844", "back": "\u0111\u1ec1 (propose, mention/nominate, upwards character stroke(calligraphy))  <hr id=answer>  \u63d0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/1c9f5005-6edb-45f1-8aa3-386fd90e4ede/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u63d0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u63d0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6b79", "id": "1448524506105", "back": "\u6b79 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/21030618-c2b4-4e01-b561-29bf6baffba2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b79\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b79\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u00e3i (bad/wrong)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00e3i (bad/wrong)", "id": "1448524506106", "back": "\u0111\u00e3i (bad/wrong)  <hr id=answer>  \u6b79 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/21030618-c2b4-4e01-b561-29bf6baffba2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b79\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b79\">Etymology</a>"}]